<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://cur.lv/5xyoe">
<channel>
  <title>RSSMix.com Mix ID 3845704</title>
  <generator>RSSMix</generator>
  <link>http://cur.lv/65yf1</link>
  <description>This feed was created by mixing existing feeds from various sources.</description>
  <language>en-gb</language>
  
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [NEM] NEM -New Economy Movement - No Envy Movement - Updates+Discussion thread]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[I'd say we should stop discussing that. There're lots of ways to prevent having more then 2-3 stakes. Let's wait until 4000 stakes are bought and then check legitimity. If someone bought more then 2-3 stakes he'll just lose his money.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 04:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [ANN] [PMC] Premine! - 100% Premine / 100% Distribution - Mining TX fees only]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700td]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[I will not close the thread, not to worry. <br><br><br>In other news: my "reward bot" is finished and running. this should help ensure rewards for every block mined for the time being. <br>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 04:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: Silkroad 2.0]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700te]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/700tf">Quote from: zneww on <b>Today</b> at 04:22:39 AM</a></div><div>you guys slay me&nbsp; <img src="http://cur.lv/65yf8" alt="Wink" border="0"><br></div><br>No need for us to interfere.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 04:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [ANN] [PMC] Premine! - 100% Premine / 100% Distribution - Mining TX fees only]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[We need the new wallet and atomic-trade to add the coin!]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 04:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: Hacking a BFL Single/25 to 48gh and beyond.....]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700th]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/700ti">Quote from: southerngentuk on <b>Today</b> at 02:39:37 AM</a></div><div><div><a href="http://cur.lv/700tj">Quote from: helipotte on January 31, 2014, 12:57:55 AM</a></div><div><br>Also, installing a 7.5K resistor was very successful. &nbsp;Gained 3Ghs (57-60) and error ...</div></div>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 04:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Hong Kong ATM Location]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I was wondering if any of your guys know the exact location of the bitcoin atm in Hong Kong? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>rand0mize</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 03:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What hash rate should I expect using a BiFury with USB2.0 rather than USB3.0?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tl]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm considering the <a href="http://cur.lv/700tm" rel="nofollow">BiFury</a> which is generates ~5GH/s on a USB3 port. They say,</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Miner is designed to be used with USB 3.0 port or USB 3.0 hub (must meet min. 0.9A per port to achieve full hashrate)
  USB 2.0 support is also available but hashrate will be lower.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>However they don't quote an expected hash rate for USB2.0. Will it be significantly lower?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>boyfarrell</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 03:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can Bitcoin Save the Postal Service?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700tn"><img src="http://cur.lv/700to" alt="Can Bitcoin Save the Postal Service?" title="Can Bitcoin Save the Postal Service?"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700tp"> cryptocurrencylive </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700tq">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700tn">[5 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 02:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin v0.9: Release Candidate 1 released]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700tr"><img src="http://cur.lv/700ts" alt="Bitcoin v0.9: Release Candidate 1 released" title="Bitcoin v0.9: Release Candidate 1 released"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700tt"> httpteapot </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700tu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700tr">[9 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 02:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Searching through the blockchain]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700tv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>When a miner includes a transaction in a block, according to the integrity rules the miner should search for a previous transaction which output the coins being used in the current transaction. Now, the previous transaction is a record stored somewhere deep inside the blockchain.</p>

<p>What is the time taken to search and validate the previous txn output in the blockchain data structure?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Smagula</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 02:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[[ANN] EternalCoin now on an exchange [ETC] low-difficulty - Scrypt]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv0l(ann)-eternalcoin-now-on-an-exchange-(etc)-low-difficulty-scrypt/msg7451/#msg7451]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<br><div align="center"><img src="http://cur.lv/700tw" alt=""><br>Logo created by unique9 There is a <a href="http://cur.lv/700tx" target="_blank">logo contest</a> happening now in which you can win 50,000 ETC<br><span><span><strong>Eterna...</strong></span></span></div>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 01:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How rich are you compared to other r/Bitcoin readers? (Survey)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ty]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I often find myself wondering how I compare to others my age in r/Bitcoin. </p> <p>I've created a short survey on Google docs. Please only fill out the survey once, and be honest with your responses. You know, for science. </p> <p>I will post the results in graph form to r/Bitcoin on 2/5/2014.</p> <p>For privacy and security purposes, please do not post the amount of Bitcoin you own in this thread, unless you create a disposable or just don't care. </p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700tz">http://cur.lv/700tz</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700u0"> BTCSurvey </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700ty">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ty">[12 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 01:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Sun-Times Experiments With Bitcoin Paywall on Saturday]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700u1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700u1"><img src="http://cur.lv/700u2" alt="Sun-Times Experiments With Bitcoin Paywall on Saturday" title="Sun-Times Experiments With Bitcoin Paywall on Saturday"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjrk"> anthonykantara </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700u3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700u1">[6 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 01:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[You can now Send flowers Online with Bitcoins!! www.bloomnation.com]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700u4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Thought this was awesome!... came across this site that accepts BTC as a form of payment to send flowers to ppl.... <a href="http://cur.lv/700u5" target="_blank">www.bloomnation.com</a>&nbsp; &nbsp;<img src="http://cur.lv/700u6" alt=":)" title="Smiley">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 00:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin exchange at bitcoins4currency and Mtgox]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700u7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>i did some ex at bitcoins4currency, what you think about this site? they pay a good price i think is a good way to sell bitcoins, i have a lot of bitcoins stuck at Mtgox, i asked them to transfer to bitcoins4currency but they dont answer, i dont understant what is going on mtgox.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user11781</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 23:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Talking to bitcoind thru web browser returns empty JSON document]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700u8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I am attempting to access bitcoind's http-json-rpc api thru firefox. I enter the following URL </p>

<pre><code>http://cur.lv/700u9
</code></pre>

<p>and it returns</p>

<pre><code>There was an error parsing the JSON document. The document may not be well-formed.
Document contents:
</code></pre>

<p>So the document contents are empty, but when I inspect element and look at the response, I get </p>

<pre><code>Status-code: 404 Not Found
Connection: Close
Content-Type: "application/json"
Server: "bitcoin-json-rpc/v0.8.2-815-g5f083af-beta"
</code></pre>

<p>So the server is replying, but doesn't recognize the request or something. </p>

<p>My bitcoin.conf file reads</p>

<pre><code>rpcuser=user
rpcpassword=password
rpcport=8332
</code></pre>

<p>If I do </p>

<pre><code> http://cur.lv/700ua
</code></pre>

<p>instead, it gives me a 500 Internal Server Error</p>

<p>Any idea what is missing?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Zeemer</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 23:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is best secure payment method for bitcoin used in development e-commerce website?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ub]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>What is best secure payment method for bitcoin used in development e-commerce website ?</p>

<p>I means bitcoin-qt via JSON-RPC <strong>(bitcoind server)</strong>  or blockchain.info API or others <strong>(third party systems)</strong></p>

<p>edit: i will create website accept bitcoin and send bitcoin, what is best method to do that with high security ?</p>

<p>i know may be wrong bitcoin-qt store private keys in my server but blockchain api(third party systems) store in his website, and he can access this private keys, right ?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user3258732</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 22:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[blockchain no tab for new shared key seems to have gone]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700uc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>for some reason there is no tab that allows to create a new shared key </p>

<p>does any one no why the tab missing or is it only me ??</p>

<p>any help will be great</p>

<p>it was deffo there this morning </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>billy</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 22:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[CampBX Has Been Dropped By Their Bitcoin Fearing Bank; They've Halted ACH And Wire Transfers In And Out]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ud]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ud"><img src="http://cur.lv/700ue" alt="CampBX Has Been Dropped By Their Bitcoin Fearing Bank; They've Halted ACH And Wire Transfers In And Out" title="CampBX Has Been Dropped By Their Bitcoin Fearing Bank; They've Halted ACH And Wire Transfers In And Out"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700uf"> bitbybitbybitcoin </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700ug">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ud">[17 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[NXT – Proof of Stake and the New Alternative Altcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700uh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>When the crypto community thinks of altcoin, cryptocurrencies like Litecoin, Dogecoin, and Peercoin are usually first on their mind. We have seen a growing number of altcoin since Bitcoin&rsquo;s introduction in 2009, simply because of the rapid adoption of cryptocurrencies all over the world. But is it possible to have an alternative altcoin? The new and innovative altcoin NXT and its developers have made it possible. Less than a month ago, NXT launched their brand new digital currency, and soon after signed BTER as an exchange partner. With no mining on the network, NXT is the most energy efficient cryptocurrency, because the &ldquo;forging&rdquo; process requires little processing power. Forging NXT can even be done from a mobile device. The new [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700uh">NXT &ndash; Proof of Stake and the New Alternative Altcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/700uh"><img width="300" height="158" src="http://cur.lv/700ui" alt="nxt_logo_blue_300px"></a><p dir="ltr">When the crypto community thinks of altcoin, cryptocurrencies like Litecoin, Dogecoin, and Peercoin are usually first on their mind. We have seen a growing number of altcoin since Bitcoin&rsquo;s introduction in 2009, simply because of the rapid adoption of cryptocurrencies all over the world. But is it possible to have an alternative altcoin? The new and innovative altcoin NXT and its developers have made it possible.</p>
<p>Less than a month ago, NXT launched their brand new digital currency, and soon after signed BTER as an exchange partner. With no mining on the network, NXT is the most energy efficient cryptocurrency, because the &ldquo;forging&rdquo; process requires little processing power. Forging NXT can even be done from a mobile device.</p>
<p><strong>The new Alt-Altcoin?</strong></p>
<p>The way NXT works is completely different from that of Bitcoin as it uses completely different algorithms for mining. In fact, the developers created NXT completely from scratch, in order to create the new alt-altcoin. The different algorithms used allow NXT users to mine with exponentially less computing power. NXT uses Proof of Stake (PoS), a concept initially pioneered by Peercoin, rather than Proof of Work, used by Bitcoin and other coins.</p>
<p><strong>NXT and Proof of Stake</strong></p>
<p>As the first 100% Proof of Stake digital currency written from the ground-up, NXT is creating a new path on which altcoins can be built from. Unlike Proof of Work currencies like Bitcoin, the currency is secured by owners of already existing coins that receive a portion of transaction fees for forging a NXT block. A user is chosen to solve a block depending on their stake in the market, which allows everyone on the network to have the same reward potential.</p>
<p>The idea behind NXT and Proof of Stake is to generate coins without using vast amounts of energy as the Bitcoin network does. This is done through the network, by calculating the amount of coins each user has and randomly selecting who will forge the next block. Everyone knows who will be mining the next block in the blockchain, making it impossible for a user to convince the network that a transaction didn&rsquo;t occur.</p>
<p>Additionally, the network can detect which accounts do not participate in PoS and also recognize users forging a fraudulent block. A process called Transparent Forging enables the network to decrease the attacker&rsquo;s mining power to zero and keep the NXT network secure.</p>
<p><strong>Reducing Double Spending and 51% Attacks</strong></p>
<p>NXT eliminates the possibility of double spending and 51% attacks, because each user knows who is responsible for forging the next block of transactions. A fork in the blockchain simply does not exist with the newest alt-altcoin. What Transparent Forging and PoS provides to NXT is something new for cryptocurrencies. Transactions continue to remain anonymous and secure, but unlike Bitcoin, each transaction requires less user confirmation, making digital transactions even more efficient.</p>
<p>NXT is the first cryptocurrency that has been completely rewritten and is 100% Proof of Stake. Other altcoins like Peercoin, only uses PoS for a portion of its coins and uses Proof of Work for the rest. Digital currencies, most namely Bitcoin, along with other altcoins like Peercoin use mining to create new coins, working together to solve each block. This is the main point of difference with NXT &ndash; instead of mining new coins, NXT has already produced them. This enables the NXT network to focus on solving blocks and increase transaction efficiency, while decreasing power consumption for users.</p>
<p><strong>What&rsquo;s Next for NXT?</strong></p>
<p>As with any alternative coin, NXT is very new to the cryptocurrency community. The entire market consists of 1 billion coins, all created by the NXT developers, and are currently worth just under $74,000,000USD. NXT also provides an alias system, arbitrary messaging at Block 40,000, asset exchange and a decentralized domain name system. There is no question that NXT warrants its own category, as the world&rsquo;s first alt-altcoin entirely based on Proof of Stake. With the growing popularity of cryptocurrency, the future looks very bright for NXT.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700uh">NXT &ndash; Proof of Stake and the New Alternative Altcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam Hofman</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 21:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Acknowledgement (data networks) - Wikipedia, the free ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2j(data_networks)]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[In data networking, an acknowledgement (or acknowledgment) is a signal passed between communicating processes or computers to signify acknowledgement, or receipt of ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[CampBX news: Unfortunately we have some bad news regarding our ACH and WIRE Processor]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700uj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700uk"> campbx </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700ul">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700uj">[32 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 21:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Keith Rabois; Paypal &amp; Square engineer: There is no chance Bitcoin becomes successful in the USA, period, end of story.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700um]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700um"><img src="http://cur.lv/700un" alt="Keith Rabois; Paypal &amp; Square engineer: There is no chance Bitcoin becomes successful in the USA, period, end of story." title="Keith Rabois; Paypal &amp; Square engineer: There is no chance Bitcoin becomes successful in the USA, period, end of story."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700uo"> absurdity69 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700up">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700um">[61 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 21:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[AntiPolygraph.org: Learn the Truth About Lie Detectors]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yjn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Non-profit, public interest website dedicated to exposing and ending polygraph waste, fraud, and abuse.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[were has the shared tab gone on re]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700uq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>does any one no why there is no shared tab any more on blockchaine on received tab</p>

<p>I loged in just now and can not see it any more any help will be great </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>billy</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[assetID for account on smart contract now optional]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ur]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>assetID for account on smart contract now optional

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>assetID for account on smart contract now optional

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[get a f*cking laptop for f*cking bitcoins.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700us]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700us"><img src="http://cur.lv/700ut" alt="get a f*cking laptop for f*cking bitcoins." title="get a f*cking laptop for f*cking bitcoins."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/63ig9"> neofatalist </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700uu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700us">[37 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How can I import blockchain.dat into bitcoind?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700uv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm getting the latest torrent and I'm running bitcoind on my linux box. How can I import this once it's downloaded?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ryan Detzel</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Hi Reddit, New West Technologies here! We created a Bitpay integration for POS. Ask us anything!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700uw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Here is a link to see the integration in action: <del><a href="http://cur.lv/700ux">http://cur.lv/700ux</a></del> </p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700uy">http://cur.lv/700uy</a></p> <p>Here is a link to the Yahoo Finance article: <a href="http://cur.lv/700uz">http://cur.lv/700uz</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700v0"> Newestech </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700uw">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700uw">[13 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitpay tweets Overstock: Pay your employees in Bitcoin? We've got the API for it.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700v1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700v1"><img src="http://cur.lv/63ig8" alt="Bitpay tweets Overstock: Pay your employees in Bitcoin? We've got the API for it." title="Bitpay tweets Overstock: Pay your employees in Bitcoin? We've got the API for it."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700v2"> zoopz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700v3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700v1">[21 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Vasalgel (Long-term Male Contraceptive with 100% Effectiveness) Needs Donations. Guess what they now accept...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700v4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Vasalgel is basically a completely reversible vasectomy by injection. One injection lasts about a decade, and the stuff in the syringe costs less than the syringe itself. The injection to undo it is pretty much just water and baking soda. Drug companies don't want to fund it, they make way more selling hormone pills to women.</p> <p>Their clinical trials need funding to make this available. That's a worthy cause in my book. Let's show them what we do.</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700v5">Home Page</a></p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700v6">Facebook Page</a></p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700v7">Donation Page</a></p> <p>Edit: Corrections</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700v8"> The_Ugliest_Man_Ever </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700v4">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700v4">[44 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Block first transaction]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700v9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin wiki <a href="http://cur.lv/700va" rel="nofollow">states</a>:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>the first transaction of a block is, with few exceptions, the
  transaction that grants those coins to their recipient (the miner)</p>
</blockquote>

<p>How are those "few exceptions"? When is the first transaction of a block not the miner reward?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Randomblue</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Overstock CEO Reveals He Now Holds Millions in Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vb"><img src="http://cur.lv/700vc" alt="Overstock CEO Reveals He Now Holds Millions in Bitcoin" title="Overstock CEO Reveals He Now Holds Millions in Bitcoin"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg69"> Egon_1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700vd">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vb">[51 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Meltdown becomes first comic store to take Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ve]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ve"><img src="http://cur.lv/700vf" alt="Meltdown becomes first comic store to take Bitcoin" title="Meltdown becomes first comic store to take Bitcoin"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vg"> tea-girl </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700vh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ve">[5 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ten Ripple Labs User Stories. How we got involved.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vj"> busterzzz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700vk">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vi">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: Bitcoin Giveaway - FREE]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vl]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[16tTBZ1uWWjjRGuyRs2j1Q6DAcR8xA7ieM]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 18:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Add USD - BTC to Google Currency Converter.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vn"> umlal </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700vo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vm">[17 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 18:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Estonia Central Bank Warns Bitcoin Could be a Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vp"><img src="http://cur.lv/700vq" alt="Estonia Central Bank Warns Bitcoin Could be a Ponzi Scheme" title="Estonia Central Bank Warns Bitcoin Could be a Ponzi Scheme"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vr"> 4204lfe </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700vs">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vp">[31 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 18:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Investing in Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[One topic I am often asked about by clients is investing in Bitcoin. Not just bitcoins the currency, but Bitcoin, the network and technology ecosystem. The conversation usually starts like, &ldquo;I have X amount of money to invest in Bitcoin, how should I invest it?&rdquo; After giving the disclaimer that I am not a licensed [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>John Light</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Coincove - Mexican Bitcoin exchange]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vu]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey guys, I am with the <a href="http://cur.lv/700vv">coincove</a> team.</p> <p>Just wanted to drop by and announce that after a few months of trying many different things we realized that exclusively relying on local Bitcoin communities was seriously going to limit the impact and rate of adoption we wanted to achieve. We were getting ahead of ourselves (bitcoiners, such an ambitious bunch) and after very much appreciated advice from our mentors and members from <a href="http://cur.lv/700vw">boost.vc</a>&rsquo;s founding team, we have decided to take a step back and modify our plan of attack. We are setting up a robust and reliable exchange to serve Mexico and then we will go after Western Union.</p> <p>If all goes well, hopefully by the next time you visit Cabo or Playa you will be able to pay for your beach micheladas using Bitcoins.</p> <p>Anyways, site is in Spanish - for obvious reasons &ndash; but if you happen to know some Mexicans please point them in our direction. We will soon have an English version too.</p> <p>Cheers, The Coincove team</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vx"> talme </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700vu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vu">[51 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Very impressed with multi device behavior of Bit Message]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I just started testing BitMessage across my multiple computers. I aes-256 encrypted my keys.dat file and put in the cloud. I've got multiple machines now with the same keys.</p> <p>So far the behavior of sending and receiving messages across multiple devices has been exactly as one would expect. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vz"> zmanian </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700w0">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vy">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fan Gets Tattoo of His Public Bitcoin Address]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700w1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>A man from Whidbey Island, Washington recently got his public bitcoin address tattooed to his forearm trying to get it done in time for the Superbowl. Nai sent me a message before heading to the tattoo studio. &ldquo;Hello BTC Mag, I had a great idea that just popped into my head, and I don&rsquo;t know if it&rsquo;s because of my medical marijuana kicking in or I just can&rsquo;t stop thinking about bitcoin. My name is Nai Saephan and I live on Whidbey Island, a suburb I guess you can call it, located about an hour north of Seattle. I heard about bitcoins about 3 months ago and every breath I take and every walk I step I can&rsquo;t get bitcoin [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700w1">Bitcoin Fan Gets Tattoo of His Public Bitcoin Address</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/700w1"><img width="950" height="350" src="http://cur.lv/700w2" alt="bitmap"></a><p dir="ltr">A man from Whidbey Island, Washington recently got his public bitcoin address tattooed to his forearm trying to get it done in time for the Superbowl. Nai sent me a message before heading to the tattoo studio.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Hello BTC Mag, I had a great idea that just popped into my head, and I don&rsquo;t know if it&rsquo;s because of my medical marijuana kicking in or I just can&rsquo;t stop thinking about bitcoin. My name is Nai Saephan and I live on Whidbey Island, a suburb I guess you can call it, located about an hour north of Seattle. I heard about bitcoins about 3 months ago and every breath I take and every walk I step I can&rsquo;t get bitcoin out of my head. I have been trying to tell more and more people about bitcoin, but living on a island its kind of hard. Now don&rsquo;t get me wrong, the island isn&rsquo;t small by any means but here on the south end we don&rsquo;t have fast food restaurants except a Dairy Queen that is exceptionally slow and takes about 10 minutes for 2 cheeseburgers and a drink. Our restaurants are pretty much closed by 9 pm and gas stations by 11. But there is a lot of money on this island to be spent on bitcoins.&rdquo;</p>
<p>I suggested to him he may want to do a henna QR code, but he went through the tattoo and sent pictures. The tattoo parlor he chose was <a href="http://cur.lv/700w3">Bayside Tattoo</a>, in Oak Harbor, WA.</p>
<p><img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700w4" width="240px;" height="320px;"><img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700w5" width="240px;" height="320px;"><img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700w6" width="320px;" height="240px;"><img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700w7" width="240px;" height="320px;"><img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700w8" width="240px;" height="320px;"><img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700w9" width="240px;" height="320px;"></p>
<p dir="ltr">I couldn&rsquo;t get the QR to scan, but he was able to get a new business to take Bitcoins. Nai shot off this message after getting his tattoo.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Haha so it&rsquo;s done and I have a Bitcoin Qr code tattooed on my right forearm. I have tried to see if it would read yet, but it&rsquo;s still kind of lumpy. Overall I am happy with the tattoo. Pictures don&rsquo;t do it justice yet. I honestly don&rsquo;t even care if it works or not. I did it to get the interest of bitcoin out there. And you know what, it worked already. On our return trip home my buddy took me to a new restaurant that just reopened in a new location, <a href="http://cur.lv/700wa">The Roaming Radish</a>. We went inside and he showed the owners my new tattoo and that was their tipping point as my friend has been trying to talk them into accepting bitcoin since they reopened a few weeks ago at their new location. For them to see someone who embraces BTC so much that they got a QR code tattooed on their body meant that bitcoin is getting widespread and is legitimate.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you are in the Whidbey Island / Seattle area, feel free to go help the Roaming Radish set up Bitcoin payments if they haven&rsquo;t already. If they have, head over and grab a meal with your Bitcoins.</p>
<p><span>Roaming Radish</span></p>
<p>5023 Harbor Hills Dr, Freeland, WA 98249</p>
<p dir="ltr">(360) 331-5939</p>
<p dir="ltr">fb: <a href="http://cur.lv/700wb">http://cur.lv/700wb</a></p>
<p><span>Here&rsquo;s Nai&rsquo;s info in case you wanted to give him a pat on the back</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Tattooed address: <a href="http://cur.lv/700wc">1HDt5hfxYg9KathZcNz9B2QRGic8aeDUte</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">reddit username: <a href="http://cur.lv/700wd">Whidbeyislandshibe</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;<img alt="Displaying 1111.png" src="http://cur.lv/700we"></p>
<p><em>update: I changed the previous QR code at Nai&rsquo;s request. Previous one and this one should both resolve to the address he provided (<a href="http://cur.lv/700wc">1HDt5hfxYg9KathZcNz9B2QRGic8aeDUte</a>)</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700w1">Bitcoin Fan Gets Tattoo of His Public Bitcoin Address</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ruben Alexander</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to check status of an order on BTC-e API?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>It would appear there is no way of obtaining fill notifications for active orders.</p>

<p>If I am mistaken, please enlighten me!</p>

<p>When orders are submitted to a BTC-e account, either via API or their website, and they are NOT instantly filled, they get assigned an OrderID integer. I can query the authenticated API for account info, which will give me back a list of all Active Orders and associated OIDs, but aside from having my program maintain a list of what it "thinks" are Active, versus what actually is active on the account by sending a query every X seconds, I do not know of a simpler/faster way to determine what orders got filled or when.</p>

<p>I also would like some clarification on the <code>status</code> field of the order response from API. it would appear <code>0</code> is <code>active</code> and <code>1</code> is <code>filled</code>. What are the values for <code>partial fill</code> and <code>cancelled</code>? </p>

<p>There is also a way to see <code>All</code> orders on the website by going to <code>Finances</code>-&gt;<code>Orders History</code> and then the drop down for <code>Show All</code>, is there a corresponding API call for that?</p>

<p>I need to be able to monitor for partial and complete fills.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>ACVentures</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Trend , support and resistance levels]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[BTCXINDIA is providing technical analysis of trend, support and resistance.For latest updates on trend, visit <a href="http://cur.lv/700wh" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/700wi</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[not revieving my bitcoins (GUIminer, BTC guild)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wj(guiminer-btc-guild)/msg7447/#msg7447]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[hello,<br>i started mining with my (slow) nvidea GPU , just to test it, i think i want to buy a 2.2 GHZ ASIC.<br>well i accepted at least already an 25 shares but the BTC Guild site in not showing then.... <br>i use (in GUIminer) the option "other" and fill it ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[We wanted /r/bitcoin to be the first to know that our Sci-Fi Indie MMO has begun accepting Bitcoins as a payment option!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey reddit! My name is Marty and I&rsquo;m the community manager over at Star Sonata 2, an indie massively multiplayer online science fiction game that is fast approaching it's TEN year anniversary this year!</p> <p>We&rsquo;re happy to announce that <a href="http://cur.lv/700wl">Star Sonata 2</a> is now accepting bitcoin as a payment option! Bitcoin is ideal for us because we have a very international player-base, with the majority of our players living outside the US. We often get requests for different payment options or currencies but are unable to accommodate everyone. Star Sonata is an MMO with one server, which means everyone around the world plays together. As a truly international currency, we hope that Bitcoin will allow Star Sonata to reach even more people from around the world and really enrich our global community! </p> <p>Our game is free for the first 80% or so of the game with only the end game and building permanent assets requiring the subscription. </p> <p>If you'd like to show your support for us, but don't want to give us your precious bitcoins just yet, we could really use your vote on <a href="http://cur.lv/700wm">steam greenlight</a>! You can find out more about the features of the game there. I have a feeling you guys will like the game because the in game economy isn't touched by admins and is completely player controlled. The game is also developed by a bunch of people who don&rsquo;t like regulated currencies. :)</p> <p>And finally here&rsquo;s a review done about the game a few months ago to give you an idea of the game! <a href="http://cur.lv/700wn">http://cur.lv/700wn</a> Our current trailer is a bit outdated, but you can catch it on our steam greenlight page. :P</p> <p>I reddit way too much for my own good, so I&rsquo;ll be around all day if anyone has any questions about the game or our bitcoin support. </p> <p>P.S: Congratulations on 100,000 subscribers! :D </p> <p>Edit: It appears as though we are one of the first standalone, full featured (non casino) games to accept bitcoin! Awesome! </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700wo"> Bageese </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700wk">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wk">[15 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Another crash predictor bites the dust]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wp"><img src="http://cur.lv/700wq" alt="Another crash predictor bites the dust" title="Another crash predictor bites the dust"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700wr"> btcnr </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700ws">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wp">[66 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How stupid are they? "So this leads to the risk that creators of bitcoin can disappear with all people's money" - Official announcement by Lithuanian Central Bank]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wt"><img src="http://cur.lv/700wu" alt="How stupid are they? &quot;So this leads to the risk that creators of bitcoin can disappear with all people's money&quot; - Official announcement by Lithuanian Central Bank" title="How stupid are they? &quot;So this leads to the risk that creators of bitcoin can disappear with all people's money&quot; - Official announcement by Lithuanian Central Bank"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700wv"> MtGoxx </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700ww">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wt">[103 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[PSA: Do NOT store a wallet backup in your Dropbox. It is NOT SECURE.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>At least once a week I see someone with 2FA turned on who somehow loses coins from whatever service, and one of the common threads that comes up is storing backups (even encrypted (though weakly)) in Dropbox. This is not secure and your coins will be stolen.</p> <p>Don't do it. If you have already done it, start a new wallet and transfer your coins to it asap, then delete all traces of the old one.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700wy"> davvblack </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700wx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wx">[145 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 15:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[比特信 BitMessage]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yj8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[&#27604;&#29305;&#20449;&#65288;Bitmessage&#65289;&#26159;&#19968;&#31181;&#29992;&#26469;&#21521;&#21478;&#19968;&#20010;&#20154;&#25110;&#32773;&#20854;&#23427;&#22810;&#20010;&#35746;&#38405;&#32773;&#21457;&#36865;&#21152;&#23494;&#28040;&#24687;&#30340;&#21327;&#35758;&#12290;&#23427;&#26159;&#19968;&#20010;p2p&#30340;&#21435;&#20013;&#24515;&#21270;&#21644;&#26080;&#39035;&#31532;&#19977;&#26041;&#25552;&#20379; ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[US Treasury confirms Bitcoin miners and investors won't be regulated]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wz"><img src="http://cur.lv/700x0" alt="US Treasury confirms Bitcoin miners and investors won't be regulated" title="US Treasury confirms Bitcoin miners and investors won't be regulated"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700x1"> ancientbearwizard </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700x2">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700wz">[211 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 14:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[cgminer api-allow using dns instead of IP address]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700x3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I am wondering why cgminer is not accepting dns instead of IP addresses</p>

<p>I need to allow a server by it's dns...is it possible?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Royi Mindel</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 14:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Silk Road Vendor Filing Claim For Seized Bitcoins, Argues He Sold Only Legal Items]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700x4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700x4"><img src="http://cur.lv/700x5" alt="Silk Road Vendor Filing Claim For Seized Bitcoins, Argues He Sold Only Legal Items" title="Silk Road Vendor Filing Claim For Seized Bitcoins, Argues He Sold Only Legal Items"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700x6"> Elpoepbarc </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700x7">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700x4">[265 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can each Bitcoin and Satoshi be uniquely identified?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700x8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm pretty sure I've read somewhere that BitCoins have an "address", so they can be uniquely identified.</p>

<p>What I want to know is:</p>

<ol><li>Does each Satoshi have it's own unique identity?</li>
<li>How is the identity of a Satoshi formatted? (providing 1 is true)</li>
</ol>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>series0ne</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 14:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Fate Is in the Hands of Clueless Regulators | Wired Enterprise]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700x9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/700x9"><img src="http://cur.lv/700xa" alt="Bitcoin's Fate Is in the Hands of Clueless Regulators | Wired Enterprise" title="Bitcoin's Fate Is in the Hands of Clueless Regulators | Wired Enterprise"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700x6"> Elpoepbarc </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700xb">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700x9">[111 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 12:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Andreas Antonopoulos TED nomination]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Forgive me for re-posting a hot topic on the very same subject but I want to make a more clear attempt to try and entice people to nominate Andreas for a TED conference on Bitcoin. This will greately benifit the proliferation of Bitcoin and thus make society a better place.</p> <p>The link to nominate a speaker is <a href="http://cur.lv/700xd">http://cur.lv/700xd</a></p> <p>It will ask for several bits of information of the speaker you are nominating which might be off putting if you are on time constraints but please take the time to fill these in as a small effort can have a big effect!</p> <p>I will put here serveral bits of information that you will require to make it easier!</p> <p>Contact telephone: 1 888-998-2918 Email: <a href="mailto:media@antonopoulos.com">media@antonopoulos.com</a></p> <p>The section on TED that asks you about the speaker credentials can be found on Andreas website: <a href="http://cur.lv/700xe">http://cur.lv/700xe</a> which is a simple copy and paste job.</p> <p>For example, 'Andreas is a passionate technologist, who is well-versed in many technical subjects. He is a serial tech-entrepreneur, having launched businesses in London, New York, and California. He has earned degrees in Computer Science and Data Communications and Distributed Systems from UCL. With experience ranging from hardware and electronics to high level business and financial systems technology consulting and years as CTO/CIO/CSO in many companies &mdash; he combines authority and deep knowledge with an ability to make complex subjects easy to understand. He often brings a fresh perspective to a topic with surprising insights and his ability to identify underlying principles and connections between different topics. More than 200 of his articles on security, cloud computing and data centers have been published in print and syndicated worldwide. His expertise includes Bitcoin, crypto-currencies, Information Security, Cryptography, Cloud Computing, Data Centers, Linux, Open Source and robotics software development. He also has been CISSP certified for 12 years'.</p> <p>TED will also ask for video of the speaker, a high profile one of him on RT news is here</p> <p>ww.youtube.com/watch?v=8l4vgP3Elwg </p> <p>and also a very inspirational one of him in Argentina </p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700xf">http://cur.lv/700xf</a></p> <p>again more videos can be found on his website <a href="http://cur.lv/700xe">http://cur.lv/700xg</a></p> <p>Let's get him on TED!!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700xh"> Panni30 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700xc">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700xc">[28 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 12:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[New cryptocoin fundraising subreddit!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey everyone!</p> <p>Seeing how generous the various cryptocurrency subreddits are, I thought it would be a good idea to work together on achieving bigger and bigger goals. This is why I started <a href="http://cur.lv/700xj">/r/CryptoFundraiser/</a> - a subreddit dedicating to raising money for various selfless projects using any number of coins. You can start your own campaigns there, or just promote your existing fundraisers by linking to them in that subreddit.</p> <p>I am also looking for moderators to help shape the subreddit. I would be happy to accept any existing moderator of a cryptocurrency-focused subreddit as a mod - just let me know :). Other candidates are also welcome to apply, but I would expect a good reputation in the cryptocoin space as a minimum requirement.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokl"> ThePiachu </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700xi">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700xi">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Creating a fake transaction]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>AttackerAlice has a BTC Wallet with 0 BTC.
AccompliceBob has a BTC Wallet.</p>

<p>Is it possible to transfer 100 BTC from AttackerAlice to AccompliceBob? </p>

<p>Suppose a BadMiner accepted this as a valid transaction, and puts this fake transaction into a block, how will it be detected and rejected?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Smagula</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 10:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Silly, but cool: Reddit renames a server "To-The-Moon" in honor of 100k subs on r/Bitcoin.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xl]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700xm"> alprazolame </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700xn">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700xl">[61 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 09:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can you transfer Bitcoins from one address to another address directly without going through the web?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>If you and a recipient both have a wallet on a flash drive, is it then possible to transfer bitcoins from one wallet to the other using a computer without going through the web? </p>

<p>Example in life: "Here you go nephew, I'll give you 5 bitcoins for your birthday." Then we go to the computer with our wallets and transfer the funds, without waiting for people to decrypt bits and pieces of it across the web, just relying on the local computer.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Alex</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 05:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[My computer will not allow me to download bitmessage.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I have been a user of bitmessage for awhile now and I recently got a new computer. I have been trying to download bitmessage onto the new computer which is a lenovo thinkpad running windows 7 and everytime I try to open up the application it says; </p> <p>Cannot open self C:UsersNameDownloadsBitmessage.exe or archive C:UsersNameDownloadsBitmessage.pkg</p> <p>Anyone know what is happening? Thanks! </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700xq"> throwaway456211 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700xr">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700xp">[11 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 00:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Setting Up And Using Bitmessage – An Encrypted ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yic]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[42 Responses to &ldquo;Setting Up And Using Bitmessage &ndash; An Encrypted Communications Platform Based On Bitcoin&rdquo;]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Hearings: A Regulator’s Perspective]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In a municipal building not far from Wall Street, financial regulators, law enforcement, and industry entrepreneurs met this week to discuss the future of virtual currencies, with specific focus on the increased acceptance of Bitcoin. The hearing, which took place on Tuesday and Wednesday, was part of a fact-finding investigation that began last August, and [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700xs">The Bitcoin Hearings: A Regulator&rsquo;s Perspective</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/700xt"><img alt="New York to regulate Bitcoin" src="http://cur.lv/700xu" width="300" height="128"></a><p>New York is set to be the first state to issue clear regulations for virtual currencies. Image: Rick Bowmer/AP</p></div>
<p>In a municipal building not far from Wall Street, financial regulators, law enforcement, and industry entrepreneurs <a href="http://cur.lv/700xv">met this week</a> to discuss the future of virtual currencies, with specific focus on the increased acceptance of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The hearing, which took place on Tuesday and Wednesday, was part of a fact-finding investigation that began last August, and seeks to establish a framework of regulations for virtual currency operators.</p>
<p>During the public hearing, government officials insisted on definite rules for virtual currencies, arguing that the price volatility and decentralized nature of virtual currencies pose risks for users.&nbsp; Additionally, law enforcement officials voiced concerns that the anonymity allowed by crypto-currencies such as Bitcoin lends itself to issues such as the buying and selling of <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv49">illegal goods</a>, money laundering and tax evasion.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/700xv">Cyrus R. Vance, Jr.</a>, the district attorney of New York County was one such voice.&nbsp; &ldquo;The anonymity offered by these payment systems attracts, from time to time, criminals,&rdquo; Vance said.&nbsp; &ldquo;Without stronger government oversight in this area I believe we are going to be permitting cybercriminals, identity thieves and even traffickers of child pornography and other criminal actors to operate in what would be a digital Wild West,&rdquo; he added.</p>
<p>These comments come on the heels of the <a href="http://cur.lv/700xw">arrests of two men</a> earlier this week for allegedly operating a $1 million Bitcoin money-laundering scheme in connection with the now defunct underground Silk Road website.</p>
<p>Even though there are practices in place to detect and act against criminal activity linked to virtual currency, authorities say they are now facing an increased potential for such crimes, and are pushing for rules that will help alleviate these concerns.</p>
<p>In addition to calling for virtual currency exchanges to establish the identities of users to help prevent criminal activity, Vance thinks regulations should also require them to obtain licenses.</p>
<p>Vance stated that virtual currency systems are a form of money transmission and, as such, &ldquo;should be licensed&hellip; to do business in the State of New York and therefore come under that regulatory framework.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Though virtual currency exchanges and companies have had to register as money service businesses under federal guidelines, states have yet to officially classify these exchanges as transmitters of money, allowing them to operate without state licenses.</p>
<p>The New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) has already announced that the new rules might include issuance of a &ldquo;BitLicense,&rdquo; specific to virtual currencies.</p>
<p>Benjamin Lawsky, the New York Superintendent of Financial Services who called for the hearing, believes that his will be the first state to issue clear and comprehensive regulatory guidelines for Bitcoin and other virtual currencies.&nbsp; &ldquo;If we want innovation to happen, and we also want to root out money laundering, and we try to get that balance right, we also want to give businesses certainty,&rdquo; he said.</p>
<p>Being one of the financial centers of the world, getting that balance right could make New York a center for legitimate Bitcoin commerce.&nbsp; Lawsky said his <a href="http://cur.lv/700xx">state is hoping</a> to do something concrete in 2014.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700xs">The Bitcoin Hearings: A Regulator&rsquo;s Perspective</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 21:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[btc2ripple.com by SnapSwap "If you create an account or use our services, we may collect the following types of information: * Contact information - your name, address, phone, email, Skype ID and other similar information." What for? Very Strange Terms!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700xz"> kkoolook </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700y0">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700xy">[6 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 21:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Good resources for learning about encryption/decryption]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700y1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I've been devouring information about bitcoin and bitmessage and distributed computing lately, and I feel I have a good handle on how it all works. The only black box left is the actual encryption used. I'm a computer engineer so I have a good handle on a decent amount of it, but I still don't get how the actual encryption and decryption works. I get how SHA can create message digests of information, but you obviously can't decode that to a full message.</p> <p>Are there any good internet resources are books to just get up to speed on the current state of encryption and decryption?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700y2"> MacroMeez </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700y3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700y1">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 19:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Should you protect your Bitcoin address like your credit card number?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700y4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, I recieved this scam email:</p>

<pre><code>We have reached the biggest milestone in our history &ndash; over a million wallets.

http://cur.lv/700y5[removed] will celebrate with some big prizes.

In October 2013, the lucky user who created the 500,000th wallet was rewarded with 10 BTC.

Read more about this: http://cur.lv/700y6[removed]

We have discovered that you created the wallet with number 1.000.000

[removed] want to reward you with 50 BTC.

To prove that you are the rightful owner of the lucky wallet,

please reply to this email and send us your mnemonic ( the long string of words generated randomly when your account was created)

After verification, your wallet will be credited instantly with the 50 BTC.

Thank you that you have chosen http://cur.lv/700y5[removed]
</code></pre>

<p>I am guessing this is a scam as (a) it was sent to two seperate email addresses I have, (b) the sender's email is in no way affiliated to the websites listed in the email and (c) I don't think anyone is willing to just give away 50 BTC which is close to $42,000 USD. I was wondering if I were to give them my Bitcoin address, what would happen next? Would they be able to use it like a credit card number? Or would they just be asking for more personal information?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>ub3rst4r</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Economy App]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700y7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700y8">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700y7">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 19:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MMM #5 – Role Playing]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700y9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Paul Boyer</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 16:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: NoFiatCoin (XNF) founder speaks to media for first time on gold-backed currency]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ya]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65ygw"> Bitaboom </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700yb">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ya">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 14:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The New Kid on The Block of Digital Currency, NoFiatCoin, Opens Unprecedented Doors]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700yc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65ygw"> Bitaboom </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700yd">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700yc">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 14:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Gateway issue]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ye]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Reading all the info regarding gateway operation I<code>m completely missing one point - withdrawal. As far as I understood ammount of IOU</code>s issued by GW in Ripple system are always equal to the ammount of clients deposits on gateway account (bank). As a relust there is alway a limit of "phisical" cash or fiat money for every particular gateway which is an ammount of total deposits (suppose as a GW I recieve 1000 Euros from my client and issuing IOUs for that very ammont) What I<code>m trying to understand - if a peson within ripple who have been credited by another gateway (lets say 5000 USD), is changing them on euros (~3600 euros) and trying to withdraw them via me as a gateway, establishing a trustline. Howether my limit of "phisical" cash in a bank acc is only 1000 euros and I</code>m unable to proceed his request. Can someone explain it to me?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700yf"> AlexFalko </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700ye">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700ye">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 12:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple Singapore launches Gold &amp; Silver on ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700yg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>RIPPLE SINGAPORE SUMMARY</p> <p>Ripple Singapore website: <a href="http://cur.lv/700yh">http://cur.lv/700yi</a></p> <p>Gateway address: r9Dr5xwkeLegBeXq6ujinjSBLQzQ1zQGjH</p> <p>Currencies: USD SGD XAU (GOLD IN TROY OUNCES) XAG (SILVER IN TROY OUNCES) XPT (PLATINUM IN TROY OUNCES)</p> <p>Reserve ratio: 100%</p> <p>IRBA disclosure page for Ripple Singapore: <a href="http://cur.lv/700yj">http://cur.lv/700yj</a></p> <p>Fee schedule for Ripple Singapore: <a href="http://cur.lv/700yk">http://cur.lv/700yk</a></p> <p>Redemption policy Currencies: any amount via Telegraphic Transfer or local bank transfer methods (GIRO, MEPS) Bullion: - XAU in 10oz bars (equals to 10 XAU) - XAG in 5*100oz bars (equal to 500AG) - XPT in 10oz bars (equal to 10 XPT)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700yl"> Bonface </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700yg">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700yg">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 05:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin like love?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ym]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>4&nbsp;Love is patient,&nbsp;love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud.&nbsp;5&nbsp;It does not dishonor others, it is not self-seeking,&nbsp;it is not easily angered,&nbsp;it keeps no record of wrongs.&nbsp;6&nbsp;Love does not delight in evil&nbsp;but rejoices with the truth.&nbsp;7&nbsp;It always protects, always trusts, always hopes, and always perseveres. 8&nbsp;Love never fails. -1 Cor 13 It has been said that the love of money is the root of all evil.&nbsp; Greed can easily top the list of the deadly sins for its impact on the world, but money, at least some types of money, might also be able to teach us something about love.&nbsp; Consider the generous love that has gone into Bitcoin in its creation, distribution, [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700ym">Is Bitcoin like love?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/700ym"><img width="600" height="600" src="http://cur.lv/700yn" alt="sticker-coeur-rouge-logo-bitcoin"></a><p><b><i><sup>4&nbsp;</sup></i></b><i>Love is patient,</i><i>&nbsp;</i><i>love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud.</i><i>&nbsp;</i><b><i><sup>5&nbsp;</sup></i></b><i>It does not dishonor others, it is not self-seeking,</i><i>&nbsp;</i><i>it is not easily angered,</i><i>&nbsp;</i><i>it keeps no record of wrongs.</i><i>&nbsp;</i><b><i><sup>6&nbsp;</sup></i></b><i>Love does not delight in evil</i><i>&nbsp;</i><i>but rejoices with the truth.</i><i>&nbsp;</i><b><i><sup>7&nbsp;</sup></i></b><i>It always protects, always trusts, always hopes, and always perseveres. </i><b><i><sup>8&nbsp;</sup></i></b><i>Love never fails.</i><i></i></p>
<p>-1 Cor 13</p>
<p>It has been said that the love of money is the root of all evil.&nbsp; Greed can easily top the list of the deadly sins for its impact on the world, but money, at least some types of money, might also be able to teach us something about love.&nbsp; Consider the generous love that has gone into Bitcoin in its creation, distribution, and implementation.&nbsp; Consider also the protocol&rsquo;s reliance on the greed of people to defeat greed itself.&nbsp; The motivation of greed is met with curiosity and even benevolence within the mining community.&nbsp; The protocol itself uses the natural greed to engender sufficient mining growth along a continuum and weans us from this greed through the progressive halving of the block rewards predictably every few years.&nbsp; Let&rsquo;s see how good of a match they make on each of those?</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin is patient.</b></p>
<p>Although it sometimes seems like there is this rush of change in Bitcoin Land, and we just can&rsquo;t get things done fast enough, this is our impatience, not any impatience of Bitcoin.&nbsp; Bitcoin is patient; it will still be here even if any of our projects fail.&nbsp; The protocol was crafted and designed and released and will await our capacity to make sense of it.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin is kind.</b></p>
<p>The boundless benevolence of Bitcoin is characterized by the notion of &ldquo;random acts of kindness&rdquo;.&nbsp; There is nowhere this is made more manifest as in the Bitcoin protocol.&nbsp; The random distribution of block rewards to those that are engaging in Bitcoin is deeply kind.&nbsp; This extends out into the Bitcoin community.&nbsp; Bitcoin in its early days was and is a sort of gift economy.&nbsp; It enabled the &ldquo;random act of kindness&rdquo; in a wonderful new way.&nbsp; A great proportion of the early transactions were gifts, and it with Bitcoin that a simple anonymous donation can be very easily made, an anonymous gift is a profound kindness as there is no possibility for any return favor, or even acknowledgement.&nbsp; A simple gift transaction to someone you never met just because you like some code they wrote or something they are doing is so very easily enabled by this wonderful innovation that it has spread love and joy through its kindness worldwide.&nbsp; This kindness is built into the basic elements of the protocol.&nbsp; Every transaction has the option of including within it a gift to those that calculate the hashes to secure the block chain, the miners.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin does not envy.</b></p>
<p>The excellent are not prone to envy. Bitcoin is content with what it is.&nbsp; It does not covet the attentions of anyone from individuals to central banking.&nbsp; It is self-sufficient in that it does not beg for someone to come along and attend to it.</p>
<p>Bitcoin does not seek what it does not have.&nbsp; Bitcoin does not look to become Legal Tender, and does not want to force you by rule of law to accept it, or even to abandon any other means of transaction.&nbsp; Bitcoin is assuredly content to be what it is.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin does not boast</b></p>
<p>Much of what is said about Bitcoin sounds boastful.&nbsp; &ldquo;Best investment of the year&rdquo;, &ldquo;greatest innovation in financial instruments&rdquo;, &ldquo;Largest challenge to central banking in a century&rdquo;. &nbsp;We would do well to make less grand claims as our experiment grows up and meets the world.&nbsp; These however are not Bitcoin&rsquo;s own boasts.&nbsp; Bitcoin is in beta, it is what it is.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin is not proud.</b></p>
<p>It stands naked with its code exposed.&nbsp; One of the foundational principles of Bitcoin is that it is open source.&nbsp; It has always been open source.&nbsp; The Bitcoin code is exposed and laid bare for any criticism and this is its strength.&nbsp; These criticisms are welcomed and when they are on point they are cherished not answered with pride.&nbsp; Though Bitcoin Land is inhabited by folks who are smarter and more attractive than average, its greatest gift is given anonymously.&nbsp; The protocol itself.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin does not dishonor others</b></p>
<p>Bitcoin is honorable; it is at its essence, mathematics.&nbsp; What can be more honorable than math?&nbsp; Its calculations are known and open and exposed.&nbsp; There is no encryption in Bitcoin.&nbsp; The transactions are in the public, they are shared and open and above all honorable. As the transactions are confirmed by the proof of work securing each block they become increasingly honorable such that everyone will honor transactions even the block reward after 100 blocks have been stacked on top.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin is not self-seeking</b></p>
<p>Bitcoin does not seek its own.&nbsp; Once a public address is used, it would be proper to not reuse the address.&nbsp; The protocol is not built to create great stores of wealth on any address.&nbsp; The more bitcoins are transacted to an address the more exposed that address becomes and therefore the least safe.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin is not easily angered</b></p>
<p>It is difficult to imagine the emotion of anger applying to Bitcoin.&nbsp; It is a gentle protocol, even the competitive activity of the mining of fresh Bitcoin by creating new blocks in the block chain creates cooperation and pooling in the same way that friends can join a lottery pool and share the rewards of winning.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin keeps no record of wrongs</b></p>
<p>Bitcoin keeps every record, and keeps it in the open.&nbsp; The wrongs of Bitcoin would be those blocks that are orphaned and not propagated.&nbsp; Those blocks are lost to posterity.&nbsp; Unless they have blocks stacked upon them in order and with properly calculated hashes they are not kept in the block chain record.&nbsp; The Bitcoin block chain keeps no record of these lost chains gone wrong.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin does not delight in evil.</b></p>
<p>Bitcoin relies on the sanctity of mathematics.&nbsp; There are many examples of evil.&nbsp; The evil that sought out the loving embrace of Bitcoin in attempts to hide ultimately become exposed and there is no delight in the evil.&nbsp; The greatest evils are those for which Bitcoin was designed to protect us all:&nbsp; The insidious theft of the product of our labors of the world through the non-consensual devaluation of our wealth by national money issuers.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin rejoices with the truth.</b></p>
<p>When the mathematical truth of the proof of work calculation is reached, when a sufficiently difficult hash is randomly accomplished upon a block to proclaim its truth the world it is met with a joyful reward.&nbsp; This reward is met with rejoicing and swiftly followed by more and more blocks and more and more rewards.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin protects</b></p>
<p>The security of each and every key that protects the wealth of the smallest measure of Bitcoin, a satoshi, is protected by just the same cryptographic security as the largest.&nbsp;&nbsp; Even the poorest among us receives this same benefit of mathematics.&nbsp; All of us are protected without monetary discrimination from the alpaca sock merchant to the exchange traded fund.&nbsp; There are no classes of people or special privileges.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin trusts</b></p>
<p>Bitcoin is designed to not require trusting anyone other than the folks involved in the transaction.&nbsp; This is new.&nbsp; Bitcoin is a novel solution to a problem that has perplexed some of the smartest minds of a generation and handily solves the <a href="http://cur.lv/700yo">Byzantine General&rsquo;s Problem</a>. You do not have to trust that my bank will honor a check, or that your bank will cash it.&nbsp; You do not have to trust that I am the true owner of a credit card, the transaction provides all the trust that you will need.&nbsp; When the Bitcoin transaction is recognized in the block chain, the block chain can trust you to do as you will with them when you present to it a transaction for them signed by your private key.&nbsp; Holding the key is all the trust that is required.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin hopes </b></p>
<p>The Bitcoin protocol was designed with hoped for liberation from artificial and arbitrary constraints.&nbsp; We no longer have to wait for banks and payment institutions to generate new monetary innovations.&nbsp; We hope for freedom from the onerous consumer protection structures and fee structures.&nbsp; We hope to be liberated from an unpredictable inflation arbitrarily decided behind closed doors pulling the value out of our savings.&nbsp; We instead empower ourselves with the ability to program our money to behave according to clear and open rules which only change when all those who are impacted are in agreement.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin preserves</b></p>
<p>The ability of Bitcoin to preserve in permanent open record is unsurpassed by any other endeavor attempted by humans.&nbsp; The propagation of the block chain into every full client insures the persistent and continuous record of preserving the transactional history of every exchange since its inception.&nbsp; It has created an open book preserved for posterity of what we each do with each other.</p>
<p><b>Bitcoin never fails.</b></p>
<p>This remains to be seen, but so far so good.&nbsp; Love wins.&nbsp; Happy Valentine&rsquo;s Day.<img alt="" src="http://cur.lv/700yp" width="500" height="441"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700ym">Is Bitcoin like love?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Joseph VaughnPerling</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 00:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Regulatory Update- 01/29/14]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700yq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Regulatory developments over the past two weeks are indicative of a widening gap in treatment of Bitcoin among developed nations.&nbsp; The various American regulatory bodies seem to be receptive to Bitcoin, if not overtly supportive.&nbsp; However, many other countries, especially European Union member states and Asian countries, have taken the opposite tack. US authorities seem primarily concerned with detection and prevention of money laundering, while European authorities are staking out positions likely to increase tax revenue as Bitcoin acceptance grows. Developing countries in general and Asian countries specifically, seem to be gravitating toward positions that defend and strengthen state control of the money supply. Bitcoin is not legal tender in Canada.&nbsp; According to the Canadian Treasury, as outlined by an [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700yq">Bitcoin Regulatory Update- 01/29/14</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/700yq"><img width="400" height="266" src="http://cur.lv/6kv4j" alt="ravenbit-physical-bitcoin-closeup-1015a-400"></a><p>Regulatory developments over the past two weeks are indicative of a widening gap in treatment of Bitcoin among developed nations.&nbsp; The various American regulatory bodies seem to be receptive to Bitcoin, if not overtly supportive.&nbsp; However, many other countries, especially European Union member states and Asian countries, have taken the opposite tack. US authorities seem primarily concerned with detection and prevention of money laundering, while European authorities are staking out positions likely to increase tax revenue as Bitcoin acceptance grows. Developing countries in general and Asian countries specifically, seem to be gravitating toward positions that defend and strengthen state control of the money supply.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is not legal tender in Canada.&nbsp; According to the Canadian Treasury, as outlined by an unnamed &ldquo;official&rdquo; in an emailed message, only Canadian bank notes are considered legal tender in Canada. This echoes the sentiments of a number of other countries recently, though it is not clear what this means (if anything) for consumers who wish to spend their Bitcoins with Canadian vendors at this time.&nbsp; Canadian Bitcoiners remain free to enter into contracts for payment in any manner that is mutually agreeable to both buyer and seller, but transactions denominated in a medium that is not &ldquo;legal tender&rdquo; may be subject to additional taxes beyond what would normally apply to the same transaction when paid in Canadian Dollars.&nbsp; According to <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4t">Spendbitcoins</a>, more than one thousand Canadian vendors currently accept Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Finland&rsquo;s central bank classifies Bitcoin as a &ldquo;commodity,&rdquo; according to Bloomberg News Service. &nbsp;Paevi Heikkinen, the head of oversight at the Bank of Finland said that, since Bitcoin doesn&rsquo;t have a central issuer responsible for its operation, it does not meet the definition of currency as specified by Finnish law. He went on to state &ldquo;at this stage it&rsquo;s more comparable to a commodity.&rdquo; As a commodity, Bitcoin will likely be subject to capital gains taxes or their Finnish equivalent. US tax law does not recognize a separate class of asset for commodities. However, the Commodities Futures Trading Commission has hinted on at least one occasion that it might attempt to regulate Bitcoin trading in the future based on such a definition.</p>
<p>Sweden&rsquo;s tax agency announced last week that Bitcoin will be treated as an &ldquo;other asset&rdquo;, putting it in the same category as art and antiques and subjecting Bitcoin denominated transactions to capital gains taxes. Sweden is also considering whether to treat miners as businesses, which would allow them to deduct ordinary expenses from mining revenues. This position is the same as that taken by Norway in an announcement last December.&nbsp; The US Internal Revenue Code, by contrast, already provides a framework for writing off ordinary business expenses related to Bitcoin, to include mining expenses.</p>
<p>On Monday, Russia&rsquo;s central bank published a statement on its website warning that Bitcoin users that they could be unintentionally breaking the law.&nbsp; Without providing additional examples, the statement pointed out that issuing &ldquo;alternative currencies&rdquo; is against Russian law. On a semi-related note, Zero Hedge is reporting that Russian bank &ldquo;MyBank&rdquo; announced Tuesday that it is suspending all cash withdrawals until at least next week in response to fears of a spreading &ldquo;global bank run.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Following the success of its private &ldquo;summit&rdquo; held in San Francisco last week, Wells Fargo announced that it will hold a public event to discuss Bitcoin.&nbsp; According to Coindesk.com, five speakers will each make a fifteen minute presentation.&nbsp; The speakers include Bitcoin industry insiders, a Department of Justice official and an attorney from a firm that specializes in money laundering cases.&nbsp; Wells Fargo also announced that it will lead an industry based effort to develop anti-money laundering rules for Bitcoin startups.&nbsp; Anecdotal reports suggest that the event was not quite public, as the sixty places reserved for the &ldquo;public&rdquo; were filled by Wells Fargo&rsquo;s clients and other industry stakeholders.</p>
<p>&ldquo;The US government needs more time to assess the bitcoin &lsquo;phenomenon&rsquo; to ensure the virtual currency isn&rsquo;t used for unlawful purposes,&rdquo; Treasury Secretary Jacob J. Lew told CNBC during an interview at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.&nbsp; Though, without mentioning &ldquo;who&rdquo; he though needed to grant the US government more time.&nbsp; He went on to state that &ldquo;we have to make sure it does not become an avenue to funding illegal activities that have malignant purposes like terrorist activities.&rdquo; Lew seems to be the irony of his comments in that they apply as well to the venerable US greenback as to Bitcoin or any other anonymous or semi-anonymous payment technology. Meanwhile, in the absence of restrictive regulations, Bitcoin supporters, including a growing number of tech startups, are charging ahead.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700yq">Bitcoin Regulatory Update- 01/29/14</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Jason M. Tyra</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 17:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Why I Quit My Day Job]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700yr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[By Dan Roseman | Coinality.com January 29, 2014 Towards the end of the day before this past New Year&rsquo;s holiday at work, my supervisors pulled me aside for &ldquo;a little chat.&rdquo; I knew what this was about. It was a long time coming. We sat down in a conference room, where I was given a [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Dan Roseman</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[New West Technologies Introduces Bitcoin Integration for Microsoft Dynamics RMS]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700ys]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA &mdash; January 28, 2014 &mdash; New West Technologies, Inc. has released the first Bitcoin integration for Microsoft Dynamics Retail Management Systems (RMS). In partnership with BitPay, the world leader in business solutions for virtual currencies, New West will deliver a streamlined approach to allow businesses to process Bitcoin payments. Bitcoin provides a progressive extension to RMS, allowing Microsoft RMS to receive and process Bitcoin payments for goods and services. Bitcoin eliminates opportunity for fraud and identity theft by using cryptography to control the creation and transfer of money. For business, the Bitcoin network does not allow payment cancellations, making chargebacks impossible. New West&rsquo;s introduction of RMS Bitcoin extends the powerful POS software package and increases automation of POS processes. [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700ys">New West Technologies Introduces Bitcoin Integration for Microsoft Dynamics RMS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/700ys"><img width="888" height="346" src="http://cur.lv/700yt" alt="NWTCircleWaveLOGO"></a><p dir="ltr"><strong>ATLANTA &mdash; January 28, 2014</strong> &mdash; <a href="http://cur.lv/700yu">New West Technologies, Inc.</a> has released the first Bitcoin integration for Microsoft Dynamics Retail Management Systems (RMS). In partnership with <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">BitPay</a>, the world leader in business solutions for virtual currencies, New West will deliver a streamlined approach to allow businesses to process Bitcoin payments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin provides a progressive extension to RMS, allowing Microsoft RMS to receive and process Bitcoin payments for goods and services. Bitcoin eliminates opportunity for fraud and identity theft by using cryptography to control the creation and transfer of money. For business, the Bitcoin network does not allow payment cancellations, making chargebacks impossible. New West&rsquo;s introduction of RMS Bitcoin extends the powerful POS software package and increases automation of POS processes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;New West makes accepting Bitcoin payments easier than ever and through our implementation of RMS Bitcoin, merchants will see tremendous value in accepting this additional payment method,&rdquo; states Dale Fowleri, New West Technologies Marketing Director. &ldquo;Our integration is the most powerful, reliable, and scalable tools for businesses to accept Bitcoin.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users send payments by broadcasting digitally signed messages to the network; however the process of completing the transaction does not change. The merchant tenders the Bitcoin, the consumer scans the QR code and approves the payment. Upon approval, the exchange rate is established through BitPay, the transaction is made, and receipt is printed. All action is accomplished through RMS and the internet, making the process effortless for consumers and retailers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Microsoft Dynamics Retail Management System (RMS) offers small and midsize retailers a complete point of sale (POS) solution that is fast and easy, adaptable to meet unique system requirements. With RMS Bitcoin, retailers can expand their customers&rsquo; payment options and establish a foothold using the most secure payment network.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>About New West</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Founded in 1992 in Portland, Oregon, New West Technologies is a leading integrator of retail POS and customized software solutions. As a full&shy;-service technology provider with extensive experience in small business computer networking and retail software development and installation, we deliver easy &shy;to &shy;use, practical solutions that dramatically improve your profitability and workflow management. <a href="http://cur.lv/700yu">www.newestech.com</a></p>
<p><strong>About BitPay</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">BitPay is a Payment Service Provider (PSP) specializing in eCommerce and B2B solutions for virtual currencies. Visit <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">http://cur.lv/700yv</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700ys">New West Technologies Introduces Bitcoin Integration for Microsoft Dynamics RMS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam Hofman</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Jupiter Colony]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgc7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Jupiter Broadcasting Community Resources]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage without X]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700yw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hello, is it possible to use Bitmessage using a textual interface? In Arch pybitmessage has qt4 package as dependencie, but I know that qt doesn't offers only GUIs</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yoa"> Inaltoasinistra </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700yx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700yw">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 14:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[I created a bitmessage protocol dissector for Wireshark]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700yy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>During my research of the Bitmessage protocol, I decided that it would be useful to be able to dissect the network packages to and from the Bitmessage client in Wireshark.</p> <p>Apparently, no one had created a Wireshark dissector for Bitmessage before, so I did just that in Lua and am sharing the result publicly on GitHub.</p> <p>It can currently recognize the the version, verack, addr, inv, and getdata message types as well as the getpubkey, pubkey, msg, and broadcast object types.</p> <p>Of course, it is only possible to view the unencrypted payload with this dissector.</p> <p>You can find it here: <a href="http://cur.lv/700yz">http://cur.lv/700yz</a></p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700z0">Screenshot</a></p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/700z1">Blog post</a> (contains pretty much the same text as this post): </p> <p>EDIT: I changed a word</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700z2"> jesperbb </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700z3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700yy">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Updated Usage Credits so they work in the new GUI.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700z4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Updated Usage Credits so they work in the new GUI.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Updated Usage Credits so they work in the new GUI.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 11:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange CEO Arrested]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700xw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In the latest development connected to the Silk Road case, U.S. officials have arrested the CEO of Bitcoin exchange, BitInstant. Charlie Shrem, co-founder and chief executive of BitInstant, was taken into custody in New York on Sunday and charged with money laundering, operating an unlicensed money transmitting business, and failing to report suspicious activity. Robert [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700xw">Bitcoin Exchange CEO Arrested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the latest development connected to the <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv49">Silk Road</a> case, U.S. officials have arrested the CEO of Bitcoin exchange, BitInstant.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/700z5"><img alt="BitInstant CEO arrested for money laundering" src="http://cur.lv/700z5" width="502" height="340"></a><p>BitInstant CEO Charlie Shrem arrested for money laundering. Image: Dustin Drakoski/vocativ</p></div>
<p>Charlie Shrem, co-founder and chief executive of BitInstant, was taken into custody in New York on Sunday and charged with money laundering, operating an unlicensed money transmitting business, and failing to report suspicious activity.</p>
<p>Robert Faiella, a 52-year-old man, was arrested in Cape Coral, Fla. on Monday in connection to the case and is accused of running an underground Bitcoin exchange on the Silk Road website under the name BTCKing.</p>
<p>According to the document filed by the <a href="http://cur.lv/700z6">Manhattan U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office</a>, Shrem, who personally bought drugs on Silk Road, sold Faiella bitcoins knowing that they would be used on the underground drug-trafficking website.&nbsp; The criminal complaint also states that Shrem gave Faiella discounts on high-volume transactions, personally processed his orders, and deliberately facilitated Faiella in avoiding anti-money laundering restrictions, even though it was his part of his role as the company&rsquo;s Compliance Officer to enforce the laws and report suspected illicit activity.</p>
<p>Over a period of ten months, the pair exchanged over $1 million in bitcoins for Silk Road users before Faiella ended the partnership in late 2012, the IRS claims.</p>
<p>Last year, BitInstant received a $1.5 million investment from Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss&rsquo; venture capitalist firm, Winklevoss Capital.</p>
<p>The Winklevoss twins issued a <a href="http://cur.lv/700z7">statement</a> earlier this week making it clear that when they invested in BitInstant, they company&rsquo;s management made a commitment to &ldquo;abide by all applicable laws &ndash; including money laundering laws &ndash; and we expected nothing less.&rdquo;&nbsp; Nevertheless, they remain &ldquo;deeply concerned&rdquo; with the BitInstant CEO&rsquo;s arrest and &ldquo;support any and all governmental efforts to ensure that money laundering requirements are enforced.&rdquo;</p>
<p>BitInstant aren&rsquo;t the only ones affected by the allegations.&nbsp; Shrem, 24, was a well-known advocate for the crypto-currency and held a vice chairman position on the board of Bitcoin Foundation, a non-profit organization dedicated to raising awareness and promoting education on digital currency.</p>
<p>Though careful to acknowledge that Shrem has yet to be proven guilty, executive director Jon Matoinis said the pending trial &ldquo;would detract from advancing [the] core mission&rdquo; of the foundation.&nbsp; Shrem&rsquo;s <a href="http://cur.lv/700z8">resignation</a> from the board of Bitcoin Foundation was mutually decided and has been accepted, effective immediately.</p>
<p>If convicted, Shrem and Faiella face up to 20 years in prison for conspiring to commit money laundering.&nbsp; Charges of operating an unlicensed money transmitting business could carry an additional five-year sentence for each man.</p>
<p>Schrem could earn another five years for failing to file a suspicious activity report on Faiella&rsquo;s activity.</p>
<p>The recent arrests have heightened the already palpable <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymp">concerns</a> of governments and lawmakers pushing for regulation of virtual currencies, given Bitcoin&rsquo;s culture of anonymity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700xw">Bitcoin Exchange CEO Arrested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 10:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Question about Bitmessage storage.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700z9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey guys, sorry if this is a noob question, but I am wondering about how much storage space bitmessage allows for each user. I saw that you are allowed to send 500 messages a day and 20 mbs of space. Does this mean that I will have to delete older messages to make space for new ones, or is there more space being added as time goes on? I'm still new to BM (I just created one today).</p> <p>Thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700za"> Bravo777 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700zb">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700z9">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 04:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E79 – A Bitcoin World]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700zc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E79 &ndash; A Bitcoin World In what&rsquo;s got to be the fastest turnaround ever in a Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin episode, we&rsquo;re happy to bring you a twenty minute set of exchanges I found particularly interesting from the first panel of January [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 22:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[NYDFS PUBLIC HEARING REGARDING VIRTUAL CURRENCIES]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700zd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>By Elizabeth T. Ploshay &amp; Ruben Alexander The New York State Department of Financial Services will be conducting hearings on virtual currencies today (January 28th) and tomorrow gathering some of the more visible and influential members of the Bitcoin community as part of their fact-finding initiative that began with an initial inquiry back in late 2013. You can watch the hearings live here. The following information was gathered from a document the NYDFS posted on their site: Panel 1: Barry Silbert &ndash; Founder &amp; CEO of SecondMarket and Founder of the Bitcoin Investment Trust Jeremy Liew &ndash; Partner, Lightspeed Venture Partners Fred Wilson &ndash; Partner, Union Square Ventures Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss &ndash; Principals, Winklevoss Capital Management Panel 2: Charles [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700zd">NYDFS PUBLIC HEARING REGARDING VIRTUAL CURRENCIES</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/700zd"><img width="950" height="350" src="http://cur.lv/700ze" alt="nyfds_bitcoin"></a><p dir="ltr"><em><span>By <a href="http://cur.lv/700zf">Elizabeth T. Ploshay</a> &amp; Ruben Alexander</span></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>The New York State Department of Financial Services will be conducting hearings on virtual currencies today (January 28th) and tomorrow gathering some of the more visible and influential members of the Bitcoin community as part of their fact-finding initiative that began with an <a href="http://cur.lv/700zg">initial inquiry</a> back in late 2013. You can watch the hearings live </span><a href="http://cur.lv/700zh">here.</a></p>
<p><span>The following information was gathered from a document the NYDFS </span><a href="http://cur.lv/700zi">posted</a><span> on their site:</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Panel 1:</p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr">Barry Silbert &ndash; Founder &amp; CEO of <a href="http://cur.lv/700zj">SecondMarket</a> and Founder of the Bitcoin Investment Trust</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Jeremy Liew &ndash; Partner, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zk">Lightspeed Venture Partners</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Fred Wilson &ndash; Partner, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zl">Union Square Ventures</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss &ndash; Principals, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zm">Winklevoss Capital Management</a></p>
</li>
</ul><p><span>Panel 2:</span></p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr">Charles Lee &ndash; Creator of <a href="http://cur.lv/700zn">Litecoin</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Judie Rinearson &ndash; Partner, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zo">Bryan Cave</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Carol Van Cleef &ndash; Partner, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zp">Patton Boggs</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">TBD Additional Witnesses</p>
</li>
</ul><p><span>Schedule:</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">Panel 1 (10:00am &ndash; 11:00am) &ndash; Law Enforcement and Virtual Currencies</p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr">Cyrus R. Vance, Jr &ndash; District Attorney of New York County</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Richard B. Zabel &ndash; Deputy U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York</p>
</li>
</ul><p><span>Panel 2 (11:30am &ndash; 1:30pm) &ndash; Virtual Currency Commerce and Consumer Protections</span></p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr">Fred Ehrsam &ndash; Co-Founder, <a href="http://cur.lv/68b9s">Coinbase</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Jeremy Allaire &ndash; Founder &amp; CEO, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zq">Circle Internet Financial</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">TBD Representative of <a href="http://cur.lv/700zr">Overstock.com</a></p>
</li>
</ul><p dir="ltr"><span>Panel 3 (2:30pm &ndash; 4:00pm) &ndash; The Academic View on Virtual Currencies</span></p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr">Ed W. Felten &ndash; Professor of Computer Science and Public Affairs, and Director of the &nbsp;<a href="http://cur.lv/700zs">Center for Information Technology Policy, Princeton University</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Susan Athey &ndash; Professor of Economics, <a href="http://cur.lv/700zt">Stanford University</a></p>
</li>
</ul><p><span>The end result will most likely inform a BitLicense to address the unique nature of the digital transactions associated with business who allow their customers to exchange Bitcoin for USD.</span></p>
<p><span>Those on the panel will take part in a discussion to gauge the impact of a potential BitLicense on the various Bitcoin business represented in the hearing.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>update: We&rsquo;ve been sent the full transcript of the testimony of Jeremy Allaire, CEO of Circle Internet Financial.</em><br><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<hr><div>
<p align="center"><b>New York State Department of Financial Services</b></p>
</div>
<p align="center"><b>Hearing on Virtual Currency</b></p>
<p align="center"><b>Testimony of</b></p>
<p align="center"><b>Jeremy Allaire, Chairman and CEO,</b></p>
<p align="center"><b>Circle Internet Financial, Inc.</b></p>
<p><b>&nbsp;</b></p>
<p align="center"><b>January 29, 2014</b></p>
<p>Superintendent Lawksy, thank you for the opportunity to participate in today&rsquo;s hearing.&nbsp; My name is Jeremy Allaire, and I am the Founder and CEO of Circle Internet Financial, a financial services company aimed at enabling consumers and businesses to use Bitcoin and digital currency for payments and money transfers. &nbsp;I have been building Internet software platforms and online services for twenty years, having founded and helped to lead multiple global public companies.</p>
<p>Payments and money transfers are still operating in the pre-internet era. &nbsp;Digital currency has enormous potential as a payment method for both consumers and merchants.&nbsp; It offers greater ease of use, convenience, and security than existing payment networks, and at a significantly lower cost.&nbsp; Bitcoin, specifically, offers a powerful open platform that is global in scope and enables nearly instant, verifiable transactions at a fraction of the cost of existing electronic payment systems, while increasing security for end-users and businesses accepting payments.&nbsp; As programmable currency, Bitcoin also portends to enable new forms of automated financial contracts and use as a globally verifiable ledger of ownership in nearly any form of asset.</p>
<p>Without a doubt, there are currently many risks associated with digital currency, and many of these have been voiced by government agencies around the world, including:&nbsp; price volatility, lack of consumer protections and safeguards around the potential theft of digital assets, the lack of consistent safeguards against &ldquo;seller fraud&rdquo;, and the potential for criminal use and abuse of a system that by design provides very high levels of financial privacy. We believe that through private industry and community-led innovation, as well as collaboration with law making bodies, all of these risks can be addressed and the innovation value allowed to flourish.</p>
<p><span>We appreciate the leadership role that the New York Department of Financial Services has taken regarding digital currency and the efforts of the Conference of State Banking Supervisors, and other federal and state regulators, to review the benefits and risks associated with digital currency.&nbsp; We are also encouraged by the guidance issued by FinCEN last March geared to ensuring that digital currency transactions are not used for money laundering and providing digital currency firms with much needed regulatory clarity on these issues. With that said, we believe more needs to be done from a regulatory perspective. The current state statutes are outdated and never contemplated technology such as Bitcoin. As a result, state regulators are finding it difficult to accept and process licensing applications for digital currency firms.&nbsp; We believe that there should be more guidance specifically geared toward digital currency firms and that the states should develop a streamlined approach to licensing these firms.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span>The growing global awareness and interest in Bitcoin is a testament to the innovation represented by this technology, and while there are clear risks, we see very strong evidence of industry and regulatory engagement needed to address these risks and allow for the disruptive potential of the technology to take hold and drive mainstream acceptance of digital currency.</span></p>
<p><span>Thank you again for organizing this hearing and for providing me with the chance to discuss the future of digital currency. I look forward to answering your questions and reviewing this matter in more detail.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Please find the responses below to the specific questions raised by the New York State Department of Financial Services in preparation for the hearing.</span></p>
<p><strong><span>1.&nbsp;&nbsp; The feasibility of the Department issuing a &ldquo;BitLicense&rdquo; specific to virtual currency transactions.&nbsp;</span></strong></p>
<p>Digital currency offers unique benefits to consumers and businesses to transmit, store, send and receive digital currency, such as Bitcoin, in a secure environment at a low cost. Due to the financial nature of these transactions, it is clear that firms participating in this market should be subject to regulatory oversight.&nbsp; Digital currency firms, like other financial services companies, are charged with protecting and securing consumer&rsquo;s assets and therefore should be subject to appropriate regulations, such as anti-money laundering and consumer protection laws.</p>
<p>We are encouraged by the guidance provided by the Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (&ldquo;FinCEN&rdquo;) at the federal level and believe that there are enough safeguards in place to prevent anti-money laundering under existing laws and regulations. We also believe it is appropriate for digital currency firms to be required to maintain strong Know Your Customer (&ldquo;KYC&rdquo;) policies, monitor transactions for suspicious activity and provide reports to regulatory bodies as necessary and as is required by FinCEN.</p>
<p>However, there is still too much regulatory uncertainty and inconsistency in relation to the oversight of digital currency firms from a state regulatory perspective.&nbsp; It is evident that the current statutory framework among the states is outdated and does not contemplate digital currency technology.&nbsp; We believe that it would be beneficial to have a special license (such as a BitLicense) that is geared to mitigating the risks specifically associated with digital currency.&nbsp; We also believe that the licensing process should be streamlined among the fifty states to allow legitimate businesses to enter the market. As it currently stands, the lack of regulatory clarity, and the inconsistent application of laws among the states, has created a barrier to entry for digital currency firms.</p>
<p><strong><span>2.&nbsp; What specific types of virtual currency transactions and activities should require regulation?</span></strong></p>
<p>We believe that recent FinCEN guidance appropriately regulates those firms facilitating digital currency transactions and not individual users or holders of digital currency. Firms that should be regulated include exchanges that convert fiat currency to digital currency and companies, such as Circle, that help consumers and businesses store, send and receive digital currency.&nbsp; The FinCEN regulations exclude miners of digital currency which play a critical role in the validation of digital currency transactions.</p>
<p><strong><span>3. Should entities that are regulated be required to follow specific anti-money laundering regulations?&nbsp;</span></strong></p>
<p>Digital currency firms should be required to follow anti-money laundering regulations and are appropriately designated a money service business for this purpose.&nbsp; As previously stated, we believe that firms can be adequately regulated under the current statutory framework.&nbsp; Recent high profile enforcement actions suggest that law enforcement can, and will, bring actions, against bad actors in this area under existing anti-money laundering laws.&nbsp; It is entirely appropriate for digital currency firms to be required to register with FinCEN as an MSB, establish KYC standards, monitor transactions and report suspicious activity.<b> &nbsp; &nbsp;</b></p>
<p><strong><span>4.&nbsp; Should entities that are regulated be required to follow specifically tailored consumer protection guidelines?</span></strong></p>
<p>Digital currency firms are charged with protecting assets for individuals and businesses.&nbsp; It is important that digital currency firms not only put into place security and risk management protocols to protect consumer&rsquo;s digital currency, but also be transparent and educate consumers about the risks associated with transactions.&nbsp; In this regard, it would be appropriate to have specific consumer protection laws and disclosures to ensure consumers understand all of the transactions and that consumers are protected from fraudulent transactions.&nbsp; Likewise, unlike traditional MSBs where consumer financial assets are stored within Federal Reserve backed commercial banks, digital currency MSBs are custodians of financial assets in the form of private keys, and thus should have higher levels of protection around those assets.&nbsp; We are committed to working proactively with the state agencies and the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau to determine what level of regulation is needed in this area.</p>
<p><strong><span>5. Should entities that are regulated be required to follow specifically tailored examination requirements?</span></strong></p>
<p>It would be appropriate for digital currency firms to have tailored examinations and oversight. Digital currency risks and compliance issues are unique and the technology is evolving and therefore it would make sense to have specific related procedures.&nbsp; From a practical standpoint, this would also most likely create the need for specialized examination teams who understand the risks and the technology.&nbsp; We would recommend that the states combine efforts through the CSBS or other bodies to come up with a standard examination manual similar to the approach taken by the federal financial regulators through the FFIEC to ensure a consistent approach is taken and that the expectations are clear.</p>
<p><strong><span>6. The benefits and drawbacks of using virtual currency from a retail perspective.&nbsp;</span></strong></p>
<p><b></b>Digital currency offers tremendous potential economic benefits from a retail perspective, including making payment transactions more accessible and secure, while doing so at a lower cost More specifically, the benefits of digital currency include the following:</p>
<ul><li>Materially lowering the costs associated with electronic payments, from an average of 2-3% down to close to 0%;</li>
<li>Open up global trade, specifically e-commerce and online services, by facilitating trade and transactions across borders with low overhead;</li>
<li>Radically lower the costs of money transfers, including and especially international remittances, which often carry 7-10% transaction fees;</li>
<li>Reducing fraud associated with current electronic payment methods, where customers must constantly share sensitive bank account information, compared to Bitcoin whose cryptography-based architecture enables payments to happen without providing counter-parties with sensitive financial account information;</li>
<li>Because of Bitcoin&rsquo;s low-cost transaction model, it can support payments for products and services priced on a micro-payment basis, including innovative metered pricing models;</li>
<li>By leverage software and online services as well as smart mobile devices, help to improve the consumer retail experience; and</li>
<li>Long-term, as a core set of technology and protocols, Bitcoin offers significant opportunities in establishing and enforcing contracts, including financial contracts, as well as new methods of trust in commercial exchanges.</li>
</ul><p><b>Digital currency, and Bitcoin specifically, does present significant risks and threats,</b><b></b></p>
<p><b>including the following:</b><b></b></p>
<ul><li>Criminals and terrorists will seek to employ digital currency if it remains unregulated;</li>
<li>Tax evaders will seek to employ digital currency if the government doesn&rsquo;t issue and enforce clearly guidelines and rules on the role of digital currency in income and taxation;</li>
<li>Consumers and businesses could be defrauded of their money if digital currency operators are not compelled to operate their business with the highest levels of security safeguards for the storage of digital currency and associated personal information; and</li>
<li>Consumers and businesses could be exposed to financial loss if Bitcoin market prices fluctuate wildly, and governments and institutional investors are not able to act as market-makers in Bitcoin.</li>
</ul><p><strong>7. Pricing, volatility and security of the virtual currency market from an investor perspective.</strong></p>
<p>Primarily, the price swings reflect the fact that Bitcoin is a nascent market with limited float and trade volume.&nbsp; Similar to small cap stocks on public exchanges, lack of liquidity at scale and lower trade volume will tend to yield higher levels of volatility.&nbsp; In its current incarnation, digital currency has been a news-driven phenomenon, which in the early stages can lead to more significant price swings.</p>
<p>While volatility is a short-term concern, we do not believe it is a long-term issue.&nbsp; As more legal exchanges begin to operate in key financial markets (US, UK, Germany, Japan, etc.), we expect to see trade volumes grow considerably, and exchange products to become more sophisticated in terms of features that would be attractive to institutional investors.&nbsp; This broader institutional participation will drive greater price stability and greater liquidity for consumers and businesses using the currency. In addition, widespread adoption and use of digital currency as a payment method should create additional stability in the marketplace.<b></b></p>
<p><strong><span>8. The future expectations and anticipated developments of the virtual currency market from an investor and retail perspective.&nbsp;</span></strong></p>
<p>We believe that global digital currency will become a critical component to how world trade and e-commerce takes place over the next twenty years.&nbsp; The technology offers tremendous opportunities to build a new infrastructure as well as consumer and business-focused financial services that support this global adoption.</p>
<p>There are several short and long-term challenges for digital currency from a business, regulatory and technological perspective. In terms of regulation, we believe it is important that U.S. federal and state regulators take a leadership role and provide regulatory guidance needed for legitimate businesses to prevent these companies from going overseas. One area that needs to be addressed in the short term relates to the tax treatment of digital currency.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Without certainty in this area, merchants and consumers that utilize digital currency will be discouraged from doing so.&nbsp; From a technology perspective, the protocols around Bitcoin are still in early stages. We expect that future versions and improvements to the open architecture will provide enhancements that will improve the efficiency and use of Bitcoin by the consumer and businesses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/700zd">NYDFS PUBLIC HEARING REGARDING VIRTUAL CURRENCIES</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ruben Alexander</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 18:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Alcatel-Lucent files Patent for Vault to Wallet Transfer System]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700zu]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[The essence of the patent is a system whereby a decentralized currency such as Bitcoin is stored in a secure environment known as a Vault and a smaller unsecured portion of funds are stored in an unsecured Wallet.  <p></p> With cryptocurrency thefts in the news as the price hovers near $1000 each, Brian Cohen catches another patent in this LTB exclusive.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Brian Cohen</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Have you heard of Bitcoin Roulette Scam?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700zv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Even if you have been playing bitcoin roulette for a while now, it&rsquo;s still important that you keep one eye open for any possibility of scam. After all, the number of Scam Bitcoin roulette sites is increasing at a faster rate, so you have to make sure that you won&rsquo;t be the next victim of online scam. Have you heard of any bitcoin roulette scam lately?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>andrewdolan</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 05:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage + skypemorph , possible?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700zw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I think to reduce the use of Tor Bandwidth, it could be a nice idea. What do u think? </p> <p>more about skypemorph: <a href="http://cur.lv/700zx">http://cur.lv/700zx</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700zy">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700zw">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 22:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The China Syndrome]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700zz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Hayden Gill</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 19:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Identities with separate adressbooks]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/70100]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>At the moment I have different identities but I have just one adressbook. If you have a lot of adresses it would be nice to have an adressbook for each identity. Thus you could have something like the circles in Google+.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyw"> berndfleisig </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/70101">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/70100">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 19:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[This is why the world needs bitmessage - FBI has the TorMail database]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/70102]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow28"> laxisusous </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/70103">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/70102">[9 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 19:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Altruistic Economics: A Framework for Interactions between Sympathetic Peers [PDF]]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/70104]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/70105">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/70104">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 18:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitinstant CEO charged by US government for facilitating SilkRoad purchases with bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/70106]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/70107">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/70106">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple Success Stories]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/70108]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/70109">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/70108">[6 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 16:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Circular Multilateral Barter / News: Circular Multilateral Barter 1.11]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010a]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7010b">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7010a">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is BitVestor.us legit/a scam?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This is pretty much the same as Altermine.org, which was indeed a scam. A minimum of 0.01 BTC is required to be deposited to get your passive income. This site looks more promising, but stuff always happens. Has anyone tried this site out?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 03:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[steroids signs of physical or emotional]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>what are some physical signs or otherwise that an athlete is using ped's? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>derpderp</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 21:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Artwork illustrating how Bitmessage delivers mail without metadata]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6x9zs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6x9zt"> fineartcoin </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6x9zu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6x9zs">[8 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 21:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Chris Odom on OpenTransactions]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa06]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 18:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What happens if your gateway goes offline?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa0q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I was thinking about this whole gateway process and thought about what would happen if you as an example have usd in your wallet.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0r"> r4ndomguy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0q">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0q">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How secure are current deterministic wallets?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010e]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Can someone explain how secure the deterministic wallet implementations of Electrum and Armory are? As far as I know, Electrum uses a 128-bit seed to generate all the addresses. I don't get this because since even a single bitcoin address consists of 256-bits. why not make this seed something much larger? And electrum uses something called "root key" and "chain code" which I can't find any explanations about. </p>

<p>Any ideas on how secure these implementations are? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Kent748484</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 09:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BETA: New Bitmessage stats page, now with heatmaps and an API]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa0x]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3m"> dokumentamarble </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0y">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0x">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 06:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Suspicious activity with NoFiatCoin (XNF) trade book? Anyone have some answers?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa0z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>This'll be long, but it has to be to explain my suspicions so bear with me.</p> <p>So, last night, I was setting up some bids and asks on the Ripple order book as per usual when I decided to check XNF/USD. To my surprise a sell order for somewhere in the range of 550 XNF going at about $0.14 each popped up right in front of my eyes. Because XNF bids were sitting at around 3 or 4 dollars per at the time I of course almost had a heart attack whilst typing and clicking furiously trying to buy as many as I could. </p> <p>I feel like I couldn't have noticed it any faster or reacted any faster yet the order was completely gone before my order could go through. I felt kinda bummed but also kinda figured it must have been a fluke order and they cancelled it instantly so no big deal. Skip forward about an hour and the price XNF/USD has risen to about 6. And that's a solid 6 with hundreds of XNF support under it coming up from seemingly nowhere in a very short time. Hmmmm.</p> <p>At this point I'm holding on to 10 XNF that I'd bought at roughly 2 USD per only a half day prior. I decided to wait a little longer and see what happens.</p> <p>Nothing much happens until about 8 AM when suddenly I notice MULTIPLE sell orders of anywhere from 10 - 500 XNF going for .0125-.015 USD per. At this point there's an established bid range of about 4 - 5.5 USD (support at 6 per from before collapsed) so one could easily buy and turn around and sell for a huge profit. I tried to grab ANY of these orders for any amount I could to no avail, they were gone instantly. In about an hour from 8-9AM there were maybe 10 of these sell orders for a sum total of around 1000 XNF being sold at ridiculously low amounts.</p> <p>Now the first time that mysterious sell order popped up last night the price of XNF rose about 2 USD per instantly and just stayed there until 8AM. This time, though, was the most HECTIC trading experience I've ever seen. The cross markets were totally screwed. At one point, I was able to sell 1 xnf for about 6.5 usd and then buy XRP with that and use that to buy XNF for a huge profit (averaged about 150% returns and more at some points doing this.) I imagine this is because the XNF/USD market was so volatile, no one was keeping track of XNF/XRP in those first few minutes? Keep in mind that both markets were pretty stagnant from 2AM to 8AM and these big sell orders popped up out of nowhere.</p> <p>Eventually both markets evened out with shallow support at around 8 USD per XNF at 9:30AM after reaching a high of 9.99 USD per XNF (I actually sold 1 for that much.) Activity ceased for about half an hour and I didn't check the market again until 5 PM today. Seems to have been no activity since I last checked except some more ask support around 8 USD per XNF.</p> <p>I guess I'm just asking WTF is going on with XNF? Is it suspicious that someone sold that many XNF that low and now the price has basically doubled? Did I miss something crucial somewhere? Were any of you trading alongside me this morning and have your own take on what happened? There seems to be no logic behind this.</p> <p>TL; DR I noticed suspiciously low price sell orders for large amounts of XNF followed quickly by a massive price surge from 3 USD per XNF to 8 USD per in less than 12 hours. What is happening?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9w"> AlistorMcCoy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0z">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa0z">[9 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 04:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[N00b question - icon still yellow]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa11]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><ul><li>Proxy server / Tor: None</li> <li>Listening on 8444</li> <li>Firewall looks open</li> </ul><p>Any suggestions?</p> <p>Thanks,</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa12"> JXChristopher </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6xa13">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa11">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 21:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Significance of Satoshi Square]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa14]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[In light of Decembers' news out of China regarding the new restrictions which prevent Chinese exchanges from accepting the local Chinese currency (Reminbi), it seems appropriate to take another look at the significance of the Satoshi Square phenomena.  
<p>Today we're pleased to share with you Ashe Whiteners' first interview for LTB, with the Catalyst of Satoshi Square.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Visiting Author</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 16:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[AltcoinWeekly: A weekly curated altcoin newsletter]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa15]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hi fellow Ripplers!</p> <p>Not too long ago, I started curating a weekly altcoin newsletter on the top news stories in the cryptocurrency world to help people stay abreast with the top developments in the altcoin scene. </p> <p>I just released <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa16">Newsletter #8</a> yesterday. Could you kindly take a look at <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa17">altcoinweekly.com</a> and offer some feedback on how to improve the newsletters?</p> <p>Thank you loads!</p> <p>Cheers,</p> <p>Bobby</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa18"> bobbyong </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6xa15">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa15">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 14:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is Ethereum a Ripple killer?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6xa19]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yji"> pa2013 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxc">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6xa19">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 06:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple’s Distributed Exchange and the High Frequency Trading Arms Race]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yjf"> alwillis </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvg">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 02:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin A Bubble?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>As the World Economic Forum (WEF) gathers in Davos, Switzerland this week, Bitcoin appears to be merely a blip on the radar for the international political and financial elite.&nbsp; Even so, comments from leaders in these fields have been less than enthusiastic Perhaps the most attention garnering sentiments have come from Robert Shiller, Nobel laureate [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxwo">Is Bitcoin A Bubble?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwp"><img alt="Bitcoin labeled 'a bubble.'" src="http://cur.lv/6qxwp" width="419" height="214"></a><p>Bitcoin met with harsh critics at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. Image: &nbsp;modified from TheBitMom</p></div>
<p>As the World Economic Forum (WEF) gathers in Davos, Switzerland this week, Bitcoin appears to be merely a blip on the radar for the international political and financial elite.&nbsp; Even so, comments from leaders in these fields have been less than enthusiastic</p>
<p>Perhaps the most attention garnering sentiments have come from Robert Shiller, Nobel laureate and Yale Professor of Economics.&nbsp; An expert in the nature of market excesses, Shiller is <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwq">quoted</a> as saying &ldquo;It is a bubble, there is no question about&hellip; It&rsquo;s just an amazing example of a bubble.&rdquo;</p>
<p>While Shiller himself suggests that Bitcoin is a return to the dark ages of currency due to the lack of clarity surrounding its use and <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">regulation</a>, he acknowledges that he understands how others may find the computer science behind the virtual currency &ldquo;inspirational.&rdquo;&nbsp; Shiller also concedes that the jump in value over the past year is &ldquo;logical&rdquo; because it follows human interest in high votility markets.</p>
<p>Treasure Secretary Jack Lew and JP Morgan Chairman and CEO Jamie Dimon had similar attitudes regarding the digital currency.&nbsp; Both admitted to sharing an &ldquo;incredulity&rdquo; about Bitcoin, with Dimon calling it a &ldquo;terrible store of value.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;The question isn&rsquo;t whether we accept it,&rdquo; Dimon <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwr">told CNBC</a>, &ldquo;[t]he question is do we even&nbsp;participate [with] people who&nbsp;facilitate bitcoin?&rdquo;&nbsp; Once Bitcoin is made to follow the same standards as other payment systems, that will &ldquo;probably be the end of them,&rdquo; he concluded.</p>
<p>Lew added to this his <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxws">concerns</a> about a virtual currency&rsquo;s potential to be misused by criminals or for terrorist activities, saying the anonymity of Bitcoin &ldquo;offers places for people to hide.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Lew has made it clear that the government will look at Bitcoin and similar transactions and will &ldquo;enforce all the rules on illegal money activity.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwt">World Economic Forum</a> is held annually in Davos-Klosters, Switzerland, and wraps up tomorrow with the Global Economic Outlook for 2014, followed by a multimedia performance titled, quite fittingly, &ldquo;A Leap of Faith.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxwo">Is Bitcoin A Bubble?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 21:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E78 – Bitcoin Boots on the Ground]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxy2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E78 &ndash; Bitcoins&rsquo; Boots on the Ground Michael Yeung is the founder of the Simon Fraser Bitcoin Club (http://cur.lv/6qxy3), located in Vancouver, Canada. From ATMs, to events to the growth of user adoption, I spoke with Mike earlier this month about [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Let's Talk Bitcoin!</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can you help test it?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Hello. Please visit our new <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyg" title="Provably fair Bitcoin casino">bitcoin casino</a>. It'll be great if you comment what you like/dislike. Or find some bugs))</p>
<p>Thank you guys.</p>
<p>Link: <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyh" title="Best bitcoin roulette"></a><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyg">http://cur.lv/6qxyi</a></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>lalabum</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Multipath support discussion thread [pre-Ripple Labs design discussion]]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyt">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How can I delete Identities?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>As I can't find the file 'keys.dat' anywhere in the new Bitmessage my question is: Where it is gone?</p> <p>On the whole I think that the identities should be deleted where they are. They could be 'protected' but you should be able to make an identity just for one to talk and to delete it then.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyw"> berndfleisig </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyv">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Scaling Cryptocurrency With Ripple | P2P Connects Us]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyz">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyy">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 06:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Moneyness: What equity markets can learn from bitcoin and ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxz8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz8">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 01:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[[bitmessage.ch] Subscribing to a channel?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovvv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey, is it somehow possible to subscribe to a channel of a certain person with bitmassage adress from bitmessage.ch? </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovvw"> throwawy021392 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovvx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovvv">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Not A Gamble In Vegas]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxza]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The flashy lights and star-studded shows of the Las Vegas strip are about to be joined by the rising celebrity of currency, Bitcoin.&nbsp; As of next week, two of Sin City&rsquo;s casinos, The D Las Vegas Casino Hotel and Golden Gate Hotel &amp; Casino, the city&rsquo;s oldest, will be accepting Bitcoin in five of their [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxza">Bitcoin Not A Gamble In Vegas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The flashy lights and star-studded shows of the Las Vegas strip are about to be joined by the rising celebrity of currency, Bitcoin.&nbsp; As of next week, two of Sin City&rsquo;s casinos, The D Las Vegas Casino Hotel and Golden Gate Hotel &amp; Casino, the city&rsquo;s oldest, will be accepting Bitcoin in five of their locations.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzb"><img alt="Bitcoin in Vegas Casinos" src="http://cur.lv/6qxzb" width="477" height="268"></a><p>Bitcoin to be accepted in two Las Vegas casinos. Image: Getty Images</p></div>
<p>Golden Gate, the first casino in the city to install a telephone and the first to offer shrimp cocktails on its menu, prides itself on being ahead of the curve.&nbsp; Derek Stevens, co-owner of both casinos, acknowledges that consumer interest coupled with pressure from the presence of other forward-thinking businesses in the area have played no small part in the decision.&nbsp; &ldquo;Zappos is only a block away from us,&rdquo; he told Cade Metz of <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzc">Wired</a>. &ldquo;People started asking me: &lsquo;Do you accept bitcoin?&rsquo;&rdquo;</p>
<p>According to Jerry Brito, senior research fellow at the Mercatus Center of George Mason University, the immediacy of processing and absence of transaction fees offered by Bitcoin affords the virtual currency the potential to catch up to other payment forms. In an interview with <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzd">USA Today</a>, Brito likened an increased use of Bitcoin to the arrival of credit cards in the 60s, when people had previously only used cash and checks.&nbsp; He reinforced the public&rsquo;s embrace of new payment options and the willingness of businesses to promote technology by adding, &ldquo;and then Paypal came along.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Though the move to include Bitcoin in casinos is receiving equal amounts of enthusiasm and press, its use will be limited to the gift shops, hotels and bistros.&nbsp; According to all parties involved, Bitcoin will not be allowed on the casino floors for the foreseeable future.&nbsp; A.G. Burnett, chairman of the Nevada Gaming Control Board, was very clear that state regulators are in no hurry to replace the current cash-only system.&nbsp; &ldquo;We would have to have an extremely high level of comfort with virtual currency of this kind in order for that to ever occur,&rdquo; Burnett told <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxze">Bloomberg Press</a>.</p>
<p>Even Stevens agrees that there needs to be more clarity from the <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzc">IRS</a>, the U.S. Treasury, and the Department of Justice before Bitcoin receives an extension, saying &ldquo;once we have more from our government, we might be able to implement bitcoin for casino gaming, but I think we&rsquo;re still a ways away from that.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Until then, consumers will have to be content with cashing in their Bitcoin on souvenirs, suites, and shrimp cocktails.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxza">Bitcoin Not A Gamble In Vegas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MMM #4 – Explosive Poetry]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow03]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Paul Boyer</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 16:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[HAK5 Episode Covers Bitmessage]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow27]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow28"> laxisusous </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow29">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow27">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 23:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to run Bitmessage in Passive operating mode?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow35]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><ol><li><p>How to run Bitmessage in Passive operating mode?</p></li> <li><p>And how much is the possibility in real life/practically, that a Receiver's IP can be revealed to an attacker if passive operating mode is not used?</p></li> </ol><p>Read about Passive operating mode in 7th the paragraph: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow36">http://cur.lv/6ow36</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow37">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow35">[7 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 12:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Taxation Vexation]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3a]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this week, Bitcoinx reviewed some of the decisions shaping Bitcoin regulation around the world.&nbsp; While there has been no movement regarding classification of the crypto-currency on the part of the IRS, their silence means more to Bitcoin users than just frustration. Though there are a growing number of businesses and high-profile websites accepting the [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3a">Bitcoin Taxation Vexation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this week, Bitcoinx reviewed some of the decisions shaping <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">Bitcoin regulation</a> around the world.&nbsp; While there has been no movement regarding classification of the crypto-currency on the part of the IRS, their silence means more to Bitcoin users than just frustration.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3c"><img alt="IRS needs clear tax rules on Bitcoiin" src="http://cur.lv/6ow3c" width="377" height="284"></a><p>IRS needs clear tax rules on Bitcoin. Image via Michael Carney/pondodaily</p></div>
<p>Though there are a growing number of <a href="http://cur.lv/68b4a">businesses</a> and high-profile websites accepting the virtual currency, the lack of direction on the part of the IRS may be affecting Bitcoin (and its users) on two fronts: investment and evasion.</p>
<p>Richard Asquith, Head of Tax for international expansion and investment firm, TMX Group, noted that if the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">new rules</a> go through in the UK, the regulation could be highly beneficial for Bitcoin &ndash; in the UK.&nbsp; &ldquo;If the UK tax re-categorisation goes ahead, it will stabilize the domestic Bitcoin exchange market which had been threatening to move out,&rdquo; he said in an interview with <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3z">Forbes</a>. Asquith went on to add that &ldquo;it would also probably start attracting European and even global trade to migrate to the UK as it will be one of the first countries to have a well thought through tax regime.&rdquo;</p>
<p>While any stabilization in the market is likely to help Bitcoin in the long run, the absence of clear rules may be drawing potential investment away from the uncertainty in domestic markets.</p>
<p>The lack of clarity on the part of the government has others in the U.S. concerned with the issue of tax compliance.</p>
<p>In an annual <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3d">report</a> to Congress, National Taxpayer Advocate, Nina Olsen made it clear that &ldquo;It is the government&rsquo;s responsibility to inform the public about the rules they are required to follow.&rdquo;&nbsp; Olsen, who leads the independent Taxpayer Advocate Service office within the IRS, added that &ldquo;the lack of clear answers to basic questions such as when and how taxpayers should report gains and losses on digital currency transactions probably encourages tax avoidance.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Whether they ultimately decide to treat Bitcoin as a capital asset or a fiat currency for tax purposes, one thing is clear, the IRS needs to make a decision &ndash; and the sooner the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3a">Bitcoin Taxation Vexation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 10:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Heatmap 2014-01-21, Bitmessage user IP addresses]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3l]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3m"> dokumentamarble </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3n">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3l">[18 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Goes Up For Sale On eBay]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3w]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Just as Her Majesty&rsquo;s Revenue and Customs authorities in the UK are updating their policy on Bitcoin, eBay and PayPal are looking to re-evaluate their own approach to virtual currencies. Last week, PayPal President David Marcus tweeted &ldquo;To clarify: we have no policies against using PayPal to sell Bitcoin mining rigs. We don&rsquo;t support any [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3w">Bitcoin Goes Up For Sale On eBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3x"><img alt="eBay adds Virtual Currency category" src="http://cur.lv/6ow3x" width="496" height="310"></a><p>eBay to add Virtual Currency category in Classified Ads format. Photo: AP</p></div>
<p>Just as <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">Her Majesty&rsquo;s Revenue and Customs</a> authorities in the UK are updating their policy on Bitcoin, eBay and PayPal are looking to re-evaluate their own approach to virtual currencies.</p>
<p>Last week, PayPal President David Marcus <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3y">tweeted</a> &ldquo;To clarify: we have no policies against using PayPal to sell Bitcoin mining rigs. We don&rsquo;t support any currency txn whether fiat or BTC&hellip; for a host of regulatory issues. But we treat BTC and any FX txn the same way. We&rsquo;re believers in BTC though.</p>
<p>Days after Marcus&rsquo; comments hit Twitter feeds, eBay UK sent an <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3z">email</a> to one of its merchants outlining a plan to update their policy on virtual currencies, including Bitcoin.&nbsp; While eBay UK insisted that virtual currencies &ldquo;cannot be listed in Auctions or Buy-It-Now formats,&rdquo; they also made it clear that &ldquo;eBay is opening a Virtual Currency category to allow the sale of virtual currency in Classified Ads format.&rdquo;&nbsp; The statement went on to &ldquo;request that you do not list these items until that date,&rdquo; warning that breaching the current policy could put users&rsquo; accounts statuses in jeopardy.&nbsp; The email further advised that in order &ldquo;to avoid any inconvenience in future, we&rsquo;d appreciate it if you go through our help pages or contact us before listing any such items.&rdquo;</p>
<p>eBay UK spokesman Steve Heywood further explained the policy updates, in an email to <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow40">CNET</a>, saying &ldquo;The updated policy clarifies that listings for Bitcoin and other similar virtual currencies must be listed in the Virtual Currency Category in the Classified Ad format. This applies to both the US (effective immediately) and the UK (effective 10 February).&rdquo;</p>
<p>Though Marcus is himself a supporter (and private owner) of bitcoins, and eBay has opened up more options for Bitcoin, PayPal is not yet ready to allow payment with the virtual currency.&nbsp; In an <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow41">interview</a> with Stephen Shankland, Marcus said they (PayPal) will consider it, &ldquo;[when] the regulatory framework is clearer, and the volatility comes down.&rdquo;</p>
<p>It is currently unclear whether eBay&rsquo;s new Bitcoin-friendly policy will be implemented in countries outside the US and the UK.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3w">Bitcoin Goes Up For Sale On eBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Blog Tips | Internet News and Tips for Bloggers and ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv52]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Blog Tips New technology launched today by Royal Holloway University, will help protect people from the cyber attack known as "phishing," believed to have affected 37 ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 05:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b0c Capital Asset or Currency?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3b]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Now that we&rsquo;ve just about finished arguing whether Bitcoin is a legitimate payment form or not, we&rsquo;re faced with a whole new set of questions regarding the crypto-currency.&nbsp; One of the most prevalent, confusing, and contested topics is how Bitcoin can and will be taxed.&nbsp; In short, is Bitcoin a currency or a capital asset? [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">http://cur.lv/68b0c Capital Asset or Currency?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now that we&rsquo;ve just about finished arguing whether Bitcoin is a legitimate payment form or not, we&rsquo;re faced with a whole new set of questions regarding the crypto-currency.&nbsp; One of the most prevalent, confusing, and contested topics is how Bitcoin can and will be taxed.&nbsp; In short, is Bitcoin a currency or a capital asset?</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4k"><img alt="Bitcoin, currency or commodity?" src="http://cur.lv/6ow4k" width="407" height="311"></a><p>Will Bitcoin be taxed as a currency or a capital asset? Image: Shutterstock via venturebeat.com</p></div>
<p>While the Internal Revenue Service remains noticeably silent, other countries have been quicker to the mark, adding to the speculation and frustration of investors in the U.S.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s a rundown of what other countries are doing, and why the classification matters.</p>
<p>Last year, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4l">Germany</a> took a stand and ruled that bitcoins fall into the category of personal money, meaning that &ldquo;purchases are subject to sales tax&rdquo; and users will be required to pay capital gains.</p>
<p>Slovenia says Bitcoin is neither a monetary asset, nor a financial instrument, but that taxation will be reviewed on an individual basis (to determine whether income tax applies).</p>
<p>Singapore, where capital gains are not taxed, recognizes Bitcoin as a product, and will apply the goods and services tax.</p>
<p>In the past week, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4m">Finland</a> decided that Bitcoin must be a commodity, after finding that it did not fit legal definitions of a currency or an electronic payment form.</p>
<p>Her Majesty&rsquo;s Revenue and Customs (HMRC), the tax authorities in the UK, are right now looking to <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3z">change</a> the classification of virtual currencies from a tradable voucher to a private currency.&nbsp; Though it is not yet official, handling Bitcoin as though it is private money means a value added tax would apply to commissions charged on exchanges, while still making it subject to capital gains taxes.</p>
<p>Though speculators seem to think that the IRS will eventually lean toward a capital gains classification, an income tax ruling could have bigger implications.</p>
<p>If treated under <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4n">capital gains</a> rules, the same that are used against stocks or commodities, taxes up to 24% may apply, depending on the tax bracket.&nbsp; If the IRS decides that Bitcoin falls into the category of currency, gains would be taxed like income and the rate could go as high as 43.4%.&nbsp; The government&rsquo;s final decision could mean a difference of more than 20% for taxpayers.</p>
<p>In the absence of any clear direction, Bitcoin users in the U.S. are left without much more course of action than to just watch and wait.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">http://cur.lv/68b0c Capital Asset or Currency?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 19:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[XIB New Digital Currency Will Launch Today On The Ripple Network]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65ykf"> Aburgboy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2d">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2c">[6 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #20 from FellowTraveler/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #20 from FellowTraveler/master

Various Android fixes</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #20 from FellowTraveler/master

Various Android fixes</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 06:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MIRI (formerly the Singularity Institute) seems to accept Ripple as a donation method now]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2r">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2q">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Edge Conf 2: Payments]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2u">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2t">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 04:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to attach a File with Bitmessage client?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv32]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I know there is a base64 encode and decode method, but I am not finding any downloadable software client to encode and decode a file. Can you name any file encoder and decoder software to download?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv34">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv32">[36 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 21:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What are difference between the protocols used by "Bitmessage" and "Retroshare"?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv35]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><ol><li><p>What are the basic differences between the protocols used by "Bitmessage" and "Retroshare"?</p></li> <li><p>Can Bitmessage offer the features as like RetroShare does?</p></li> </ol></div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv36">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv35">[9 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 20:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[I want to send UDS to my Bitstamp account via the Ripple network.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv38]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>How do I go about doing that? Is that even possible?</p> <p>Edit: I mean USD</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv39"> ramblington </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv38">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv38">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 16:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Another Android fix (for the PID file.)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3b]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Another Android fix (for the PID file.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Another Android fix (for the PID file.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 10:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fixed Android problems from OTPath and OTSettings.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed Android problems from OTPath and OTSettings.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed Android problems from OTPath and OTSettings.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 10:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Home folder (android), StringToULong, new Swig.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Home folder (android), StringToULong, new Swig.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Home folder (android), StringToULong, new Swig.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 06:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple trade book down?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3e]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Anyone else having problems seeing orders on the in-client orderbook? Can't see numbers for any pair, just shows N/A. Figured it might just be an update or something but it's been going on since last night..</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9w"> AlistorMcCoy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3e">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3e">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 05:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[what is cloud mining ?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining bitcoin with cloud computing
2
2
Share on twitter Share on facebook Share on google Share on email More Sharing Services 1</p>
<p>I was investigating about this topic, and if it's profitable..</p>
<p>links about it:</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3i">http://cur.lv/6kv3i</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3j">http://cur.lv/6kv3j</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3k">http://cur.lv/6kv3k</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3l">http://cur.lv/6kv3l</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3m">http://cur.lv/6kv3m</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3n">http://cur.lv/6kv3n</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3o">http://cur.lv/6kv3o</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3p">http://cur.lv/6kv3p</a></p>
<p>The conclusion is that Bitcoin Mining on Cloud isn't profitable, but that for 1 or 2 years ago, but with the new level of worth.. still not profitable? If not, how much have to worth a bitcoin to be profitable this method?</p>
<p>Considering that a higher value implies greater difficulty</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Saqib Khan</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 20:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can I subscribe to MLs/chans through the B2M Gateway ?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv40]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv41"> ICanHearYouTick </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv42">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv40">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 16:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ciao]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv43]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Buonmgiorno, come stai?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv44"> travisjox </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv45">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv43">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 08:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there a site where you can buy Bitcoins using Amazon Giftcard?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv48]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>There are certain problems buying Bitcoins using credit cards because the operations are reversible.</p>
<p>Deliver giftcard is reversible or works like cash?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 18:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Pirate’s Bitcoin Booty To Go On Sale]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv49]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Nearly 30,000 bitcoins seized in October of last year have been signed off on a forfeiture order, federal prosecutors from the Manhattan U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s office announced on Thursday. Currently valued around $25 million, the bitcoins were seized from Ross Ulbricht, who allegedly founded and operated hidden website Silk Road under the pseudonym Dread Pirate Roberts. [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6kv49">Pirate&rsquo;s Bitcoin Booty To Go On Sale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4a"><img alt="$25 million worth of seized Bitcoin to be auctioned." src="http://cur.lv/6kv4a" width="498" height="248"></a><p>Millions worth of bit coins seized in connection with illegal activities have been cleared for federal auction. Image: Andy Field, Jay Hathaway via The Daily Dot</p></div>
<p>Nearly 30,000 bitcoins seized in October of last year have been signed off on a forfeiture order, federal prosecutors from the Manhattan U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s office announced on Thursday.</p>
<p>Currently valued around $25 million, the bitcoins were seized from Ross Ulbricht, who allegedly founded and operated hidden website Silk Road under the pseudonym Dread Pirate Roberts.</p>
<p>Described by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4b">prosecutors</a> as the most &ldquo;sophisticated and extensive criminal marketplace on the Internet,&rdquo; Silk Road facilitated anonymous users in brokering illegal deals in computer hacking, forgeries, drug trafficking, and even murder-for-hire.</p>
<p>In addition to the 30,000 bitcoins included in the forfeiture order signed by U.S. District Judge J. Paul Oetken on Wednesday, the FBI are now in possession of another 144,336 bitcoins seized in connection with the Silk Road <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4c">case</a>.&nbsp; At today&rsquo;s exchange rates, the government is holding approximately $148 million total in their wallet from the bust, the largest such action involving the virtual currency to date.</p>
<p>Though the 30,000 seized in the initial action has been cleared for sale, the additional 144, 336 will remain in the government&rsquo;s wallet for the time being.</p>
<p>It is unclear how the FBI plans to offload the bitcoins, as there is currently no legally certified Bitcoin exchange in the United States. &nbsp;Manhattan U.S. Attorney Office <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4d">spokesperson</a>, Jim Margolin, said the bitcoins will go on auction soon, but did not give a specific date.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6kv49">Pirate&rsquo;s Bitcoin Booty To Go On Sale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 17:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Online Games Where Gold Farming Is Legal]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4e]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Are there any games that are gold farming friendly? Gold farming is where you collect ingame currency and sell it for real money, or Bitcoins. It's a criminal offence to do this on games like Runescape and World of Warcraft due to the fact that they legally own everything. So I'm looking for games that permits you to do real world trading.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 14:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcloud: A Decentralized Cloud Based on Proof of Bandwidth]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4f]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yow"> galapag0 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4g">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4f">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 13:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Suggestions on Mining Rig Specs?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The reason I want to get in to Bitcoin Mining is so I can get some Office Space, Game Engine Licenses and Game Design Software / Tools so that I can get in to game design. Based on the current Bitcoin Market Value, which is $840.10 (Which for me is &pound;514.64): The amount which I think I'd need for everything is 350BTC, which is $294,035.00 (Which for me is &pound;180,113.20).</p>
<p>In a few months time, I will be designing and purchasing my own Custom-Built PC and I'm looking for suggestions of Machine Specs I should get which might help me get my Bitcoin Goal by the end of this year or the start of next. I want a computer that will be very powerful (meaning insane specs), as I'm willing to spend up to $8,000 on it, (Currently $13,059.20). Also, I'm also looking for suggestions of the best (based on your personal opinion) Bitcoin Miner and Mining Pool to use.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>CTCB</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 10:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is the title and who is the author of this tale of science fiction?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>A spaceship breaks down and the pilot decided to land on a planet. To not affect the inhabitants, look for the "ocean side" and lands in a small remote island.
Land on the beach. Tries unsuccessfully to repair the spaceship. After verifying that the atmosphere is breathable, walks along the beach. Find an attractive woman lying on the sand and... </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[¿Cuál es el título y el autor de este cuento de ciencia ficción?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Una nave espacial se aver&iacute;a y su piloto decide aterrizar en un planeta. Para no afectar a los habitantes busca el "lado oce&aacute;nico" y aterriza en una peque&ntilde;a isla alejada de todo.
Aterriza cerca de la playa. Intenta infructuosamente reparar la nave. Al verificar que la atm&oacute;sfera es respirable, sale a caminar por la playa. Encuentra una atractiva mujer acostada en la arena y....</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Considering the increase in bitcoin value, is it time to decrease the minimum bitcoin amount for withdrawal?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjth]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Are users finding it hard to reach the 0.01 bitcoin limit?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Sarah and Yair</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[bitcoins question]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjue]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>How many karma points I need to buy bitcoins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>barzeta</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Easiest Miner]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjui]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>What is the easiest miner to install and run on my PC?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sigmaasset</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 20:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fix to whirlpool for android version.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjuk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fix to whirlpool for android version.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fix to whirlpool for android version.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 08:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fixed bug in opentxs showpayments]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg6z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed bug in opentxs showpayments

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed bug in opentxs showpayments

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 07:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Help, bitmessage keeps sending me the same messages over and over.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg99]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Not sure how else to desrcibe the behavior. This is an amazing little piece of technology, but I keep getting the same messages over and over. For example I've gotten some messages 4 times over the past day. And they keep rolling in.</p> <p>Did I set something up wrong? Wtf is going on.</p> <p>(Ubuntu 13.10, installed via git)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9a"> v1- </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9b">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg99">[19 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 09:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Regular Releases? Last version was October 10, 2013]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>The forum has spam and there is a lack of posts here about continuing releases. I saw a commit 13 days ago in github, but is there a place which lists the roadmap to future releases?</p> <p>Following up that question, are there other implementations with regular development progressing? </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9e"> kaega </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9f">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9d">[8 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 05:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[RTS Games?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgb6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I would like to know if you guys have played any awesome RTS games that you just can't get enough of!
I have played : </p>
<p>AOE ( all the parts )</p>
<p>Rise Of Nations</p>
<p>Command and Conquer games.</p>
<p>[All at good settings and I wanted to play age of empires online but I came to know of it late, that is , it is shutting down In July.)</p>
<p>So would you guys recommend any similar games like these for my specs&gt;</p>
<p>Intel G41 Chipset, 2GB ram, 2.7 (x 2)GHz Processors . ( I know they are not fit to play any great games but games similar to the ones I mentioned would be fantastic! :) </p>
<p>Thanks &amp; Best regards,</p>
<p>Jibit</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Jibit</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Does anybody know what BitMessageErl is?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgbg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I noticed someone connect to my server with this user agent. Is someone writing a client in Erlang maybe? Cool.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yol"> bpeel </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cgbh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgbg">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin in the Real World]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b4a]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Even as Bitcoin is facing regulation challenges overseas, online retailers and service providers both here and abroad have continued to initiate Bitcoin payment options in order to make their businesses more inclusive and their transactions more immediate. Street vendors in London, bars in Berlin, flower shops in Santa Monica, real estate brokers in New York, [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4a">Bitcoin in the Real World</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even as Bitcoin is facing <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymu">regulation</a> challenges overseas, online retailers and service providers both here and abroad have continued to initiate Bitcoin payment options in order to make their businesses more inclusive and their transactions more immediate.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/68b4b"><img alt="More retailers accepting Bitcoin." src="http://cur.lv/68b4c" width="224" height="300"></a><p>An increasing number of retailers worldwide are now accepting Bitcoin. Image &amp; sign: Cryptocables</p></div>
<p>Street vendors in London, bars in Berlin, flower shops in Santa Monica, real estate brokers in New York, and even a university in Cypress join a growing list of businesses that are being drawn to the absence of transaction fees and the ability to process payments in under a minute by eschewing traditional money transfer providers and using Bitcoin instead.</p>
<p>Others, like internet gaming giant Zynga, <a href="http://cur.lv/68b4d">online megastore</a> Overstock.com, and popular blog hosting site WordPress, see value in the inherent universality of the virtual currency.&nbsp; (Bitcoin is neither created nor regulated by any central government and, as such, is not subject to an individual country&rsquo;s economic scales or inflation.)&nbsp; Andy Skelton, spokesperson for WordPress, issued a statement in November saying that the company recognizes the <a href="http://cur.lv/68b4e">restrictions</a> some people face due to the socio-politics of their geography.&nbsp; &ldquo;We don&rsquo;t think an individual blogger from Haiti, Ethiopia, or Kenya should have diminished access to the blogosphere because of payment issues they can&rsquo;t control,&rdquo; Skelton said on the website. &ldquo;Our goal is to enable people, not block them.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Far from being just an ideology or exercise in economics, Bitcoin is quickly proving to be a useful and legitimate tender for real-world goods and services.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4a">Bitcoin in the Real World</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 18:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Creative ways to earn Bitcoins]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgca]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Is there a webpage where you can offer your creativity, ingenuity, analytical or artistic gift to help solving problems for companies who are willing to pay in bitcoins? Is there a connection between industry or large companies asking for advices, problem solutions, and creative people who want to earn bitcoins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ecostroj</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 14:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is the title of this movie?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgcb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Possibly 80's, from USA. A group of coworkers arrive by plane to a tropical island to receive a leadership course. Immediately upon arrival asked to sign a life insurance policy to start the course. A person refuses to sign, instructors indicate that if one person does not sign, then the course will not be performed. Nobody reads the insurance and all signed. The chief instructor informs them that what they just signed is a complete surrender of all their human rights and thereafter can do whatever they want with them. Nightmare Begins (psychological and physical torture) and the attempt to be rid of it.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 13:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Cuál es el título de esta película?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgcc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Posiblemente de los 80, estadounidense. Un grupo de compa&ntilde;eros de trabajo llegan en avi&oacute;n a una isla tropical a recibir un curso de liderazgo. Inmediatamente al llegar les piden que firmen un seguro de vida para iniciar el curso. Una persona se niega a firmar, los instructores indican que si una sola persona no firma, entonces el curso no se va a realizar, nadie lee el seguro y todos firman. La jefa de los instructores les informa que lo que acaban de firmar es una cesi&oacute;n completa de todos sus derechos y de ah&iacute; en adelante pueden hacer lo que quieran con ellos. Se inicia la pesadilla y el intento de librarse de ella. </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 03:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin from Wall Street to Washington]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b4d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Though Bitcoin has had no shortage of speculation (both positive and negative) in 2013, the sheer volume of press it has received speaks to the resilience of the virtual currency.&nbsp; With the start of the new year, now seems the perfect time to see where the highly debated tender has been &ndash; and where it&rsquo;s [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4d">Bitcoin from Wall Street to Washington</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/68baa"><img alt="Washington and Wall Street embrace Bitcoin" src="http://cur.lv/68bab" width="405" height="229"></a><p>Washington joins Wall Street in embracing Bitcoin. Image via Troy Kuhn.</p></div>
<p>Though Bitcoin has had no shortage of speculation (both positive and negative) in 2013, the sheer volume of press it has received speaks to the resilience of the virtual currency.&nbsp; With the start of the new year, now seems the perfect time to see where the highly debated tender has been &ndash; and where it&rsquo;s headed&mdash;amongst some of the nation&rsquo;s money makers and policy makers.</p>
<p>It may be no coincidence that the upturn in attention accompanies an increasing number of Wall Street firms not only interested in, but also investing in Bitcoin.&nbsp; Merrill Lynch released a report last month, prompting lead report strategist David Woo to share <a href="http://cur.lv/68bac">his view</a> that Bitcoin is a &ldquo;serious competitor&rdquo; in monetary transactions and &ldquo;as a medium of exchange, Bitcoin has clear potential for growth.&rdquo;&nbsp; The legitimacy of the currency was solidified further last week when a San Francisco based hedge fund posted a job opening for a Junior Bitcoin Execution Trader.&nbsp; At the same time, a number of other investment firms have admitted to creating Bitcoin departments within their companies.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/65ynq">Wall Streeters</a> may have taken notice of the virtual currency&rsquo;s prospects some time ago, but new players are joining the game consistently, bringing different industries and bigger names to the table.&nbsp; In a December 2013 statement, Overstock.com CEO Patrick Byrne announced that the website will begin accepting payment in Bitcoin later this year, making it possible to use bitcoins to purchase, well, almost anything&mdash;and potentially setting precedent for other major retailers, who have been observing from the sidelines, thus far.&nbsp; Byrne made it clear that his was a business as well as a <a href="http://cur.lv/68bad">philosophical</a> decision, telling CNN&rsquo;s Ben Rooney that he believes &ldquo;the monetary base should not be something that a government can create with a stroke of a pen.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Byrne isn&rsquo;t the only one with a Libertarian love for the cyber currency.&nbsp; Even more recently, Congressman Steve Stockman has announced that he will accept Bitcoin donations to help fund his campaign for U.S. Senate.&nbsp; In an online video, Stockman stated that his <a href="http://cur.lv/68bae">support</a> for the deregulated monetary form stems from the desire for the &ldquo;freedom to choose what you do with your money, and freedom to keep your money without people influencing it,&rdquo; the Dallas Morning News reported.&nbsp; As the Federal Election Commission has yet to decide how to classify the donation, it is unclear at this time how the Bitcoin can be spent in terms of campaign financing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4d">Bitcoin from Wall Street to Washington</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can I still get paid for monetizing my videos on YouTube even though I'm not connected to AdSense?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yjc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I've recently began to monetize my videos, but I noticed that my channel has to be connected to a AdSense account. Now, I was wondering; if I monetized my video before I create an AdSense account and people clicked the ads, would I get paid for those previous clicks after I've linked an AdSense account?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 13:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #13 from randy-waterhouse/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4y]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #13 from randy-waterhouse/master

Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #13 from randy-waterhouse/master

Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>randy-waterhouse</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 02:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author></author>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 02:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can someone explain this double spend on blockchain.info?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm confused by double-spend linked below, in which both transactions ended up in blocks mined by different miners.  Specifically, I'm wondering if there's any way to tell what exactly happened based on the available information.</p>

<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7010i" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7010i</a></p>

<p>Based on my limited understanding of bitcoin, I'm assuming this could have happened in one of the following three ways. If I'm wrong, or if I'm missing other possibilities, could someone please let me know?</p>

<p>1) The double-spender broadcast the first transaction to the network, and then mined his own block containing a transaction using the same output.  He ultimately wasn't able to "outrun" the honest blockchain, but he managed to mine his block quickly enough that some nodes in the network received it before receiving the longer blockchain. So both blocks were briefly accepted by parts of the network, and one was eventually "orphaned" (so its transactions are unconfirmed).</p>

<p>2) Same situation, but the double-spender's blockchain prevailed and the block containing the first transaction broadcast to the network was orphaned.</p>

<p>3) The double-spender didn't mine anything, he just tried a normal double-spend against someone who doesn't require confirmations. Both transactions happened to be included in blocks that were mined simultaneously by different miners in the network, and one was orphaned.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>craw</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 01:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #15 from da2ce7/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv50]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #15 from da2ce7/master

Windows: update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #15 from da2ce7/master

Windows: update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[update 3rd-party project files]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv51]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Why is a double hash of the previous transaction included in Txin?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010j]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In <a href="http://cur.lv/7010k" rel="nofollow"><code>Txin</code></a>, there is a double hash of the previous transaction.</p>

<p>Why?  What purpose does that serve?  How is this data used later?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Gracchus</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 07:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[My MultiBit is unable to connect]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010l]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have installed my MultiBit wallet and there is red "connecting" sign in left bottom corner. Wallet never connects. When I try it from another place (my friends house) everything is ok.</p>

<p>It is obvious that its network problem in my place. I have public IP and port 8333 is properly forwarded. I am using Mac OS X 10.8.5.</p>

<p>I have no idea what else to try or where to look for some error messages. Do you have any ideas what else to try or where to look for some clues?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Macejkou</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there alt-coin dice ?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgcj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Like satochi dice. </p>
<p>I have found this <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgck">http://cur.lv/6cgck</a> </p>
<p>Looks like no one alt-dice works.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>an0nymous</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 04:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #9 from mahyar/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv53]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #9 from mahyar/master

homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #9 from mahyar/master

homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #12 from FellowTraveler/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv54]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #12 from FellowTraveler/master

FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #12 from FellowTraveler/master

FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 02:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yn8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!!
(So far tested on Mac only.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!!
(So far tested on Mac only.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 01:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Small fix for chai5.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ynf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Small fix for chai5.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Small fix for chai5.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #11 from FellowTraveler/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv55]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #11 from FellowTraveler/master

Fixing crash bug in password threads.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #11 from FellowTraveler/master

Fixing crash bug in password threads.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 00:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fixing crash bug in password threads.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ynk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fixing crash bug in password threads.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fixing crash bug in password threads.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Rugatu video]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ynt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>We would like to create a video introduction for Rugatu so that new users understand how it works from the first moment. We liked <a href="http://cur.lv/65ynu">this video</a> as an example of what we want to achieve, so if you're good with this kind of cgi and editing please take a shot at our video.</p>
<p>Anything else you want to know, please ask.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>cscoxx</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 11:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.  Verified to work from build -&gt; running on OSX 10.9]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv57]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.  Verified to work from build -&gt; running on OSX 10.9</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.  Verified to work from build -&gt; running on OSX 10.9</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>mahyar</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 22:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Mining a primecoin based currency (datacoin). How do I find out how much hash power im doing?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010m]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>How do I find out how much hashing power am I providing to the network? What is the command to find it out? </p>

<p>Currently I see this: <a href="http://cur.lv/7010n" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7010n</a></p>

<p>when I run:  <strong>watch 'datacoind listaccounts &amp; datacoind getmininginfo'</strong></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>duckx</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 16:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #7 from da2ce7/zlib_windows]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv58]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #7 from da2ce7/zlib_windows

Merged.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #7 from da2ce7/zlib_windows

Merged.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 13:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Mission to De-Centralize the Internet : The New Yorker]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yom]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[In the nineteen-seventies, the Internet was a small, decentralized collective of computers. The personal-computer revolution that followed built upon that foundation ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[sending an order through BTC-e API incorrect field error]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I get the following message when trying to send a buy/sell order through btc-e api using a variable:
<code>"you incorrectly entered one of the fields"</code>. </p>

<p>This is the line of code I use for sending an order:</p>

<pre><code>APIMain.Trade(BtcePair.BtcUsd, TradeType.Sell, Math.Round(myAskP, 4), Math.Round(myAskQ, 4));
</code></pre>

<p>Sending an order via api does work when I enter it like this:</p>

<pre><code>APIMain.Trade(BtcePair.BtcUsd, TradeType.Sell, 800m, 0.5m);
</code></pre>

<p>How do I force a decimal variable to be formatted like the line above?
Anybody experienced similar problems?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user10776</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 18:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What are the most important websites evey Bitcoin user should know?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgcp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This should help newbies:</p>
<ol><li>bitcointalk.org: Largest bitcoin-related user forum. Contains just about all the info you may need to get started in this world, although you may have to dig in quite deep.</li>
<li>Blockchain.com: Largest online wallet website. Starting a new wallet is 100% free.</li>
<li>Mt.Gox.com: Japan-based trading website, at the momet the largest site to buy and sell BTCs.</li>
<li>Weusecoins.org: Bitcoin info for the newcomer.</li>
<li>bitcoin.stackexchange.com: Q&amp;A site for bitcoins. Very similar to Rugatu but no BTC exchange involved.</li>
<li>Bitstamp: Bitcoin trade site.</li>
</ol><p>Are there any more important/useful sites newbies should know about?</p>
<p>note: I did NOT include coinbase because of some alleged scam posts I have read recently on bitcointalk.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Les</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 13:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Running bitcoind on VPS, won't speak to my web server]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have a VPS with bitcoind set up, synced the blocks and its all running fine. I have set up the bitcoin.conf file and allowed the IP of my web host server.</p>

<p>I am running a script on my web host that communicates to the wallet but it just won't connect! </p>

<pre><code>Fatal error: Uncaught exception 'Exception' with message 'Unable to connect to http://cur.lv/7010q in /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/driver_test.php:61 Stack trace: #0 /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/index.php(16): jsonRPCClient-&gt;__call('getbalance', Array) #1 /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/index.php(16): jsonRPCClient-&gt;getbalance() #2 {main} thrown in /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/driver_test.php on line 61
</code></pre>

<p>Any suggestions? I have run out of ideas.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Tau11</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 14:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Opening Wallet with a different App]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010r]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I just bought a couple of bitcoins. I got my wallet from Bitcom.org but I learned that there is this Electrum wallet which Id like to try. How do I open my wallet with the new App?</p>

<p>thanks!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user9903</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 12:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin qt synchronization problems!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010s]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>So bought my first Bitcoins the other day (27 &amp; 28/11/13) on localcoins, then transferred them to a MultiBit wallet. No problems.</p>

<p>I decided to use a 'safer' wallet, therefore I moved the coins to a Bitcoin qt wallet. The last few days I've been waiting for the blockchain to sync..got to 97% then my comp crashed.</p>

<p>I reopened bitcoin qt, and now it's syncing from zero again...just as slowly.</p>

<p>What should I do? Is there a way to open a another wallet, get my coins there?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user9800</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 08:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Not getting enough Hashrate]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have an i3-3220 processor which i am using for mining. 
I know that you're supposed to use a GPU and all that. But currently i'm just trying it out before spending money.</p>

<p>I'm using CPUMiner, mining at middlecoin.com, 24 hours a day.</p>

<p>The problem is that i'm recieving very less hashrate.
This <a href="http://cur.lv/7010u" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7010u</a> points out that an i3 processor (which is actually a lower model than mine) recieves almost 8.5 MH/s and i receive about 5.5 KH/s on each thread that is about 27 KH/s in total.Why such a large difference?</p>

<p>What do i need to tweak? Is my program useless? Are the settings wrong? Is it problem with the pool?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Harry King</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 22:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Some Bitcoin games?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010v]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Games where you can earn/win Bitcoins with little or no cost of entry.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 08:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Would it be worth it to start mining bitcoins at this point?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010w]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>My budget for mining hardware is $600. Would there be an ASIC miner that I could buy for this that would return this and also net a decent amount of profit within a month or so? Is it even worth it for beginners without tons of money to invest in it now?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user9245</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 04:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[/r/Bitcoin FAQ - Newcomers please read]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68bfo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>This posts explains some dos and don'ts about what to post on <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokc">/r/Bitcoin</a> .</p> <p>First lets start with...</p> <hr><p><strong>Messaging mods</strong></p> <p>Modmail is for:</p> <ul><li>Problems with the subreddit (some sidebar links are broken for example)</li> <li>Problems with submissions (spam filter sometimes catches too much, we sort things a few times a day. If you have an <strong>urgent</strong> submission, contact us)</li> <li>Requests that need mod support - if you need us to verify your identity for say, AMA, or that you represent an organization, contact us and we'll do our best to help you</li> </ul><p>Modmail is <strong>not</strong> for:</p> <ul><li>Asking general questions</li> <li>Reporting obvious spam submissions (that's what the <strong>Report</strong> button is for)</li> <li>Advertisements on the subreddit (it is handled <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfp">through Reddit</a>, not us)</li> <li>Help with shadowbans (again, that's Reddit, not us. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfq">Contact them</a>)</li> </ul><p><strong>Frequent requests:</strong></p> <ul><li>"Can I get a flair?" - No, at the moment we are <strong>not</strong> giving anyone flair on the subreddit</li> <li>"Can you add my subreddit to the sidebar?" - If you are a local Bitcoin subreddit, we can add you to the wiki. If you are not a Bitcoin-related subreddit, 99% chance the answer is no. If you are a Bitcoin-related subreddit, we only add subreddits that are established - if you have less than a few hundred subscribers and less than a post a day, the answer is most likely no. Beyond that, we can talk.</li> <li>"Can you link to my website from the sidebar?" - No</li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Submissions</strong></p> <p><strong>Please don't post:</strong></p> <ul><li>Ask to be stickied - it's like asking for upvotes. People don't like it when you ask for upvotes.</li> <li>General questions about how Bitcoin works - go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfr">/r/BitcoinBeginners</a> or search in <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfs">http://cur.lv/68bfs</a> .</li> <li>General newcomer questions, like "which client should I use?", "how do I buy Bitcoin?" - again, <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfr">/r/BitcoinBeginners</a></li> <li>Questions about mining - go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bft">/r/bitcoinmining</a></li> <li>"Is it profitable to mine?" - punch your numbers into <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfu">a calculator</a> or go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bft">/r/bitcoinmining</a></li> <li>"Should I buy Bitcoin?" / "Is it still worth investing in Bitcoin?" - You shouldn't take financial advice from the Internet, you need to figure this out for yourself</li> <li>"What about altcoin X?" / "Should I buy altcoin X?" / "You should buy altcoin X!" - This is a very big topic in itself. Short answer is no under most circumstances. For a longer explanation, please read <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfv">my blog entry</a> and the accompanying <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfw">reddit submission</a> for discussion on the topic.</li> <li>Asking for money - unless you are a reputable charity, your post will be treated like spam</li> <li>Complaints about not buying Bitcoins when they were $X/BTC - nobody cares</li> <li>Referral links - your post will be treated like spam</li> <li>"BUYBUYBUY"/"SELLSELLSELL" - you will be treated like a troll</li> <li>Submissions or posts with curse words directed at someone - don't insult other people. Your posts will be treated like spam otherwise. Occasional expressions like "holy shit this is awesome!" are tolerated in moderation.</li> <li>"Can I buy less than 1 bitcoin?" - The answer is "yes, you can purchase as little as 0.00000001 BTC at a time, you don't have to buy a whole coin, similarly how you can buy a gram of gold, you don't need to buy a whole gold bar"</li> <li>"What happens after all 21M BTC are mined?" - Either Bitcoin will be long gone before then (if the system doesn't catch on), or <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfx">miners will be earning their money from transaction fees instead</a>.</li> <li>"What happens to lost coins?" - Lost coins remain lost, unless someone finds a private key for them. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfy">This is <strong>ONLY</strong> viable if quantum computers become strong enough</a>. Otherwise, <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfz">the numbers used by Bitcoin are too big to be brute forced - heat death of the universe will occur before a colission is found.</a>. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg0">As for re-mining old bitcoins, there are many reasons to not return lost coins back to circulation.</a></li> </ul><p><strong>Take heed when posting:</strong></p> <ul><li>Memes - memes are allowed, but some people may not like you for posting them. Be sure to use <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg1">/r/Bitcoinmemes</a> as well</li> <li>Information about all-time-highs, price spikes, crashes and so forth - 90% of the time, someone has already posted about it. Check <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg2">/r/bitcoin/new</a> first before posting.</li> <li>Questions about help with a particular website or business - <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokc">/r/Bitcoin</a> is not tech support for any business, you're better off contacting the support of the business in question through their forums or ticket system</li> </ul><p><strong>What to do if you see...</strong></p> <ul><li>Spam - click "report" underneath the submission, vote accordingly. Don't message mods unless the spam is subtle or needs context</li> <li>Repost - vote accordingly, click "report"</li> <li>A post from the "don't" list above - direct the posted to a proper subreddit if applicable (for questions and newbie posts), vote and report accordingly otherwise</li> <li>A post that is allowed on this subreddit but you don't like it being here - vote accordingly, don't report it. If it is allowed, the mods will not remove the post. Your votes shape what submissions get the most exposure - upvote the posts you want to see more of, downvote the ones you want to see less of.</li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Some good guides you should look into:</strong></p> <ul><li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg3">Will I earn money by mining?</a></li> <li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg4">Basic Bitcoin security guide</a></li> <li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg5">The straightforward Bitcoin safety and security guide</a></li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Please do</strong></p> <ul><li>Read the sidebar for community rules - following them will make everyone's day better.</li> <li>Be sceptical of any news without credible sources - a lot of bad people are trying to play on your emotions by fabricating fake stories. Be sceptical of any story without a credible citation, especially when it is related to economic or legal side of things.</li> </ul><hr><p>Thank you for your attention. Post responsibly, vote on all submissions, live and let live, have fun.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokl"> ThePiachu </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/68bfo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfo">[196 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 04:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yokm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yqt"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>November 02, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokp" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yqt"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7010x(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7010y">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to integrate a Bitcoin payment service in my auction site]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>So, if I wanted to have Bitcoin as a form of method where users could pay, how would I do this? Obviously, there is paypal, where the buyer sends money through pp, which disperses to the seller. So, I need to have this type of system on my site as well. Is there anything like it for Bitcoins? </p>

<p>Thanks!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>ramboramos</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 04:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3180 from pstratem/processgetdata]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yra]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3180 from pstratem/processgetdata

Reduce latency in network processing</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3180 from pstratem/processgetdata

Reduce latency in network processing</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 05:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[process received messages one at a time without sleeping between messages]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>process received messages one at a time without sleeping between messages</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>process received messages one at a time without sleeping between messages</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>pstratem</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 04:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3154 from gavinandresen/mempool_refactor]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3154 from gavinandresen/mempool_refactor

Mempool refactor</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3154 from gavinandresen/mempool_refactor

Mempool refactor</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 04:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Refactor: CTxMempool class to its own txmempool.{cpp,h}]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Refactor: CTxMempool class to its own txmempool.{cpp,h}</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Refactor: CTxMempool class to its own txmempool.{cpp,h}</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 01:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3193 from joshtriplett/patch-1]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yre]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3193 from joshtriplett/patch-1

.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3193 from joshtriplett/patch-1

.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 02:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories

Unless a .gitignore pattern is anchored, it'll match in any directory, not juts at the top level.  Simplify .gitignore accordingly.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories

Unless a .gitignore pattern is anchored, it'll match in any directory, not juts at the top level.  Simplify .gitignore accordingly.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>joshtriplett</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3087]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3087

caca6aa Make some globals in main non-public. (Pieter Wuille)
85eb2ce Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database. (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3087

caca6aa Make some globals in main non-public. (Pieter Wuille)
85eb2ce Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database. (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 14:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yokw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>26 lines (14 sloc)</span><span>1.232 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>Join our Bitmessage chan! First, download the client from bitmessage.org. Then, go to file --&gt; Join/Create chan --&gt; Join Chan and enter the following details (use the full name of the chan including the "created by" part)</p>
<p><strong>Name of chan:</strong> Bitcoin Crowdfunding incubator (Created by BM-2cVPTkVZo2mDoJyXmaGkujtJNovVhu6W1H)<br><strong>Chan address:</strong> BM-2cVVS3U9zdfDyQRxP8wsLUG3epavsqsDja<br></p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoky" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://cur.lv/5yoky"></a><br><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokz" rel="nofollow"><br>Image created by </a><a href="http://cur.lv/5yol0" rel="nofollow">Jack Z</a></p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/70111(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/70112">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is Ad5.eu a scam/legit site?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow5o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Researched answers please. I would also appreciate it if you've used the service before. Ad5.eu is a URL shortener site, but pays, like Adf.ly and CoinURL. The rates are really high, and I'm wondering if it's a scam or not. Please give researched answers, or even better, your experience with this service.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 11:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yol4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>November 01, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yol6" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/70113(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/70114">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yola]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>15 lines (12 sloc)</span><span>0.604 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>You can <em>visit any project in the browser</em> by surfing to entrances.github.com/[ProjectName].html</p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/70115(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/70116">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3128]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3128

0056095 Show short scriptPubKeys correctly (Peter Todd)
22de68d Relay OP_RETURN TxOut as standard transaction type (Peter Todd)

Signed-off-by: Gavin Andresen <gavinandresen></gavinandresen></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3128

0056095 Show short scriptPubKeys correctly (Peter Todd)
22de68d Relay OP_RETURN TxOut as standard transaction type (Peter Todd)

Signed-off-by: Gavin Andresen <gavinandresen></gavinandresen></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 02:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3114]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3114

a616206 Give peer time-adjustment data an own lock (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3114

a616206 Give peer time-adjustment data an own lock (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Make some globals in main non-public.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yru]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Make some globals in main non-public.

This means they are declared static, and their extern definition in
main.h is removed. Also moved CBlockIndexWorkComparator to the .cpp
file.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Make some globals in main non-public.

This means they are declared static, and their extern definition in
main.h is removed. Also moved CBlockIndexWorkComparator to the .cpp
file.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 23:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database.

As block index entries have a flag for marking invalid blocks, the
'best invalid work' information can be derived from there. In addition,
remove the global from main.h</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database.

As block index entries have a flag for marking invalid blocks, the
'best invalid work' information can be derived from there. In addition,
remove the global from main.h</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 23:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3159]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3159

9eb4ab6 transactionview: make exportClicked() use message() (Philip Kaufmann)
868d3ee transactionview: add message() signal (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3159

9eb4ab6 transactionview: make exportClicked() use message() (Philip Kaufmann)
868d3ee transactionview: add message() signal (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 16:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3189]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3189

71ba467 [Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message() (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3189

71ba467 [Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message() (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 07:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3067 from Diapolo/debug-switch]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3067 from Diapolo/debug-switch

re-work -debug switch handling</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3067 from Diapolo/debug-switch

re-work -debug switch handling</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 22:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[[Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message()]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yry]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>[Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message()

- add new processSendCoinsReturn() function, which parses the
  status of WalletModel::SendCoinsReturn and generates a pair consisting
  of a message and message flags
- result is we only need one emit message() call
- this change ensures that the GUI is shown for warnings/errors in
  sendcoinsdialog, because of message() taking care of that for modal
  messages
- changes 2 warning message into error messages and removed "Error:"
  in front of the actual error message string</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>[Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message()

- add new processSendCoinsReturn() function, which parses the
  status of WalletModel::SendCoinsReturn and generates a pair consisting
  of a message and message flags
- result is we only need one emit message() call
- this change ensures that the GUI is shown for warnings/errors in
  sendcoinsdialog, because of message() taking care of that for modal
  messages
- changes 2 warning message into error messages and removed "Error:"
  in front of the actual error message string</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[transactionview: make exportClicked() use message()]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: make exportClicked() use message()

- use message() for displaying success or failure of export
- rework the strings to be more detailed / informative
- additional small cleanups</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: make exportClicked() use message()

- use message() for displaying success or failure of export
- rework the strings to be more detailed / informative
- additional small cleanups</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[transactionview: add message() signal]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys0]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: add message() signal

- allow to use message() in transactionview by connecting to the
  message() signal in WalletView</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: add message() signal

- allow to use message() in transactionview by connecting to the
  message() signal in WalletView</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3160 from Diapolo/walletview]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3160 from Diapolo/walletview

[Qt] walletview: make backupWallet() use GUIUtil::getSaveFileName()</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3160 from Diapolo/walletview

[Qt] walletview: make backupWallet() use GUIUtil::getSaveFileName()</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[re-work -debug switch handling]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>re-work -debug switch handling

- re-work -debug help message text
- make -debug log every debugging information again (even all categories)
- remove unneeded fDebug checks in front of LogPrint()/qDebug(), as that
  check is done in LogPrintf() when category is != NULL (true for all
  LogPrint() calls
- remove fDebug ONLY in code which is NOT performance-critical
- harmonize addrman category name
- deprecate -debugnet usage, should be used via -debug=net and remove the
  corresponding global</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>re-work -debug switch handling

- re-work -debug help message text
- make -debug log every debugging information again (even all categories)
- remove unneeded fDebug checks in front of LogPrint()/qDebug(), as that
  check is done in LogPrintf() when category is != NULL (true for all
  LogPrint() calls
- remove fDebug ONLY in code which is NOT performance-critical
- harmonize addrman category name
- deprecate -debugnet usage, should be used via -debug=net and remove the
  corresponding global</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3176 from Diapolo/key]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3176 from Diapolo/key

fix wrong memcmp() usage in CKey::operator==</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3176 from Diapolo/key

fix wrong memcmp() usage in CKey::operator==</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 08:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yole]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>October 28, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolf" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/70117(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/70118">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[18 lines (13 sloc)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div><div>
<span>18 lines (13 sloc)</span><span>0.598 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>These are our crowdfunding entries:</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolk" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/5yolk</a><br></p></article></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/70119(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7011a">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7011b(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7011c">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysa"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>October 19, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolv" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysa"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7011d(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7011e">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>14 lines (11 sloc)</span><span>0.509 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>You can visit any project in the browser by surfing to entrances.github.com/[ProjectName].html</p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7011f(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7011g">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 05:24:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yom3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysj"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>September 24, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yom5" rel="nofollow">Update README.md</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysj"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>14 lines (10 sloc)</span><span>0.408 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p></p>
<p></p>
<p></p>
<p>Hey! Welcome to the Web Developer's group!</p>
<p>We build stuff together. Have a look at the projects at entrances.github.com</p>
<p>If you want to discuss contracts, payments or other sensitive information, send a Bitmessage to <strong>BM-2D7XVMiTuyLtSGF6t4NERnUDrfbZvTdtG4</strong></p>
<p></p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7011h(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7011i">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Trying to import all blk00000.dat (many files each of 173 MB)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011j]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I've moved my bitcoind process to a new server, I made a backup of my .bitcoin folder (I'm using linux). I would really like to avoid downloading the whole blockchain again.
What's the right way to import all the blk00000.dat files? Is it enough to move the .bitcoin folder over the new one?</p>

<p>Thanks in advance,</p>

<p>EDIT: I see the Loadblock option but I suppose I should run it after move the file outside.
Anyone can confirm this? Is there a better way?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>dna2</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 21:02:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BBC News - Snowden link to encrypted email service closes]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ysm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Two encrypted email services have closed down for reasons linked to US intelligence leaker Edward Snowden. Texas-based Lavabit service has shut down but ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How much memory and bandwidth does bitcoind take up on a CentOS Linux system?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm thinking about installing <a href="http://cur.lv/7011l" rel="nofollow">bitcoind</a> on my web server that runs on <a href="http://cur.lv/7011m" rel="nofollow">CentOS</a>. How much memory and bandwidth might it take up and would it affect my other sites on my server?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>duckx</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 16:04:37 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Pirate Bay founder is raising money for spy-proof ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv5z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Has the recent NSA scandal created a greater appetite for fully encrypted communications options? Hemlis, developed by The Pirate Bay's Peter Sunde, will be one test ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 21:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage is the Bitcoin of online communication - CoinDesk]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgdc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage is a protocol that implements some of the ideas of Bitcoin into communications.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 09:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How did you find out about Bitcoins?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yso]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I found out about bitcoins from an article on Mashable a few days ago, I've spend my days since then researching all about them and now hoping to get 1 shiney BTC. </p>
<p>How'd you find out about bitcoins?</p>
<p>Edit: by the way I'd love to offer a reward but I literally have no coins, my computer isnt powerful enough to mine and I havent earnt enough to transfer to my wallet yet :(</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>kerodean</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 17:28:01 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Something to laugh at?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ysp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Sudden boredom has led to me posting this. Got any video, image or text that seems to make people laugh? Why don't you post it here to prevent boredom of me and others! (May tip very funny stuff)</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 09:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can you find some "bugs"?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yt2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yt3">this thread</a> on bitcointalk.org we decided to offer bounties for finding software bugs and vulnerabilities on Rugatu, so here is your chance to earn bitcoins while doing some ethical hacking.</p>
<p>Here is a small list so you can make an idea of what to expect, although every contribution will be rewarded.</p>
<ul><li>0.001 BTC Embarrassing language mistakes and typos<br></li>
<li>0.0025 BTC Unknown unexpected behavior (e.g. endless loops, links to 404 pages, UI issues ...)<br></li>
<li>0.005 BTC Harmless XSS problems<br></li>
<li>0.010 BTC CSRF and XSS problems</li>
<li>0.05 BTC Critical CSRF and XSS problems (e.g. possibility of session stealing)</li>
<li>0.1 BTC Manipulating parts of the DB</li>
<li>0.25 BTC RFI/LFI bugs</li>
<li>0.5 BTC Full access to the Database</li>
<li>1 BTC Full root access to the server</li>
<li>2 BTC Stealing coins from the hot wallet.</li>
</ul><p>Rules:</p>
<ul><li>No (D)DoS</li>
<li>Security related bugs have to be reported privately - report at rugatu dot com</li>
<li>Once a bug is abused you won't get a reward anymore</li>
<li>UI issues have to apply for at least 2% of the users (IE 6 problems are ignored)</li>
</ul><p>Have fun.</p>
<p>11.18.2013 Rewards updated</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>paraipan</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 02:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[First bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yt4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a pic my my FIRST bitcoin :) thinking about hanging it on my wall.</p>
<p><img alt="alt text" src="http://cur.lv/65yt5"></p>
<p>anyone else have pics of their very first bitcoins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scott</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Open Transactions Client (for Grandmas)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgde]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Asked by Obsi on <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgdf">bitcointalk</a></strong></p>
<p>I'm not even going to pretend to understand all the features &amp; possibilities that Open Transactions offers. </p>
<p>I read a bit about it and felt like I should take the short bus from now on. Baskets here, nyms there, Chaumian something or other... it frankly left my head swimming and I put it on my list of things to look into when I had more free time (and possibly a brain upgrade) to try and wrap my head around it.</p>
<p>But that doesn't stop me from realizing that OT is very powerful and can become extremely useful in the future.</p>
<p>So to claim this bounty we need you to provide an easy to use, open source, cross-platform client. Something my grandma (who thinks firefox is "the google", and "internets" her emails to me) would be able to use.</p>
<p>FellowTraveler has stated that the API is high-level &amp; easy to use, so anyone making a client really only needs to worry about the display layer. He recommends using C++ or Java since those are the best tested.</p>
<p>I simply haven't dug into OT enough to adequately make such judgements, so I will defer to FellowTraveler in this regard. If he says you have created such a client I will make good on my portion of the bounty.</p>
<p>Devs and testers are available in #opentransactions on FreeNode</p>
<p>You can read more about OT here: <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgdg">http://cur.lv/6cgdg</a></p>
<h2>BOUNTIES</h2>
<p>Obsi     -  100 BTC<br>
FellowTraveler   -  80 BTC<br>
da2ce7   -  some BTC<br>
Donations    -  5.2505 BTC<br></p>
<p>To further fund this bounty send bitcoins to :  166siuo8xaJQLKJRZTk9DFPympSA9CUWt4<br>
(Changed original address to a show a permanent one generated for this request by Rugatu)</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Rugatu</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 15:58:36 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How do you like Rugatu on facebook?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yt8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Our facebook page isn't too fancy but it definitely needs some love, so for every "like" you give we tip you here on Rugatu, only make sure you answer to this question. </p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/65yt9">Rugatu Q&amp;A Community on Facebook</a></p>
<p>Please tell us your suggestions on how to make it better too. Thanks and good luck!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Rugatu</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 16:20:35 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there a maximum factor by which difficulty can change?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011n]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I seem to recall, long ago, being told that difficulty couldn't change more than a certain amount at each retarget, but I can't seem to find what that factor is (or even confirmation that such a factor exists) no matter how hard I google. Does such a factor exist and if so what is its value?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>David Perry</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 00:49:54 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[In mining, we trust.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In mining we trust. On the side of the US $1 bill it says &ldquo;In God, we trust&rdquo;. Because money is all about trust. Trust that it&rsquo;s real, trust that it will remain at a similar value for the duration of the transaction at least, trust that the products are represented honestly. In the past trust that the paper was redeemable in gold, and more recently trust that our dollar will be backed by the &ldquo;full faith and credit of the US Government&rdquo;. And when that trust is lacking society shuts down. To some extent, the crisis of 2008, in the same manner as the one in 1929 was about the lack of trust. They called it &ldquo;counter party risk&rdquo;, [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7011o">In mining, we trust.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7011o"><img width="820" height="420" src="http://cur.lv/7011p" alt="bitcoin_logo_flat_coin_star_by_carbonism-d3h79mu-820x420"></a><p><span>In mining we trust.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">On the side of the US $1 bill it says &ldquo;In God, we trust&rdquo;. Because money is all about trust. Trust that it&rsquo;s real, trust that it will remain at a similar value for the duration of the transaction at least, trust that the products are represented honestly. In the past trust that the paper was redeemable in gold, and more recently trust that our dollar will be backed by the &ldquo;full faith and credit of the US Government&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And when that trust is lacking society shuts down. To some extent, the crisis of 2008, in the same manner as the one in 1929 was about the lack of trust. They called it &ldquo;counter party risk&rdquo;, but it basically means: &ldquo;Do I trust that the other side of the contract will be honored when the time comes?&rdquo; When there is not trust, markets freeze.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And let&rsquo;s be honest, our trust in government, in markets, in society in general has been shaken over the last few years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is precisely TRUST that makes Bitcoin, and specifically mining in Bitcoin, so world changing. Remember, Bitcoin is not just a virtual currency. It is a &ldquo;public, trusted, distributed transaction ledger&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Public because we can all see the transactions. The block chain is open for anyone to inspect. Every transaction is recorded and available for public view. We ALL know what was sold and for how much, even if not necessarily to whom.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Trusted because it is mathematically very difficult, almost impossible, to fake the data. That is very, very important because it means the ledger can be relied on. We can trust it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Distributed, because no one single entity can modify the ledger data. No-one can cheat. Again, trust.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That means that the data in the ledger can&rsquo;t be faked. It is in other words &ldquo;TRUSTED&rdquo;. Mathematically TRUSTED. Cryptographically TRUSTED. And so, socially trusted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And remember, it&rsquo;s a &ldquo;ledger&rdquo;. A &ldquo;TRUSTED ledger&rdquo;. A ledger we, as a society, can all agree on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now think about how MANY ledgers are out there. You run into them every day, many times a day. The checkout counter for your coffee? A ledger. Taxes you will pay later in the year? Ledger. Election results? Ledger. Company balance sheet? Ledger. Stock market? Big ledger&hellip; And so on&hellip;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Right now we don&rsquo;t really trust these ledgers. That&rsquo;s why we have audits, and spot checks, and back office settlement. How much money does the NYSE spend on &ldquo;back room clearing&rdquo;, the matching process that allocates buyers and sellers to each transaction at the end of the day? Billions. &nbsp;And at the end not really &ldquo;TRUSTED&rdquo;. How much do we all spend every year on tax filings? And our taxes are often wrong and take a lot of work to figure out.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, and alts, solve this problem. By creating and maintaining these &ldquo;public transaction ledgers&rdquo;, we can increase trust in government and in our society, and drastically reduce transaction costs. More importantly we can, for the first time, have total transparency of our institutions and REALLY know what they&rsquo;re doing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Imagine: the 2000 election result battle? Solved. Just tally up the electronic register. It&rsquo;s TRUSTED. MERS, the Mortgage Electronic Registry System, the culprit behind so many bad foreclosures? Follow the transactions. TRUSTED. NYSE back office settlement? Yep, that too. How about annual company audits? How about tax filing? Yep. A TRUSTED register allows for all of these issues to be resolved. But the trick is TRUSTED.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So how do we know that it&rsquo;s &ldquo;TRUSTED&rdquo;. I mean, can we REALLY know?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Well, that actually is the reason that Bitcoin works. Because we can. While the details of the process are a bit too technical for this article, the details are available. Bitcoin is after all an &ldquo;open source&rdquo; protocol.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And as you dig into those details, as I, and many others, have, you find that we can really TRUST the ledger. The ledger allows for the kind of verification that Ronald Reagan talked about when he said &ldquo;we trust, but verify&rdquo;. (As a side note, it&rsquo;s interesting that Ronald Reagan got that from a Russian Proverb.)</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is mining that provides that trust. Mining, as an activity allows for many different miners and mining machines to cryptographically coordinate, verify and agree upon the transaction ledger. This, under most conditions, protects the ledger from external modification.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Under most conditions&rdquo;. Pretty good legalese, huh? The process fails when any one entity (or combination of entities) can control 51% of the hashing power. This is called the 51% attack. If you control most of the hashing power, you can change the ledger and force the rest of the system to agree with you. You can compromise the TRUST of the ledger.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The solution to THIS problem is the &ldquo;distributed&rdquo; component of the mining process. A company or government that maintains its own ledger cannot be trusted. But if it is maintained by many other entities, ones not associated with the user of the ledger, it can. The trick of course, as outlined above, is that no ONE entity, or collusion of entities can own more than 51% of the hashing power.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So under the right conditions, where mining is done by the public, and where mining is distributed into small pools with many different players, the Bitcoin &ldquo;public transaction ledger&rdquo; really CAN be TRUSTED, but only if they are &ldquo;mined&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In MINING we TRUST.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7011o">In mining, we trust.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>David Mondrus</author>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Greater Promise of a Blockchain]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is dead! It must be true, Reuters told me. Charlie Stross will be pleased. The party&rsquo;s over. Everyone go home. It&rsquo;s time for some quiet reflection. Wait a minute. Bitcoin&rsquo;s not dead. Hold on. How does a computer protocol die anyway? The viability of http://cur.lv/68b0c it&rsquo;s a debate that seems to go on forever. It may be difficult to comprehend, but out there in cyberspace are places where Bitcoin is still a curiosity. There, this technology is superficially considered and routinely dismissed. What is being overlooked? Detractors will often tell you that money needs government. They&rsquo;ll remind you of tulips and speculative manias. They seek to distract. Long-winded diatribes on the history of money are commonplace. Readers are taken [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7011q">The Greater Promise of a Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7011q"><img width="1024" height="496" src="http://cur.lv/7011r" alt="bowling copy"></a><p><a href="http://cur.lv/7011s">Bitcoin is dead!</a> It must be true, Reuters told me. <a href="http://cur.lv/68b9d">Charlie Stross</a> will be pleased. The party&rsquo;s over. Everyone go home. It&rsquo;s time for some quiet reflection.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Wait a minute. Bitcoin&rsquo;s not dead. Hold on. How does a computer protocol die anyway?</p>
<p dir="ltr">The viability of http://cur.lv/68b0c it&rsquo;s a debate that seems to go on forever. It may be difficult to comprehend, but out there in cyberspace are places where Bitcoin is still a curiosity. There, this technology is superficially considered and routinely dismissed. What is being overlooked?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Detractors will often tell you that money needs government. They&rsquo;ll remind you of tulips and speculative manias. They seek to distract. Long-winded diatribes on the history of money are commonplace. Readers are taken on pointless journeys through antiquity. The most obscure historical references are routinely cited.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ignore the arguments for a moment. Instead, observe the humans making them.</p>
<p dir="ltr">You will necessarily find the most near-sighted of creatures: the economic analyst. The technology communities of the world are already <a href="http://cur.lv/7011t">committing</a>. For them Bitcoin is a no-brainer. It&rsquo;s their job to spot disruptive technology.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is key. Bitcoin is a technological innovation: purely disruptive in form and function. Arguments by economists that ignore the technology are worthless.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those with the loudest digital voices continue to produce the most noise: failing to engage the technical. Perhaps this can be forgiven. With only a casual glance Bitcoin could seem full of bizarre phenomenon.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But really, what does it take to think? Shouldn&rsquo;t complete analysis precede grandstanding? Maybe then we could all be spared the mind-numbing horror of another diatribe about tulips.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is an idea expressed in the language of mathematics. Its time has come. To analyse it as only a monetary phenomenon will lead you down the garden path.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fundamentally Bitcoin is a solution to a long-standing computing network problem.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The Problem of Byzantine Generals</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is, first and foremost, a ledger. The units of account are earned onto the ledger. The ledger is the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The computing problem is that, given a large group of users, each will want to create a false ledger entry, assigning themselves more units. Before Bitcoin a central party was the only solution. However a central point of failure is best avoided.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Byzantine generals problem uses an allegory to explain. Some generals and their respective armies are outside a city. They want to invade. They know that if at least half of them attack at the same time they&rsquo;ll win. But they must attack at the same time. If not, they&rsquo;ll lose. They can only co-ordinate via messages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Treachery is possible and some generals may send fake messages. How to know if a message is true? Faced with potential dishonesty, how can such a large and disparate group co-ordinate the time for attack?</p>
<p dir="ltr">The solution: attach a cost to sending the message and ensure, through the network, that only one general can send a message at a time. The cost is a proof-of-work scheme. And eureka, we&lsquo;ve finally found it. A message cannot be faked: it will not contain the math solution needed to authenticate it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A dishonest general can only succeed if the majority of the generals collude with him. This is unlikely. The system rewards generals for their resource intensive math work in maintaining the system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Voila, a time-stamped, cryptographic-ledger, distributed over a decentralised peer-to-peer network: a technological marvel that can&rsquo;t go away. To dismiss it is foolhardy. The implications are too far-reaching.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The Future Applications of a Blockchain.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Economic analysts are obviously preoccupied: tulips or Beanie Babies for this article guys? It&rsquo;s heady work. Nevertheless innovation continues in earnest. Behind the scenes we&rsquo;re really starting to hit hyper-drive.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those with vision and understanding are taking this technology and building things, amazing things: tools and protocol layers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Our future is clear. In this strange world of decentralized networks, agents will interact with each other intimately and directly, from afar, for everything. At the core of all these networks will be a blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All internet-based trusted third parties are now redundant. The corporate dead walk among us. The network is its own autonomous entity for achieving consensus.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For an economic analyst like <a href="http://cur.lv/7011s">Mr Edward Hadas</a>, for example, perhaps the ultimate proof of just how unsettling a blockchain will be are &lsquo;coloured coins&rsquo;. Here the units of account on a given blockchain are tied directly to the shares issued in a company (as an asset example).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Take a given quantity of Bitcoin, tie them to a given quantity of shares in a company and let them move around the ledger.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the blockchain agrees on asset ownership through time and transferring that ownership is trivial then there is no need for expensive stock exchanges. Assets like company shares become so liquid that they could be used in any transaction, person-to-person.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin enthusiasts are conservative revolutionaries. But the possibilities are truly endless and the mind often boggles.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One further example for the economically minded: Decentralised Autonomous Corporations (DACs). &nbsp;For a full analysis of a DAC see <a href="http://cur.lv/7011u">Vitalik Buterin&rsquo;s article on bootstrapping a DAC.</a> Essentially this is a network of economic agents interacting with each other according to rules allowed for by a common protocol. It is a decentralised company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is often described as the world&rsquo;s first DAC. A common protocol (business rules) underpins a network of users who contribute their land, labour, capital and enterprise (factors of production) to providing value (the network and ancillary services).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The DAC rewards economic agents by assigning them units of account on the ledger. The network is its own ecosystem and actors can be thought of as bootstrapping an economy. DACs can take a variety of forms but the blockchain is always at the core. In every case the community self-organizes and hierarchy becomes redundant.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Societal Implications: A Greater Vision.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain is the heartbeat of a new decentralised organism. This creature will completely reshape society in its own image.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This should be embraced. Our society is too complex to manage centrally. But even if this is ignored, it will not matter. This change is inevitable. The industrial age necessitated hierarchy: monolithic centres of power exercising inordinate amounts of control. Our information age does not.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hierarchy limits freedom and causes irrational economic behaviour. It stifles the human spirit and distorts natural market mechanisms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Bitcoin&rsquo;s blockchain all manner of mutually agreed, decentralised relations are possible, at distance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This new flattened society will be based on mutual contracts made possible by a blockchain. Deposit, escrow, dispute mediation, insurance, trading and micro-transactions are all possible with this technology and the costs are negligible. Property can be both registered and transferred through the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Let&rsquo;s see a tulip or a Beanie Baby do that.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>(Inspired in no small part by the vision of Andreas Antonopoulos and the ignorance of Edward Hadas).&nbsp;</em><a href="http://cur.lv/7011v"><br></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7011q">The Greater Promise of a Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Tristan Winters</author>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Biggs’ Bitcoin Bunk]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011w]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>John Biggs has a writing problem. It&rsquo;s terrible. I too know manias. I see them most often among writers who have a mania for writing even when they have nothing to say. Such is the case with John Biggs&rsquo; recent Bitcoin&rsquo;s Image Problem. First off, Bitcoin&rsquo;s image problem is evident to anyone watching the mainstream media&rsquo;s portrayal of BTC as the domain of drug dealers and terrorists, despite all the evidence to the contrary. Bitcoin&rsquo;s image problem is one fabricated by writers like Mr. Biggs. But let&rsquo;s look at his obvious blunders. Writing students, pay attention. He claims &ldquo;Its followers see themselves as freedom fighters, attacking outsiders with vengeance and talking up their own accomplishments in the language of the [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7011w">Biggs&rsquo; Bitcoin Bunk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7011w"><img width="620" height="375" src="http://cur.lv/7011x" alt="bunk-21"></a><p dir="ltr">John Biggs has a writing problem. It&rsquo;s terrible.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I too know manias. I see them most often among writers who have a mania for writing even when they have nothing to say. Such is the case with John Biggs&rsquo; recent <a href="http://cur.lv/7011y">Bitcoin&rsquo;s Image Problem</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">First off, Bitcoin&rsquo;s image problem is evident to anyone watching the mainstream media&rsquo;s portrayal of BTC as the domain of drug dealers and terrorists, despite all the evidence to the contrary. Bitcoin&rsquo;s image problem is one fabricated by writers like Mr. Biggs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But let&rsquo;s look at his obvious blunders. Writing students, pay attention. He claims &ldquo;<em>Its followers see themselves as freedom fighters, attacking outsiders with vengeance and talking up their own accomplishments in the language of the already victorious.</em>&ldquo; This sentence is an assertion made without evidence, and one that ascribes a universal characteristic (<em>freedom fighters, attacking outsiders with vengeance</em>, etc&hellip;) to the whole of the Bitcoin user base without differentiation. Having just attended nearly every workshop and panel of the North American Bitcoin Conference on Miami Beach, I can assure you that freedom fighters, or even those claiming to be freedom fighters were scarcely to be found. And just to establish some kind of credibility here, having worked in South Africa on behalf of the ANC, I know a freedom fighter when I see one.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is true that among some outliers in the Bitcoin community (and I do not mean any pejorative by the word outlier), one may find the overheated rhetoric of anarchists and radical libertarians. What else is new? One can hear them at any time of day on almost any subject across the radio airwaves and in the comments section of every local newspaper. No one mistakes the tin foil hats for the majority&rsquo;s sensible headgear.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Biggs really goes off the rails with statements like &ldquo;<em>These incremental hoots make it seem like bitcoin is growing. It isn&rsquo;t, at least not in a global sense.</em>&rdquo; To say that Bitcoin adoption is not growing on a global scale ignores the facts of what we see all around us. Ask them at Tiger Direct. Perhaps Biggs would like to say that climate change is not happening either.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And let&rsquo;s look at this one: &ldquo;<em>There is no impetus for the average user to dump money into an unregulated system that appears as volatile as the currency of some banana republic run by a capricious dictator.</em>&rdquo; Funny, Latin America is where we find enormous demand for the services that Bitcoin can provide. And I would suggest Mr. Biggs drop his ever-so-gringo caricatures of our neighbors to the south.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Finally, bitcoin users are seen as misogynistic and sexist.</em>&rdquo; That&rsquo;s a handy slur. The presentation by Elizabeth Ploshay on the subject of Bitcoin and its potential for the empowerment of women at the Miami conference was one of the best attended and most lively. Not one sexist remark from the audience. Not a hoot or a whistle or a wolf-call. Should conventions such as these adopt non-harassment policies? Of course. So should every business conference in the world. (&ldquo;<em>TechCrunch learned far too late</em>&rdquo;) &nbsp;It wasn&rsquo;t Bitcoin conferences that prompted the formulation of those guidelines, they were prompted by a historically discriminatory business environment. To suggest that Bitcoin users are any more misogynistic and sexist than any other group is transparently misleading, especially as no evidence is offered.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Unlike the Internet, there is no clear way forward, no use case that the average user will accept as valid.</em>&rdquo; Really, Mr. Biggs. You must not have been around in the early days of the internet, as I was. There was no clear way forward then either.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But perhaps you haven&rsquo;t read in the history books about that time that the driving economy of the early internet, as it was with the VCR, was pornography. This inconvenient little truth kind of puts your moralistic little tome in perspective. It&rsquo;s just silly, the product of yet another immature writer with a mania for writing. Here&rsquo;s a suggestion from Creative Writing 101. Write What You Know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7011w">Biggs&rsquo; Bitcoin Bunk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Stephen Malagodi</author>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining with HashPlex]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/70120]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR We at HashPlex are building a new kind of datacenter designed from the ground up for bitcoin miners. Our prices have already set a market low at $99/kw-month, and our services and automation will set a new industry standard (we provide space, power, cooling, internet, and automated miner management). We&rsquo;re on track to have our first HashCenter in Q2 of 2014, and we will be opening limited availability in our interim space in a few weeks. We&rsquo;re accepting reservations for space in our HashCenters at http://cur.lv/70121. We pledge to forever remain a positive force in a vibrant, decentralized bitcoin mining community. Come check us out! Our Genesis HashPlex was a glimmer in my eye (some might say a tear) [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/70120">Bitcoin Mining with HashPlex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/70120"><img width="700" height="211" src="http://cur.lv/70122" alt="hashplex_logo_black_transparent_horiz_700w2"></a><h2>TLDR</h2>
<p dir="ltr">We at HashPlex are building a new kind of datacenter designed from the ground up for bitcoin miners. Our prices have already set a market low at $99/kw-month, and our services and automation will set a new industry standard (we provide space, power, cooling, internet, and automated miner management). We&rsquo;re on track to have our first HashCenter in Q2 of 2014, and we will be opening limited availability in our interim space in a few weeks. We&rsquo;re accepting reservations for space in our HashCenters at <a href="http://cur.lv/70123">http://cur.lv/70121</a>. We pledge to forever remain a positive force in a vibrant, decentralized bitcoin mining community. Come check us out!</p>
<h2>Our Genesis</h2>
<p dir="ltr">HashPlex was a glimmer in my eye (some might say a tear) while setting up various bitcoin miners (mostly BFL and KNC) as they arrived.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Couldn&rsquo;t this be easier?&rdquo; I asked myself, exhaling mumbled expletives through acidic, cold-press-infused spittle. I had quickly exhausted all the power in my apartment and my sister&rsquo;s garage, and I was looking for more. I had what I thought was a great setup: several raspberry pi&rsquo;s running ArchLinux with a simple cron for cgminer. Gradually I learned just how far from automated this setup was. CGMiner would segfault, my raspberry pi&rsquo;s would crash, my GFIs would trip from bad power supplies. With my girlfriend&rsquo;s various pained expressions weighing on my mind as our electrical panel buzzed like a pack of Asian hornets, I remembered the old adage, &ldquo;some find opportunity in adversity.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I went looking for larger venues to put my miners. &ldquo;You want how many amps!?&rdquo; was a common response from leasing agents. Even those that did have the electrical capacity had nothing near my required thermal capacity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I went looking at datacenter space. Certainly they must have solved this problem. Oh, they had solved it (in the most inelegant, massively brute-force way possible), and boy would I pay for it out the nose. At the end of the day, even if I paid their exorbitant rates, I still didn&rsquo;t receive any automated miner management.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I went to my friends and described our opportunity to build HashPlex. They were excited (a rarity for my ideas).</p>
<h2>The Pitch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">We&rsquo;re offering full-service miner hosting at a 2-3x discount of what&rsquo;s on the market, and we provide all the services not typically provided by the other guys. Our entry-level plan is $99/kw-month, and we drop to $89/kw-month if you can bring us 30kw or more of mining power. How many gigahashes is that? Here&rsquo;s a handy lookup table:</p>
<p>Butterfly Labs Mini-Rig: 0.5TH/s, ~2.2kw &rarr; $297 / month<br>
KNC Miner Jupiter: 0.55TH/s, ~600w &rarr; $99 / month<br>
Coincraft Rig: 2.8TH/s, ~3kw &rarr; $297 / month<br>
Cointerra TerraMiner IV: 2TH/s, ~1.5kw &rarr; $198 / month<br>
HashFast Sierra: 1.2TH/s, ~800w &rarr; $99 / month<br>
BlackArrow Prospero X-3 (@1.56GHz): 2TH/s, ~1kw &rarr; $99 / month</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Our $99/kw-month rate comes out to a price of ~$0.1375 / kw-hour (and that includes power, internet, space, cooling, security, and automated management). Many miners pay more than that for power alone while mining at home. Do you have a solution for security at home? Will you have enough cooling when the summer months come? Are you tired of worrying about miners crashing while you&rsquo;re on a trip? We at HashPlex pledge to be a ship-it-and-forget-it solution for the rest of the life of your miner.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">How do we do it? We could never offer you this service and pricing while leasing existing spaces. Our custom HashCenters will enable new, unrivaled levels of productivity per dollar.</p>
<h2>Who We Are</h2>
<p dir="ltr">I&rsquo;m Bernie, the founder and CEO of HashPlex. I studied Electrical Engineering at Stanford through 2009. I&rsquo;ve worked at Better Place, Apple Computer, and Microsoft (where I spent my last 4 years).</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/70124"><img alt="Bernie Rihn, Founder, CEO at hashplex.com " src="http://cur.lv/70124" width="500" height="541"></a><p>Bernie Rihn, Founder, CEO at hashplex.com</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">While at Microsoft I helped with the video-input-processor and ambient light cancellation algorithm in Sensor-In-Pixel based Samsung LCDs which went into Micosoft PixelSense. I later tinkered on a few small inventions and worked on bringing an accessory for Microsoft Surface (the tablet) out of the labs while in the Microsoft Applied Sciences group.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I met Jason Prado (Advisor, SW Chief) at Stanford in the LaIR, a space for entry-level CS students to work and get help. Though not on duty, he volunteered answers to my questions all while his hands furiously thwacked the keyboard of a 12&rdquo; PowerBook G4 in their own self-governed other-world of LateX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">cmd-tab &hellip; thwack-click-click-click &hellip; cmd-tab, compile &hellip; cmd-tab</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;So you see&rdquo; &hellip; &ldquo;when you reach&rdquo; &hellip; &ldquo;the end&rdquo; &hellip; &ldquo;of a linked-list&rdquo;</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/70125"><img title="Jason Prado" alt="Jason Prado" src="http://cur.lv/70125" width="500" height="598"></a><p>Jason Prado</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">Jason would go on to work at Meebo, Apture, Microsoft, Plannr (acquired by Google), Google, and Facebook.</p>
<p dir="ltr">John Stockdale (Advisor, HW Chief) and I met during Stanford&rsquo;s prospective freshman weekend. We both ran our own FTP servers and drooled over cars and computers. That weekend John took me to a (then mystical) burger place called &ldquo;In-N-Out&rdquo; in a Mitsubishi Evolution tuned to run on race gas. Both have had remarkable staying power in my still boyish subconscious.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/70126"><img alt="John Stockdale" src="http://cur.lv/70126" width="500" height="397"></a><p>John Stockdale</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">After graduating, John went on to VW Research, Videosurf (acquired by Microsoft), and Facebook to work on their Open Compute Project. John is now an active angel investor, skydiver, and hacker of all kinds.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/70127"><img alt="George Schnurle" src="http://cur.lv/70128" width="444" height="620"></a><p>George Schnurle</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">George Schnurle (VP Engineering) and I met through Jason in 2010. Shocked that somehow we had not crossed paths during school, we immediately hit it off, discussing our various clever mechanical inventions and apparati (both real and serial-day-dreamt). We&rsquo;ve been burner &amp; engineering buds ever since. George has done mechanical engineering for SLAC, WhereNet, and Paramit.</p>
<h2>Why We&rsquo;re A Great, Positive Force For The Network</h2>
<p dir="ltr">We at HashPlex want to re-empower entry-level miners and help maintain healthy decentralization in the network. Sure, the era of GPU mining (for bitcoin) is forever gone, but the era of ASIC mining is actually still very young. Companies like CEX.IO have massive, centralized hashing power that is mining for a single pool. At HashPlex, customers will always have a choice for what pool they use, and they will always be given all available facilities to participate in the network in the manner that they would like.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Interested in hosting / partnering / working with us? <a href="mailto:contact@hashplex.com" target="_blank"><strong>Drop us a line.</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/70120">Bitcoin Mining with HashPlex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bernie Rihn</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>