<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://cur.lv/5xyoe">
<channel>
  <title>RSSMix.com Mix ID 3845704</title>
  <generator>RSSMix</generator>
  <link>http://cur.lv/65yf1</link>
  <description>This feed was created by mixing existing feeds from various sources.</description>
  <language>en-gb</language>
  
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: &amp;#1059;&amp;#1082;&amp;#1088;&amp;#1072;&amp;#1080;&amp;#1085;&amp;#1072;]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqve]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvf">Quote from: maza5 on <b>Today</b> at 05:03:31 AM</a></div><div>&#1058;&#1077;&#1087;&#1077;&#1088;&#1100; &nbsp;&#1079;&#1072;&#1076;&#1072;&#1095;&#1072; &#1085;&#1072;&#1081;&#1090;&#1080; &#1086;&#1073;&#1080;&#1078;&#1077;&#1085;&#1085;&#1099;&#1093; &#1088;&#1091;&#1089;&#1089;&#1082;&#1080;&#1093; &#1085;&#1072; &#1090;&#1077;&#1088;&#1088;&#1080;&#1090;&#1086;&#1088;&#1080;&#1080; &#1059;&#1082;&#1088;&#1072;&#1080;&#1085;&#1099; &#1091;&#1089;&#1083;&#1086;&#1078;&#1085;&#1103;&#1077;&#1090;&#1089;&#1103; &nbsp;<img src="http://cur.lv/65yf8" alt="Wink" border="0"><br></div>&#1042;&#1080;&#1076;&#1077;&#1083;&#1080; &#1074; &#1089;&#1087;&#1080;&#1089;&#1082;&#1077; &#1093;&#1086;&#1090;&#1100; &#1086;&#1076;&#1085;&#1091; &#1088;&#1091;&#1089;&#1089;&#1082;&#1091;&#1102; &#1092;&#1072;&#1084;&#1080;&#1083;&#1080;&#1102;?&nbsp; <img src="http://cur.lv/7twrv" alt="Grin" border="0">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 05:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [GUIDE] GridSeed Miner Support/Tuning]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[my hash is up to 448.<br><br>&nbsp;&nbsp;so what should it do &nbsp; 400kh at freq 800]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 05:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Russia occupies the Ukrainian lands.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Hello! I live in Ukraine Crimea. Russian army occupied our land. We believe in freedom and integrity of our state . We need any help to organize people and strong points with free medicine and food. Ukraine mobilizes troops about all our achievements w...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 05:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [ANN][GRA] Graincoin - New PoW/PoS coin | Fast, secure | Version 1.5 Released!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Sorry guys but I just had to dump over a million GRA.<br><br>This piece of shit exchange COINEDUP won't give me my money. <br><br>I've sent in tickets, they ignored them.<br><br>I posted on their subreddit, they deleted it!<br><br>I made a thread here complaining about <b>how bad...</b>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 05:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: A List of Quality Questions for MT.Gox to Answer]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Non-stupid questions to ask:<br><br>* What is the case number in the Tokyo District Court?<br>* What is the name and business address of the supervisor appointed by the Court?<br>* Do you in the call center work for Mt. Gox, the Tokyo District Court, or some other ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 05:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Mark "apparently leaked" conversation with a bank in japanese - Any translator to confirm?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvl"> cokea </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvm">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvk">[23 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 04:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Peter Vessenes and Jon Matonis To Resign at the Bitcoin Foundation]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvn"><img src="http://cur.lv/7d5fd" alt="Peter Vessenes and Jon Matonis To Resign at the Bitcoin Foundation" title="Peter Vessenes and Jon Matonis To Resign at the Bitcoin Foundation"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvo"> bitpotluck </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvp">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvn">[11 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 04:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[SovereignBTC #5 – Gox is Dead, Bitcoin is Thriving]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>SovereignBTC</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 04:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[bitcoin grant entities?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>recently found a remarkable wired article[1] that mentions a rather secretive entity <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvs" rel="nofollow">"Bitcoin grant"</a> that provides bitcoin grants to open source projects, generally bitcoin related.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>looking for info on any other bitcoin grant agencies...?</p>
</blockquote>

<p>also, similarly, is there any <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvt" rel="nofollow">kickstarter</a>-like entity related to funding projects in bitcoins? are there bitcoin-related kickstarter projects? from other question here have heard of at least 2 bitcoin stock exchanges, but those appear to be for companies that are attempting to generate revenue/profit/dividends etc.</p>

<p>[1] <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvu" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin santas drop big money on hackers who have been nice</a> wired</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>vzn</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 04:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[New to bitmessage, Had some questions]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>So i read about it, figured i'd try it, Why not, right? </p> <ul><li><p>So kinda curious in general what's it about, how does it compare to IM or e-mail (besides the more obvious differences i've seen already playing around shooting a test message to myself and the Echo bot)</p></li> <li><p>Anybody cool using the Broadcast features as a replacement for something like 'tweeting'</p></li> <li><p>Any other cool use cases out there?</p></li> <li><p>Also wouldn't mind some tips...</p></li> </ul><p>(I'm BM-2cTy8HhC5AnQYfFbUik9jquo7Dh5XGQUxy btw <em>For now</em>)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvw"> speewave </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvv">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 04:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to store Bitcoin values in a MySQL database? floats are bad.... right?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>What should I be using to store the values of a wallet in a MySQL database?</p>

<p>Apparently floats are too imprecise to be storing Bitcoins, especially down to the satoshi.</p>

<p>So what should I be using? Decimal ?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Wannabee Bitcoin Dev</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 03:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[You got goxed]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqvz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvz"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqw0" alt="You got goxed" title="You got goxed"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7uv2f"> Prominence19 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw1">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqvz">[7 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How is “days destroyed” different from “amount of BTC” in existence?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqw2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>According to <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw3" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7wqw3</a> , if I have 100 BTC for seven days and then spend them, that&rsquo;s 700 days destroyed.</p>

<p>But if I didn't have them, someone else would have them.  So how does the metric differ from the amount of BTC that exists?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Wes Groleau</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 02:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Feel the power? Another Tesla bought with bitcoin!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqw4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw4"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqw5" alt="Feel the power? Another Tesla bought with bitcoin!" title="Feel the power? Another Tesla bought with bitcoin!"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw6"> AmpEater </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw7">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw4">[57 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 02:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Interpreting the Recent FinCEN Rulings on Virtual Currencies]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqw8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This article is a review of the current FinCEN administrative rulings as they apply to the use of virtual currencies in the United States. &nbsp;FinCEN first started contemplating virtual currencies in March 2013 when they released FIN-2013-G001. &nbsp;Their original ruling did not consider users of virtual currencies to be dealers in foreign exchange, which was a positive outcome because being a dealer in foreign exchange brings with it significant compliance requirements. &nbsp;There was, however, one paragraph in FIN-2013-G001 that was both unexpected and problematic. In section c., FIN-2013-G001 read: &ldquo;A person that creates units of this convertible virtual currency and uses it to purchase real or virtual goods and services is a user of the convertible virtual currency and not [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wqw8">Interpreting the Recent FinCEN Rulings on Virtual Currencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw8"><img width="1024" height="672" src="http://cur.lv/75g2i" alt="bitcoin11"></a><p dir="ltr">This article is a review of the current FinCEN administrative rulings as they apply to the use of virtual currencies in the United States. &nbsp;FinCEN first started contemplating virtual currencies in March 2013 when they released FIN-2013-G001. &nbsp;Their original ruling did not consider users of virtual currencies to be dealers in foreign exchange, which was a positive outcome because being a dealer in foreign exchange brings with it significant compliance requirements. &nbsp;There was, however, one paragraph in FIN-2013-G001 that was both unexpected and problematic. In section c., FIN-2013-G001 read:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>&ldquo;A person that creates units of this convertible virtual currency and uses it to purchase real or virtual goods and services is a user of the convertible virtual currency and not subject to regulation as a money transmitter. By contrast, a person that creates units of convertible virtual currency and sells those units to another person for real currency or its equivalent is engaged in transmission to another location and is a money transmitter.&rdquo;[1]</strong></em></p>
<p>A plain reading of this language could only lead one to conclude that a miner who creates virtual currency and sells it to another person is acting as a money transmitter. &nbsp;Fortunately, this problem seems to have been resolved by the recent &ldquo;Atlantic City Bitcoin Ruling&rdquo;, which has now been formally published by FinCEN as FIN-2014-R001. &nbsp;This new ruling supersedes the earlier one:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>&ldquo;To the extent that a user mines Bitcoin and uses the Bitcoin solely for the user&rsquo;s own purposes and not for the benefit of another, the user is not an MSB under FinCEN&rsquo;s regulations, because these activities involve neither &ldquo;acceptance&rdquo; nor &ldquo;transmission&rdquo; of the convertible virtual currency and are not the transmission of funds within the meaning of the Rule. &nbsp;This is the case whether &hellip; the user is purchasing goods or services for the user&rsquo;s own use, paying debts previously incurred in the ordinary course of business, or (in the case of a corporate user) making distributions to shareholders.&rdquo;[2]</strong></em></p>
<p>The above paragraph is significant. &nbsp;It says that, so long as a user is &ldquo;using Bitcoin&rdquo; (i.e., selling it) for their own purposes, then they are not engaged in money transmission and are not considered to be a money transmitter (and do not need to register as an MSB under FinCEN&rsquo;s regulations.) &nbsp;The paragraph even allows that a general partner who is mining on behalf of a limited partnership can make partnership distributions (whether in Bitcoin or in dollars) without being engaged in money transmission. &nbsp;There is, however, still a gray area here: it is not clear whether or not an agent who is mining Bitcoin for another user becomes a money transmitter by making a distribution to that user. &nbsp;The answer probably depends on the legal structure of their relationship. &nbsp;We hope that FinCEN addresses this question next because it affects many existing business models in our industry.</p>
<p>The Atlantic City Bitcoin Ruling was formally published by FinCEN on January 30th, 2014, along with another ruling, FIN-2014-R002[3]. &nbsp;The first ruling dealt with miners. &nbsp;The second applies the same sort of logic to traders. These rulings not only describe the conditions in which miners and traders might become money transmitters, they also apply themselves more broadly to all virtual currency users:</p>
<p><em><strong>&ldquo;How a user obtains a virtual currency &hellip; is not material to the legal characterization [of the user] under the BSA &hellip; What is material to the conclusion that a person is not an MSB is [the question of] what the person uses the convertible virtual currency for, and for whose benefit.&rdquo;[4]</strong></em></p>
<p>This is a positive result for the Bitcoin industry. &nbsp;Although we still have an incomplete picture of the regulatory landscape, we do know two things: &nbsp;1) So long as a person is buying or selling Bitcoin for their own benefit, they are not acting as a money transmitter, and 2) FinCEN is working hard to identify and address potential issues in our industry, and they will give you guidance if you ask for it. &nbsp;We encourage anybody who has questions about their own situation to contact FinCEN directly.</p>
<hr><p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>[1]<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqw9"> http://cur.lv/7wqw9</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">[2]<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwa"> http://cur.lv/7wqwa</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">[3]<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwb"> http://cur.lv/7wqwb</a></p>
<p>[4]<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwa"> http://cur.lv/7wqwa</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wqw8">Interpreting the Recent FinCEN Rulings on Virtual Currencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ryan Deming</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 02:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Most Popular Bar in Florida Accepts Bitcoin, $100k Sales in 3 Days]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwc"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqwd" alt="The Most Popular Bar in Florida Accepts Bitcoin, $100k Sales in 3 Days" title="The Most Popular Bar in Florida Accepts Bitcoin, $100k Sales in 3 Days"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwe"> SethOtterstad </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwf">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwc">[21 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 01:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BTC-e is now the BIGGEST systemic risk to Bitcoin!!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>BTC-e.com is now a close second on Bitcoincharts after Bitstamp in trade volume. They are now BY FAR the biggest systemic risk to Bitcoin.</p> <p>From day one they have been the exchange of choice for the sellers of Silk Road and every other black market site. This is because they offer(ed) every withdrawal option possible up to any amount with ZERO identification needed. They had Liberty Reserve, PerfectMoney, Ucash and many other ID-free options.</p> <p>Bitstamp may have been used by buyers indirectly through BTCKing on SR, but BTC-e has been there for the sellers. So if Charlie Schrem was worth picking up at the airport by the US, you can imagine that the owners of BTC-e are MUCH higher on the wanted list.</p> <p>THAT IS WHY THE OWNERS ARE (TRYING TO BE) ANONYMOUS.</p> <p>They can be arrested anytime and face decades in prison for laundering many millions in drug money. Guess what happens to the hundreds of thousands of coins under their control?</p> <p>For Bitcoin's sake, normal people need to be turned away from them. Another top exchange going down would be a disaster and a huge set-back for Bitcoin.</p> <p>Those wanting to buy or sell should use a 2nd generation exchange without dirty hands. Those wanting to take a bet on the rate should use derivatives, same risk with a smaller deposit.</p> <p>ps. This is not about creating a panic bank-run or hurting their business. This is about getting the facts more into the open. BTC-e is a well run site compared to Mt.Gox, but the inherent risk is JUST AS BIG!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwh"> furchtbares </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwg">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwg">[142 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 01:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Do you really still recommend MtGox?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you think that you should remove MtGox from step 2 'Get Bitcoins'?</p>

<p>I think they filed BK the other day.</p>

<p>NO NEED TO ANSWER.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Phil</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 01:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Core developer gmaxwell speaks out against HashFast]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwk"> rmvaandr </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwl">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwj">[34 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 01:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MIM File - How to open a file with an .MIM extension]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvg3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[An MIM file is a Multi-Purpose Internet Mail Message File, developed by Internet Engineering Task Force. Learn what Mac, Windows, and Linux programs can open .MIM files.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Silent Circle (software) - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwm(software)]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Silent Circle is an encrypted communications firm providing secure multiplatform communication services for mobile devices, desktop and email. Launched October 16 ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[West Edmonton Mall in Canada has a brand new Bitcoin ATM, courtesy of BitNational!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwn"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqwo" alt="West Edmonton Mall in Canada has a brand new Bitcoin ATM, courtesy of BitNational!" title="West Edmonton Mall in Canada has a brand new Bitcoin ATM, courtesy of BitNational!"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwp"> FenrisJager </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwq">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwn">[30 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 23:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Latest from Andreas Antonopoulos: Failure is an Option]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwr"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqws" alt="Latest from Andreas Antonopoulos: Failure is an Option" title="Latest from Andreas Antonopoulos: Failure is an Option"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwt"> pdtmeiwn </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwr">[32 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 23:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MT Gox Call Center - Post your experiences here]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>MT Gox have entered the first stage of a "Civil Rehabilitation". A statement on their website today announced they are opening a call center at 10am Japan Time on 3rd March (1am GMT). I'll be dialling in at the opening time and sharing what I find here. I encourage others to do the same. I expect nothing more than a 'User Busy' dial tone but hope someone will get some info. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqww"> willdcc </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwv">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwv">[119 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 23:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Top /r/bitcoin posts for this week, with MtGox posts filtered out.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqwx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwy"> martypete </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwz">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwx">[13 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 23:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Singapore launched 6 Bitcoin ATMs last week, really awesome.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqx0]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx0"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqx1" alt="Singapore launched 6 Bitcoin ATMs last week, really awesome." title="Singapore launched 6 Bitcoin ATMs last week, really awesome."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx2"> ninjalong </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx0">[1 comment]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 23:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there a cudaminer difficulty parameter option]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqx4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I try to mine some btc using cudaminer on cex.io.
I'm using cudaminer for that. I have a lot 'low' rejected shares due to low difficulty (On the ghash.io they say the minimum stratum difficulty is 16).</p>

<p>I think my rejected shares is due to this difficulty but I dunno if I can change that on my side to avoid rejected shares.</p>

<p>Any idea?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>zeflex</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 22:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Failure is an option]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqx5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx5"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqws" alt="Failure is an option" title="Failure is an option"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx6"> rmeddy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqwu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx5">[32 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 22:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Peter R’s Theory on the Collapse of Mt. Gox]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqx7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p><strong>TL/DR: A young man had a secret. To keep it hidden, he kept digging until the hole was a billion dollars deep. This is a speculative tale of a great bitcoin theft from MtGox in 2011 and the efforts that this man undertook to fix it. The tale explains the bitcoin bear market of 2011, the explosive rally of 2013, delayed fiat withdrawals, malled transactions, and a bot named Willy.</strong></p> <p>&ldquo;<em>By the time you realize that real life has begun, you are already three moves in</em>.&rdquo;&mdash;Author unknown</p> <p>It was June 19, 2011. Mark, a 26 year-old young man&mdash;a boy really&mdash;was ecstatic. He had recently purchased MtGox&mdash;a small, online exchange for trading virtual tokens&mdash;and business was booming. These virtual tokens were called bitcoins and Mark loved them. </p> <p>Bitcoins were an obscure curiosity: a peer-to-peer electronic cash system that allowed users to store and exchange credits with any other user in the world, nearly instantly, and without the assistance of a third-party or the permission of an authority. All that was needed was a 78-digit secret number&mdash;a key if you will. </p> <p>In order for his customers to withdraw their bitcoins over the internet, MtGox stored some of these keys on its online server. The remaining keys were stored on USB drives and backed up on paper to prevent theft should the server be compromised. </p> <p>But theft was hardly a concern. In October of 2010, bitcoins were trading for $0.10 and the half a million bitcoins held by MtGox was worth only $50,000. But still Mark took precautions, diligently moving bitcoins to offline storage and leaving only what was necessary for customer withdrawals online. He truly wanted both his business and bitcoin to succeed. </p> <p>By April, the bitcoin price had risen to $1 and by June it had exploded to $30. Between June 1 and June 15, an additional one million bitcoins were sent to MtGox and immediately sold, crashing the price back to $10. It was a hectic time, with hundreds of customers needing help, visits from the FBI related to the Silk Road black market, and stress related to the recent market crash. Young Mark was becoming a victim of his own success: there simply wasn&rsquo;t enough time to get everything done. On this very day in June 2011, the keys to the recently-deposited 1,000,000 BTC were still sitting on his server. </p> <p>Later this day, a group of hackers gained access to MtGox servers and executed fake trades that the world could see, driving the nominal price of bitcoin near $0. Mark was frantic. He quickly regained control of the servers and learned the dark truth: the million bitcoins that had recently flooded in earlier that month were gone. Mark admitted publically to the hack, rewound the false trades, but kept the truth of the missing coins a secret. </p> <p>How could this 26-year old explain to his customers that he had lost their bitcoins? And if the world found out, would this kill the thing he loved so dearly? Would he go to jail? Or worse yet, would someone kill him? Mark decided that he would do what he thought was right: he would slowly earn back the lost bitcoin with MtGox trading fee profits and eventually make his customers whole again. He still had over 500,000 BTC left&mdash;he moved 424242.42424242 BTC between bitcoin addresses and convinced the community that MtGox was solvent. As long as withdrawals didn&rsquo;t exceed deposits over a long period of time, no one would ever find out the truth. Or so he thought.</p> <p>Meanwhile, the bitcoin thieves slowly mixed their coins with other coins, obfuscating the chain of ownership, and then re-selling these coins on MtGox using sock-puppet accounts. Mark tried to stop them, but there was no way he could know for sure which accounts were fraudulent&mdash;he even accused innocent people of bitcoin laundering. The constant selling of these stolen bitcoins drove the price down to $2 in November 2011. Mark faithfully used all of the MtGox profits to purchase coins back during this decline. But he would never use customer funds&mdash;that was a line he swore not to cross. </p> <p>The selling of these stolen bitcoins continued at a diminished rate over 2012, and Mark continually purchased coins using the MtGox trading fees. The bitcoin economy was growing and new exchanges were opening up across the world. His bitcoin reserves weren&rsquo;t building fast enough but the price of bitcoin kept rising (along with the dollar value of the missing bitcoins). He was worried that other exchanges would suck coins out of Gox and reveal his secret. He decided he needed to take decisive action: for the first time, he used customer funds to purchase real bitcoins. These large purchases by Mark further increased demand and ignited the great rally of spring 2013 when the bitcoin price shot from $20 to $266. Mark had reduced his liability in bitcoins, but in dollar terms the coins that were still missing were worth more than ever before. </p> <p>On May 15, 2013 the US Department of Homeland Security seized millions of dollars from the MtGox Dwolla bank account. MtGox dollar reserves were already depleted at this point, and with the recent seizure, Mark could no longer make good on customer withdrawals in US dollars. </p> <p>Under the guise of &ldquo;banking problems,&rdquo; MtGox slowed US dollar withdrawals to a trickle in the summer of 2013. Customers became increasingly worried and began to bid up the price of bitcoin on MtGox, as this was the only way to escape with their funds. MtGox had little fiat and very little bitcoins, but it learned one thing: as the price differential between Gox and BitStamp grew, the outwards flow of bitcoin slowed dramatically. </p> <p>And so Willy was born. Willy was a bot, discovered by Wall Observers from bitcointalk.org, who would consistently purchased bitcoins at regular intervals between November 2013 and February 2014. Evidence that Willy belonged to Mark was revealed when both web and API trading at Gox was disabled for a brief period of time, exposing Willy as the only one left buying. </p> <p>Willy served two purposes: he drove the price of bitcoin on the MtGox exchange high, thereby slowing and sometimes reversing the outward flow of real BTC, and he reduced the number of GoxBTC held by clients. Of course, this meant that Willy eventually became the owner of a huge number of GoxBTC (that were of course no longer backed by real BTC). </p> <p>By December, the situation at MtGox was grim. In a desperate attempt to attract more funds, Mark offered reduced trading fees under the guise of celebrating their 1,000,000th customer. This partially worked, but Mark knew it was too late. If MtGox collapsed, it must appear that he didn&rsquo;t know about the theft until now&mdash;for it was better to appear incompetent than criminal. </p> <p>It was time to cover his tracks.</p> <p>He purposely mixed immature coins into bitcoin withdrawals to delay the outward flow of coins, and later began malling his own transactions. He added the Gox malleability weakness not as a bug, but as a feature, so that it would seem plausible that outsiders had recently stolen the coins without his awareness. No coins were actually lost to malleability. </p> <p>The MtGox coin supply dwindled to 2,000 BTC and on February 7, 2014. He had no choice but to disable bitcoin withdrawals. The end was near. </p> <p>The problem Mark faced was that his customers had $150,000,000 credited to their accounts, yet the MtGox bank account only contained $38,000,000. He could blame the missing bitcoins on transaction malleability, but how could he explain where the fiat money went? </p> <p>He shifted Willy into reverse and cranked the throttle. Willy relentlessly dumped bitcoins into the open bids. The price fell further and further, eventually dropping well below the BitStamp price. But still not enough people were buying! He needed his customers to buy the GoxBTC. Willy kept dumping coins until finally the price dropped below $100. MtGox even acquired new USD bank wires from customers looking to purchase the cheap coins. By this time, the majority of Gox customers had converted their dollars into bitcoins. </p> <p>On February 28, 2014, Mt Gox filed for bankruptcy protection in Tokyo, reporting 6.5 billion yen in liabilities, 3.8 billion yen in assets, and 750,000 of customer bitcoins missing. Willy had failed to completely close the fiat solvency gap and Mark finally admitted to having lost the coins.</p> <p>Now we watch the rest of the story unfold. A story of how an oversight during a hectic period, an untimely theft, and an attempt to cover it up, lead to the greatest loss in the history of bitcoin. </p> <p>Cross-posted from: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx8">http://cur.lv/7wqx8</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx9"> Peter__R </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx7">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqx7">[57 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 22:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[For each new "Gox theory" you post, I'm gonna kill a puppy]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxa]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>A nice puppy.</p> <p>Don't do it.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxb"> libertariancommunist </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxa">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxa">[116 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin rule #1: Do not publish private keys]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxc"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqxd" alt="Bitcoin rule #1: Do not publish private keys" title="Bitcoin rule #1: Do not publish private keys"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kuzx"> idlestabilizer </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxe">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxc">[121 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How did transaction malleability/DDOS attacks allow an exchange's internal accounting system to get &quot;out of sync&quot;?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7d5dw" rel="nofollow">This Coindesk article</a> says that:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>&ldquo;So as transactions are being created, malformed/parallel transactions
  are also being created so as to create a fog of confusion over the
  entire network, which then affects almost every single implementation
  out there,&rdquo; he added.</p>
  
  <p>Antonopoulos went on to say that Blockchain.info&rsquo;s implementation is
  not affected, but some exchanges have been affected &ndash; their internal
  accounting systems are gradually going out of sync with the network.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>How does this getting out of sync occur? Here's my understanding; as a transaction is created, malicious users create hundreds of transactions in the network that are identical except for a mutated signature. The original transaction may or may not be confirmed because a mutated version may get confirmed in the blockchain first. </p>

<p>For example, Mt. Gox, which used an automated system to approve withdrawals (as the article states), would consider a withdrawal transaction approved before it was actually confirmed in the blockchain. Once a mutated version of that transaction was confirmed in the blockchain, Mt. Gox's accounting system had a problem because a transaction it assumed was confirmed (and therefore had already "lost" the Bitcoins for) wasn't actually confirmed.</p>

<p>Is my understanding correct?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Jacob</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BTC-e API clarifications]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Considering the trade information reported here: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxh" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7wqxh</a></p>

<ol><li><p>Do these refer to open orders, or to completed trades?  If this shows only completed trades, does the API offer a means to retrieve the open orders?</p></li>
<li><p>Each record has an 'amount' field.  Is this field always in USD for both bids and asks?</p></li>
</ol>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>wharevvs</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BTC-E - Is there an official limit on frequency of requests that can be made?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Does anyone know if there is an official limit on the number of requests that can be made to btc-e.com? I know bitstamp will ban your ip address if it detects more than 600 requests per 10 minutes. I checked the terms, FAQ, and knowledge base and searched briefly on google but did not find much.</p>

<p>Anybody with any experience on what is the highest acceptable frequency of requests that can be made?</p>

<p>Thanks!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user14076</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[South of the Border and Northward to Success]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has few entry points where regulation can really effect it, and exchanges is a major one. Hence, new Bitcoin exchanges are hard to come by.

<b>Hayden Gill</b> reports on a new exchange in Mexico, MeXBT, and how Bitcoin can once again transcend borders.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Hayden Gill</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b0c Truth Happens (a video to promote Bitcoin)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxk"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqxl" alt="http://cur.lv/68b0c Truth Happens (a video to promote Bitcoin)" title="http://cur.lv/68b0c Truth Happens (a video to promote Bitcoin)"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxm"> lysobit </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxn">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxk">[17 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 20:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[is there a point where bitcoin mining will not be profitable?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>a lot of news accounts are pointing out that bitcoin mining is getting more difficult over time, murch even said recently in chat its getting "exponentially harder". not sure if that is the case, but has anyone studied the economics and difficulty/hardness of bitcoin mining over spans of time? it appears clearly &amp; by design to be subject to <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxp" rel="nofollow">"diminishing marginal returns"</a>. </p>

<blockquote>
  <p>is there a forecast when bitcoin mining will reach "break-even" level &amp; be exactly as expensive as the hardware/energy required to mine it?</p>
</blockquote>

<p>looking for quantitative/scientific analysis where possible. by the way, its a completely separate question of whether this would mean that bitcoin is no longer usable as a currency. (to me that is very likely <em>not</em> the case.)</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>vzn</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 19:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Full example data for scrypt Stratum-client]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm trying to write a Mining client for Scrypt-based mining using Stratum Communication.
As of now, I have some trouble verifying all my bit orders and sequences. Hashes I'm generating get always rejected due to not meeting the Target.</p>

<p>What I'm looking for is a full sequence of data, starting from the information I get from the stratum server (coinbases, merkles,...) to a final hash.</p>

<p>I could already verify parts of the algorithm (mainly from input to a valid merkle-root, using the information of <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxr" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7wqxr</a> , and a scrypt hashing, using the block header from <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxs" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7wqxs</a> ), but I guess there is some endian problem in between, or something completely different, I don't know... With a full workflow I could verify where the error happens.</p>

<p>Does anyone know where to get such data, or how to generate them for myself?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>MatthiasB</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Anyone able to run Bitcoin-Qt 0.8.6 on Mac OSX 10.9.2?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I ran the Mavericks update today, putting me at 10.9.2 and now my Bitcoin-Qt stops responding after it notifies me that it is "verifying blocks". I am using it for ongoing research and am in a bad spot now. I realize I should have thought about the possible ramifications of running the update.</p>

<p>At any rate, is anyone able to get it to run? I've tried running it from the .dmg via the gui and via command line. I get the same results in both cases. As soon as it goes to verify blocks, it stops responding.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Spike</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Gamblers wager billions (between 50 and 60 percent of all BTC transactions) on unregulated Bitcoin betting sites | “This is absolutely revolutionary, and isn’t being done by any billion dollar casino in Vegas,” – Eric Vorhees]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxu]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxu"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqxv" alt="Gamblers wager billions (between 50 and 60 percent of all BTC transactions) on unregulated Bitcoin betting sites | &ldquo;This is absolutely revolutionary, and isn&rsquo;t being done by any billion dollar casino in Vegas,&rdquo; &ndash; Eric Vorhees" title="Gamblers wager billions (between 50 and 60 percent of all BTC transactions) on unregulated Bitcoin betting sites | &ldquo;This is absolutely revolutionary, and isn&rsquo;t being done by any billion dollar casino in Vegas,&rdquo; &ndash; Eric Vorhees"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/63igk"> IamAlso_u_grahvity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxw">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxu">[57 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 18:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to tell who mined a bitcoin?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>If bitcoin algorithm was broken and some one started spitting out blocks one after the other through their other worldly space computer, could it be detected that the same miner was busting all the blocks? Follow up question: How does the network strength or hashing power get computed? By just assuming the required H/s for the current technology?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Motes</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 18:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[With the recent Mt.Gox fiasco, we'd like to present you a better, secure way to store and trade your Bitcoins]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqxy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxy"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqxz" alt="With the recent Mt.Gox fiasco, we'd like to present you a better, secure way to store and trade your Bitcoins" title="With the recent Mt.Gox fiasco, we'd like to present you a better, secure way to store and trade your Bitcoins"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy0"> m4v3r </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy1">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqxy">[126 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 18:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BTCXINDIA Bitmessage Chan for trading]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqy2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Indian Bitcoin exchange BTCXINDIA( <a href="http://cur.lv/700wh">http://cur.lv/700wh</a> ) has started Bitmessage chan called "BTCXINDIA" for P2P trading. The channel address is<br> BM-2cTUZxcBdRzSpygVEniqBedKLMkZ5WKXDd</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy3"> btcxindia </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy4">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy2">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 18:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Britain to scrap Bitcoin tax]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqy5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy5"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqy6" alt="Britain to scrap Bitcoin tax" title="Britain to scrap Bitcoin tax"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy7"> biomimic </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy8">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy5">[183 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The pressing issue of our time.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqy9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy9"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqya" alt="The pressing issue of our time." title="The pressing issue of our time."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyb"> flamingboard </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyc">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy9">[28 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ukraine Capital Control Crunch: Largest Bank Limits Cash Withdrawals To $100 Daily]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqyd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqye"> unk1911 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyf">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyd">[172 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 16:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[You Don't Need A Nobel Prize To Be Wrong About Bitcoin, But It Helps]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqyg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyg"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqyh" alt="You Don't Need A Nobel Prize To Be Wrong About Bitcoin, But It Helps" title="You Don't Need A Nobel Prize To Be Wrong About Bitcoin, But It Helps"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqy7"> biomimic </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyi">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyg">[72 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 16:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin true believers unfazed by losses in Mt. Gox collapse]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqyj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyj"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqyk" alt="Bitcoin true believers unfazed by losses in Mt. Gox collapse" title="Bitcoin true believers unfazed by losses in Mt. Gox collapse"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyl"> sometimes_correct </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqym">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyj">[75 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 15:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How is the transaction malleability issue being fixed?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqyn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>With the upcoming release of Bitcoin Core 0.9, I am wondering how the transaction malleability issue is being fixed and what are the consequences of the fix?</p>

<p>It appears that transaction malleability is causing a few problems for the Bitcoin network:</p>

<ul><li>The network is DDoSed by multiple apparent double-spends being relayed</li>
<li>Senders of the transactions need to avoid spending 0 confirmation transactions in case they become invalidated by malleability</li>
<li>When saving TxIDs of spent transaction for record keeping one has to make sure the TxID did not get changed later</li>
</ul><p>Will all of those issues be addressed in the upcoming update, and if so, how will they be addressed?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>ThePiachu</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 14:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Evidence that Karpeles still has the coins]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqyo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>The subject here is the 400K address connected to <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyp">gox's proven 424K address</a>.</p> <p>Many of the transactions out of bitcoin2cash's <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyq">advertised public address</a> (later became localbitcoins) ended up at the 400K address. I suspect it was people who bought bitcoin from bitcoin2cash and then sold on gox. You can see 25K was received by someone then 1 day later sent to a likely gox wallet where it got consolidated into the 400K: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyr">http://cur.lv/7wqyr</a></p> <p><strong>Edit</strong>: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqys">The owner just confirmed it's a gox deposit address!</a></p> <p>If the 400K address is gox then the bitcoin days destroyed spikes on Dec 21 and Feb 5 (day before gox disabled withdrawals) totaling ~160K were all gox chunks. You can see they have a similar pattern where 0.001 BTC is sent to test if the new address works, then the full 4K chunk is sent to its final resting place. This can't be tx malleability because on Feb 5 a hacker returning the 0.001 back into the gox wallet before doing the full 4K withdrawal makes no sense:</p> <p>chunk from Dec 21 spike: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyt">http://cur.lv/7wqyt</a></p> <p>chunk from Feb 5 spike: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyu">http://cur.lv/7wqyu</a></p> <p>Further evidence that the days destroyed spikes were gox: Bitcoin donated to gox (<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyv">their advertised address</a>) gets consolidated into 9K, then 45K:</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyw">http://cur.lv/7wqyw</a></p> <p>Then the 45K gets split up into 4K chunks, which went untouched until the Feb 5 spike!</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyx">http://cur.lv/7wqyx</a></p> <p>Here's a 9K chunk split off from the gox donations where on Feb 5 you see the typical 0.001 test to see if the new address works, followed by a return of the 0.001 to test sending from the address, followed by the full withdrawal:</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyy">http://cur.lv/7wqyy</a></p> <p>and the final resting places of the 9K chunk (2K+7K):</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyz">http://cur.lv/7wqyz</a></p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz0">http://cur.lv/7wqz0</a></p> <p>Once the 9K was moved out of cold storage we see a 0.001 cleanup on the hot 9K address which reveals gox's major hot wallet!</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz1">http://cur.lv/7wqz1</a></p> <p>The suspected hot wallet is a 15K chunk, backtracing it leads to <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyp">1LX</a> which leads to gox's 400K. You can see it was being siphoned off daily in 500 BTC chunks which were further distributed until withdrawals were disabled Feb 6. It became active again several days ago for the final cleanup where the hot wallet currently resides (15K + new 500 chunk):</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz2">http://cur.lv/7wqz2</a></p> <p>Although all paths from here lead to large unspent outputs, this 500 BTC chunk siphoned off Feb 6 had activity today (follow the 200 split):</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz3">http://cur.lv/7wqz3</a></p> <p><strong>On Feb 5 Karpeles resurrected cold storage to handle withdrawals but then probably thinks "screw it!"</strong> He's likely tired of getting bashed by the community and senses the looming bank run, so he uses a minor tx malleability theft as an excuse to declare bankruptcy. I believe he also sold 10K BTC on bitstamp before announcing his resignation but I have no proof yet. This is a massive fraud! Karpeles thinks he's bullet proof hiding behind corporate liability protection and lack of regulation.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz4"> Kometes_ </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqyo">[196 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Free 300 XRP Giveaway at Tradefast!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqz5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hello Ripple Redditors!</p> <p>We have recently launched a new website helping Bitcoin users to convert their holdings to Ripple XRP. Our website is located at Tradefast.me. With the aim of raising awareness about our services, we are now offering 300 free Ripple XRPs to the first 100 individuals who successfully participate in our Giveaway contest. </p> <p>What does the contest entail? We promise, it is straightforward. Here are the required steps: </p> <p>1.You must like our Facebook page found here: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz6">http://cur.lv/7wqz6</a></p> <ol><li><p>We will ask a series of questions related to Ripple XRP, the Ripple Platform, and current events surrounding Crypto-currencies (This will be easy for you. As Redditors, you guys remain up-to-date on the latest news). </p></li> <li><p>For successful participants, we will then privately contact you and/or simply reply to your correct answer requesting for you to provide us with your Ripple wallet address. </p></li> <li><p>300 free Ripple XRPs to your wallet. </p></li> </ol><p>We at Tradefast.me look forward to your participation!</p> <p>Please do not hesitate to ask any questions related to the free Ripple XRP Giveaway and/or our Tradefast.me service!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz7"> TradefastRipple </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz5">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz5">[7 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 06:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E88 – Gox Gox Gox Gox Gox Gox Gox]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqz8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Let's Talk Bitcoin!</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 03:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[DAOs Are Not Scary, Part 2: Reducing Barriers]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqz9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In the last installment of this series, we talked about what &ldquo;smart contracts&rdquo; (or, perhaps more accurately, &ldquo;self-enforcing contracts&rdquo;) are, and discussed in detail the two main mechanisms through which these contracts can have &ldquo;force&rdquo;: smart property and &ldquo;factum&rdquo; currencies. We also discussed the limits of smart contracts, and how a smart contract-enabled legal system might use a combination of human judgement and automatic execution to achieve the best possible outcomes. But what is the point of these contracts? Why automate? Why is it better to have our relationships regulated and controlled by algorithms rather than humans? These are the tough questions that this article, and the next, intends to tackle. A Tale of Two Industries The first, and most [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wqz9">DAOs Are Not Scary, Part 2: Reducing Barriers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqz9"><img width="1024" height="681" src="http://cur.lv/7lvfg" alt="Quito"></a><p>In the <a href="http://cur.lv/7soqc">last installment of this series</a>, we talked about what &ldquo;smart contracts&rdquo; (or, perhaps more accurately, &ldquo;self-enforcing contracts&rdquo;) are, and discussed in detail the two main mechanisms through which these contracts can have &ldquo;force&rdquo;: smart property and &ldquo;factum&rdquo; currencies. We also discussed the limits of smart contracts, and how a smart contract-enabled legal system might use a combination of human judgement and automatic execution to achieve the best possible outcomes. But what is the point of these contracts? Why automate? Why is it better to have our relationships regulated and controlled by algorithms rather than humans? These are the tough questions that this article, and the next, intends to tackle.</p>
<h3>A Tale of Two Industries</h3>
<p>The first, and most obvious, benefit of using internet-driven technology to automate anything is the exact same that we have seen the internet, and Bitcoin, already provide in the spheres of communications and commerce: it increases efficiency and reduces barriers to entry. One very good example of this effect providing meaningful benefits in the traditional world is the publishing industry. In the 1970s, if you wanted to write a book, there was a large number of opaque, centralized intermediaries that you would need to go through before your book would get to a consumer. First, you would need a publishing company, which would also handle editing and marketing for you and provide a quality control function to the consumer. Second, the book would need to be distributed, and then finally it would be sold at each individual bookstore. Each part of the chain would take a large cut; at the end, you would be lucky to get more than ten percent of the revenue from each copy as a royalty. Notice the use of the term &ldquo;royalty&rdquo;, implying that you the author of the book are simply just another extraneous part of the chain that deserves a few percent as a cut rather than, well, <em>the</em> single most important person without whom the book would not even exist in the first place. Now, the situation is greatly improved. We now have distinct printing companies, marketing companies and bookstores, with a clear and defined role for each one and plenty of competition in each industry &ndash; and if you&rsquo;re okay with keeping it purely digital, you can just publish on Kindle and get 70%.</p>
<p>Now, let&rsquo;s consider a very similar example, but with a completely different industry: consumer protection, or more specifically escrow. Escrow is a very important function in commerce, and especially commerce online; when you buy a product from a small online store or from a merchant on Ebay, you are participating in a transaction where neither side has a substantial reputation, and so when you send the money by default there is no way to be sure that you will actually get anything to show for it. Escrow provides the solution: instead of sending the money to the merchant directly, you first send the money to an escrow agent, and the escrow agent then waits for you to confirm that you received the item. If you confirm, then the escrow agent sends the money along, and if the merchant confirms that they can&rsquo;t send the item then the escrow agent gives you your money back. If there&rsquo;s a dispute, an adjudication process begins, and the escrow agent decides which side has the better case.</p>
<p>The way it&rsquo;s implemented today, however, escrow is handled by centralized entities, and is thrown in together with a large number of other functions. On the online marketplace <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqza">Ebay</a>, for example, Ebay serves the role of providing a server for the seller to host their product page on, a search and price comparison function for products, and a rating system for buyers and sellers. Ebay also owns Paypal, which actually moves the money from the seller to the buyer and serves as the escrow agent. Essentially, this is exactly the same situation that book publishing was in in the 1970s, although in fairness to Ebay sellers do get quite a bit more than 10% of their money. So how can we make an ideal marketplace with cryptocurrencies and smart contracts? If we wanted to be extreme about it, we could make the marketplace decentralized, using a Diaspora-like model to allow a seller to host their products on a specialized site, on their own server or on a <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzb">Decentralized Dropbox implementation</a>, use a Namecoin-like system for sellers to store their identities and keep a web of trust on the blockchain. However, what we&rsquo;re looking at now is a more moderate and simple goal: separating out the function of the escrow agent from the payment system. Fortunately, Bitcoin offers a solution: multisignature transactions.</p>
<h3>Introducing Multisig</h3>
<p>Multisignature transactions allow a user to send funds to an address with three private keys, such that you need two of those keys to unlock the funds (multisigs can also be 1-of-3, 6-of-9, or anything else, but in practice 2-of-3 is the most useful). The way to apply this to escrow is simple: create a 2-of-3 escrow between the buyer, the seller and the escrow agent, have the buyer send funds into it and when a transaction is complete the buyer and the seller sign a transaction to complete the escrow. If there is a dispute, the escrow agent picks which side has the more convincing case, and signs a transaction with them to send them the funds. On a technological level, this is slightly complicated, but fortunately <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxh">Bitrated</a> has come up with a site that makes the process quite easy for the average user.</p>
<p>Of course, in its current form, Bitrated is not perfect, and we do not see that much Bitcoin commerce using it. The interface is arguably not as easy as it could be, especially since most people are not used to the idea of storing specific per-transaction links for a few weeks, and it would be much more powerful if it was integrated into a fully-fledged merchant package. One design might be a <a href="http://cur.lv/7somb">KryptoKit</a>-like web app, showing each user a list of &ldquo;open&rdquo; buys and sells and providing a &ldquo;finalize&rdquo;, &ldquo;accept&rdquo;, &ldquo;cancel&rdquo; and &ldquo;dispute&rdquo; button for each one; users would then be able to interact with the multisig system just as if it was a standard payment processor, but then get a notification to finalize or dispute their purchases after a few weeks.</p>
<p>But if Bitrated does get its interface right and starts to see mass adoption, what will that accomplish? Once again, the answer is reduced barriers to entry. Currently, getting into the consumer escrow and arbitration business is hard. In order to be an escrow service, you essentially need to build an entire platform and an ecosystem, so that consumers and merchants operate through you. You also can&rsquo;t just be the one escrowing the money &ndash; you also need to be the one transferring the money in the first place. Ebay needs to have, and control, Paypal, in order for half of its consumer protection to work. With Bitrated, this all changes. Anyone can become an escrow agent and arbitrator, and an Ebay-like marketplace (perhaps <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzc">CryptoThrift</a> or the upcoming <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzd">Egora</a>) can have a rating system for arbitrators as well as buyers and sellers. Alternatively, the system could handle arbitration in the background similarly to how Uber handles taxi drivers: anyone could become an arbitrator after a vetting process, and the system would automatically reward arbitrators with good ratings and fire those with bad ratings. Fees would drop, likely substantially below even the 2.9% charged by Paypal alone.</p>
<h3>Smart Contracts</h3>
<p>Smart contracts in general take this same basic idea, and push it much further. Instead of relying on a platform like Bitfinex to hedge one&rsquo;s Bitcoin holdings or speculate in either direction at high leverage, one can use a blockchain-based financial derivatives contract with a decentralized order book, leaving no central party to take any fees. The ongoing cost of maintaining an exchange, complete with operational security, server management, DDoS protection, marketing and legal expenses, could be replaced with a one-time effort to write the contract, likely in less than 100 lines of code, and another one-time effort to make a pretty interface. From that point on, the entire system would be free except for network fees. File storage platforms like Dropbox could be similarly replaced; although, since hard disk space costs money, the system would not be free, it would likely be substantially cheaper than it is today. It would also help equalize the market by making it easy to participate on the supply side: anyone with a big hard drive, or even a small hard drive with some extra space, can simply install the app and start earning money renting out their unused space.</p>
<p>Instead of relying on legal contracts using expensive (and often, especially in international circumstances and poor countries, ineffective) court systems, or even moderately expensive private arbitration services, business relationships can be governed by smart contracts where those parts of the contract that do need human interpretation can be segregated into many specialized parts. There might be judges specializing in determining whether or not a product shipped (ideally, this would be the postal system itself), judges specializing in determining whether web application designs meet specifications, judges specializing in adjudicating certain classes of property insurance claims with a $0.75 fee by examining satellite images, and there would be contract writers skilled in intelligently integrating each one. Specialization has its advantages, and is the reason why society moved beyond running after bears with stone clubs and picking berries, but one of its weaknesses has always been the fact that it requires intermediaries to manage and function, including intermediaries specifically to manage the relationship between the intermediaries. Smart contracts can remove the latter category almost completely, allowing for an even greater degree of specialization, along with lower barriers to entry within each now shrunken category.</p>
<p>However, this increase in efficiency is only one part of the puzzle. The other part, and perhaps the more important one, has to do with a topic that many cryptocurrency advocates hold dear: reducing trust. We will cover that in the next installment of this series.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wqz9">DAOs Are Not Scary, Part 2: Reducing Barriers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Vitalik Buterin</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 20:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[We will Activate your Wallets]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqze]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hi guys,</p> <p>I just want to let you know that we've been giving away 25 xrp to activate wallets of people new to Ripple courtesy of The Got Jed? Initiative: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzf">http://cur.lv/7wqzf</a></p> <p>All you need to do is introduce yourself here: <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzf">http://cur.lv/7wqzf</a> and post your wallet address, then we will send you 25 xrp. </p> <p>Upon receiving the xrp, please bump this thread by saying thanks or something, so that everybody else will get a chance to see this thread. </p> <p>Thanks. :)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzg"> the_real_lucky331 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqze">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqze">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 15:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Don’t Get Goxed – Use The Five Parties Model]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wqzh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Why MtGox Went Broke &ndash; The Five Parties Model MtGox, the Bitcoin exchange, is in the news again, this time for collapsing. One&nbsp;leaked report&nbsp;maintains that MtGox may only have 2,000 Bitcoins in reserve over against 744,408 Btc in liabilities &ndash; which indicates a reserve of less than 1%. With new revelations coming out daily this paragraph will be out of date by the time this article hits the press. Whatever the final details turn out to be, MtGox melted down, and the digital currency community needs to ask why this happened, and how can we prevent this from happening again. MtGox originally claimed that their troubles stemmed from a long-term exploit of the&nbsp;malleability bug&nbsp;which tricked exchange providers into spending bitcoins [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzh">Don&rsquo;t Get Goxed &ndash; Use The Five Parties Model</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzh"><img width="1024" height="640" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzi" alt="Why Mt Gox Went Broke"></a><p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzh" title="click to read"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wqzj" width="620" height="387" alt="Why MtGox Went Broke &ndash; The Five Parties Model"></a></p>
<p>Why MtGox Went Broke &ndash; The Five Parties Model</p>
<p>MtGox, the Bitcoin exchange, is in the news again, this time for collapsing. One&nbsp;<a title="MtGox Loses 340 Million in Bitcoin - CoinDesk" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzk" target="_blank">leaked report</a>&nbsp;maintains that MtGox may only have 2,000 Bitcoins in reserve over against 744,408 Btc in liabilities &ndash; which indicates a reserve of less than 1%. With new revelations coming out daily this paragraph will be out of date by the time this article hits the press. Whatever the final details turn out to be, MtGox melted down, and the digital currency community needs to ask why this happened, and how can we prevent this from happening again.</p>
<p>MtGox originally claimed that their troubles stemmed from a long-term exploit of the&nbsp;<a title="MtGox Falls to the Malleability Bug - FinancialCryptography.com" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzl" target="_blank">malleability bug</a>&nbsp;which tricked exchange providers into spending bitcoins to the attacker&rsquo;s account.&nbsp;However, the loss of 99.7% of their reserves cannot be attributed to the malleability bug. It is clear that the failure of MtGox is a failure of governance.</p>
<p>MtGox is not alone.&nbsp;Forty-five percent&nbsp;of Bitcoin exchanges to date <a title="Statistical Analysis of Bitcoin Exchange Failures - Financial Cryptography Conference 2013" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzm" target="_blank">have failed</a>, in most cases with their&nbsp;customers&rsquo;&nbsp;money. The digital currency industry&rsquo;s track record on fiduciary responsibility is abysmal.</p>
<p>Some <a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzn" target="_blank">people on the sidelines</a> have been jumping up and down calling for government regulation of Bitcoin. However, government regulation is not the solution.</p>
<p>The digital currency community should be self-regulating. This is best achieved by using good governance.</p>
<p>In this article we will show how the&nbsp;<strong>Five Parties Model</strong>&nbsp;of governance can be applied to Bitcoin exchanges as a way to give better quality oversight than any regulator can impose. Then we will analyze the failure of MtGox and how it could have been prevented by using the Five Parties Model.</p>
<h2>Trust Shall Not Live by Tech Alone</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is an attempt to solve the problem of governance of a centralised issuer of currency through technology. By using a common protocol to manage a public blockchain, we can make it impossible to issue more Bitcoins than the pre-determined limit.</p>
<p>As MtGox has shown, the&nbsp;issuance&nbsp;problem is not the only trust problem for the digital currency community.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzo"><img alt="Trust No One - Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzo" width="599" height="496"></a>In order to provide useful services, certain businesses must hold the users&rsquo; Bitcoins and cash in escrow. These businesses, such as exchanges, brokerages, online wallets, retail payment aggregators, etc. are at risk from insider theft, external hacking and loss through currency volatility risk and poor accounting practices.</p>
<p>How can a user trust a business to protect his or her value held in escrow? Clearly the users of MtGox trusted an entity that was not trustworthy.</p>
<p>This is not a new problem for finance. It is called the &ldquo;agency problem&rdquo; in reference to the fact that an agent acts for the user as a trusted intermediary. Financial institutions have been dealing with the issue of trusted intermediaries for millennia.</p>
<p>This field is broadly called &ldquo;governance&rdquo; and has many well known methods for achieving accountability and reliability for fiduciary institutions.</p>
<p>The question then is how to bring those practices into a digital accounting and payment system.</p>
<p>To address this weakness of customer escrowed funds, back in the late 1990&rsquo;s we developed a governance technique for digital currency that we called the &ldquo;<a title="Five Parties Model of Governance - Systemics 1998" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzp" target="_blank">Five Parties Model of Governance</a>.&rdquo; (This model was built into the digital currency platform that we designed for exchange, called &ldquo;<a title="Ricardo Executive Summary - Systemics" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzq" target="_blank">Ricardo</a>&rdquo;.)</p>
<p>The five parties model shares the responsibility and roles for protection of value amongst five distinct parties involved in the transactions. Although originally designed to protect an entire digital currency, this technique should be broadly applied to businesses that hold value in escrow for their customers.</p>
<h2>The Five Parties Model (5PM)</h2>
<p>Every business that holds customer funds in escrow and allows them to trade internally, such as MtGox, is effectively a digital currency issuer.</p>
<p>For a single issuer of digital currency, the Five Parties Model looks like this (Figure 1).</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzr"><img alt="Figure 1. Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzs" width="586" height="620"></a><p>Figure 1. Five Parties Model of Governance</p></div>
<h3>1. Issuer</h3>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzt"><img title="The Issuer - Five Parties Model of Governance" alt="The Issuer - Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzt" width="132" height="135"></a>The Issuer is the institution guaranteeing the contract with the User. This is the person or entity ultimately responsible for the assets and whether the governance succeeds or fails.</p>
<p>Every Bitcoin exchange (ie. MtGox), online wallet, and payment service aggregator (ie. BitPay) who escrows customer funds and represents them as an account is acting as a digital value Issuer. The bigger the institution, the greater the need for a strong governance contract with the users.</p>
<h3><a name="h.z2zgj3x8p61k"></a>2. Trustee</h3>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzu"><img title="The Trustee  - Five Parties Model of Governance" alt="The Trustee  - Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzu" width="132" height="135"></a>Each holder of value has a signatory who controls creation or deletion of assets on the books &ndash; which should mirror the deposit or withdrawal of assets from the reserve asset pool.</p>
<p>This position has an alter ego &ndash; a different signatory on the other side, who controls deposit and withdrawal from the asset pool (reserve accounts).</p>
<p>In the Five Parties Model we assign the signatory role to a Trustee, such as an outside law firm or accountant, who is not an employee or shareholder of the Issuer.</p>
<p>The Trustee should operate under two&nbsp;rules:</p>
<p>a. The Trustee may only disburse assets with a transaction receipt from the mirror account of the one he controls.</p>
<p>Ie. if he controls the internal account for Bitcoin, then he can only create new internal value on presentation of a deposit receipt of equal value of Bitcoin for the reserve asset account (ie. the cold wallet).</p>
<p>b. The Trustee can only spend or disburse value to the Manager account. This prevents the Trustee from creating new value and spending to an account that he or an accomplice controls. For a Trustee on the asset reserve account, he can only spend withdrawals to the Manager&rsquo;s account.</p>
<h3><a name="h.7ggpkxhedt7f"></a>3. Manager</h3>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzv"><img title="The Manager - Five Parties Model of Governance" alt="The Manager - Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzv" width="132" height="135"></a> In the Five Parties Model the Manager is the person or entity, usually the trading desk of the Issuer, who asks the Trustee to perform the big controlled operations: create or destroy digital assets, or deposit or withdraw physical ones, in order to reflect the overall pattern of trading activities.</p>
<p>The Manager typically works on a daily trading basis using float accounts (hot wallets).</p>
<p>In an example business day, the trading desk may get 50 BTC deposits and 45 BTC withdrawals, leading to a net position of +5 BTC.</p>
<p>As trading balances build up or draw down, the Manager asks the Trustee to authorise the conversion of daily trading assets against the long-term reserves backing the internal value on the exchange books.</p>
<p>For the above example, if the exchange has net of +5 BTC deposits at the end of the day, the Manager should transfer 5 BTC from the hot wallet trading account to the cold wallet reserve account. Then he places a request to create 5 BTC new value on the internal books, and gives the Trustee a copy of the deposit receipt to the cold storage account.</p>
<p>After verifying the receipt is valid, the Trustee then uses his signing key to create the new value on the internal books, and then spends that value to the Manager&rsquo;s internal float account. &nbsp;In this way the Manager converted 5 actual Bitcoins in his hot wallet into 5 internal Bitcoins on his float account.</p>
<p>That is how value should be moved in and out of a Bitcoin exchange in a controlled and firewalled fashion without putting the reserve funds at risk in a &ldquo;hot wallet&rdquo;.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzw"><img alt="Example of Bailment" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzx" width="434" height="620"></a><p>Manager Bails in 5 BTC to the Cold Wallet</p></div>
<h3>4. Operator / Escrow / Vault</h3>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wqzy"><img title="The Operator- Five Parties Model of Governance" alt="The Operator- Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wqzy" width="132" height="135"></a>Most Bitcoin Exchanges to date have created their own software and operate their own servers. (This is a big part of the reason that 45% of Bitcoin exchanges have failed &ndash; 70% of the failures are due to security breaches.)</p>
<p>Another&nbsp;disadvantage of rolling your own Bitcoin exchange software is that someone inside the company may have enough information to alter the software to conduct illicit transactions and then cover their tracks by deleting the logs.</p>
<p>In the Five Parties Model, it is preferable to outsource the software and server maintenance to a third party that specializes in this service. In the Bitcoin world, <a title="Bex.io Provides Hosted Bitcoin Exchanges" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzz" target="_blank">Bex.io</a> is an example of this model. They have created a standardized Bitcoin exchange software, and lease that software out to local exchanges, while controlling the operation of the software itself. (Disclosure: the authors&rsquo; company, Dinero Limited, also provides and operates this type of software.)</p>
<p>If the role of Operator cannot be outsourced, then we put in place controls to make sure that the IT department does not have access to the signing keys of the Trustee and the Manager. Preferably these parties should not work in close contact with each other, or even work in the same location. The goal is to prevent collusion between the Trustee, the Manager and the department operating the servers.</p>
<p>For the Bitcoin reserve assets in cold storage, the Bitcoin Network is the Operator for the accounting and ledger system. There is already an excellent separation of roles in place there.</p>
<h3>5. The Fifth Party &ndash; The Public as Auditor</h3>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr00"><img title="The Public as Auditor - Five Parties Model of Governance" alt="The Public as Auditor- Five Parties Model of Governance" src="http://cur.lv/7wr00" width="132" height="135"></a>The final and most important element of the Five Parties Model is the role of the Public as auditor.</p>
<p>Typically, the role of&nbsp;auditor&nbsp;is to examine the books to validate that the other parties are indeed doing their job. As is covered elsewhere (<a title="AUDITS I: A WORD ON THE LIMITS -- MADOFF - FinancialCryptography.com" href="http://cur.lv/7wr01" target="_blank">Audit</a>), paid auditors have a long-term conflict of interest, which has been at the root of several notable disasters in the last decade &ndash; the failure of Enron, the wholesale bankruptcy of banking in 2007 financial crisis, the collapse of AIG, none of which auditors rang the bell for.</p>
<p>Auditors, as well as being conflicted, are also expensive. If governments come in and regulate Bitcoin they will require exchanges to pay for quarterly or annual external audits, which will dramatically increase costs without much benefit.</p>
<p>We should be able to find a more effective and less costly alternative.</p>
<p>Let me introduce YOU, the user, also know as &ldquo;The Public.&rdquo;</p>
<p>You, the&nbsp;Public, do not have a conflict of interest, in that it is your value at risk, and you have a strong interest in seeing that the other four parties are doing their&nbsp;jobs&nbsp;properly.</p>
<p>Yet, how can the public audit anything when audit almost by definition means seeing that which cannot be seen?</p>
<p>The answer is to make that which was previously unseen, seen. &nbsp;Make the net balances of the internal books and the reserve assets visible to the public. &nbsp;(We are not suggesting that customer accounts be exposed.) &nbsp;The public only needs to see the total net liabilities of the internal accounts, to compare them to the assets in the reserve accounts.</p>
<p>Some examples of digital currencies that have supported public audit include:</p>
<ul><li><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr02" target="_blank">e-gold</a> published a real time balance sheet of their digital issuance.</li>
<li><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr03" target="_blank">GoldMoney</a> publishes monthly reports and regular audits.</li>
<li><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr04" target="_blank">Bitcoin</a> publishes the blockchain.</li>
<li><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr05" target="_blank">Ricardo</a> publishes the balances of the Trustee and Manager accounts.</li>
</ul><p>Most Bitcoin exchanges already have public API&rsquo;s used for automated trading. It should be trivial to add a query to their API that allows the public to ascertain the net balance on the internal books in real time.</p>
<p>The addresses of the Bitcoin cold storage accounts should also be made public. This allows the public to compare the asset reserve to the internal book value that has been issued. If the internal book balance is higher than the asset reserve, there has been a breach of contract.</p>
<h2>The Five Parties Model Applied to Bitcoin Exchange</h2>
<p>The Five Parties Model is just and exactly that &ndash; a model. This means there are variations, and a business must modify it to suit. For example, many businesses in the space have not one but two bases of value to control: an underlying asset and a digital issuance. Bitcoin exchanges fall into this category.</p>
<p>When an Issuer is backing the digital currency with a reserve asset, both of these assets need to be protected. To do this, we utilise two instances of the Five Parties Model in a mirrored pair. In each, the Issuer and the Public act as parties on both sides, whereas the Trustee, the Operator and the Manager may be duplicated (or not). Figure 2 shows an application of the Five Parties Model to a Bitcoin Exchange.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr06"><img alt="5 Party Model for Two Assets" src="http://cur.lv/7wr07" width="401" height="620"></a><p>Figure 2. 5 Party Model for Bitcoin Exchange</p></div>
<p>An exchange supporting many currency pairs requires a somewhat more complicated regime. For every one of their assets &ndash; BTC, Altcoins, USD, EUR, JPY, etc, they must delegate operators, trustees and managers.</p>
<p>However, this model can still be managed for multiple currency types with only two trustees &ndash; one for the internal book value, and one for the external reserve assets.</p>
<h3>Where MtGox Went Wrong</h3>
<p>Now that we have explained the Five Parties Model and why it is important, let&rsquo;s look at where MtGox failed.</p>
<h3><a name="h.qbeenx40wy3"></a>MtGox as the Issuer of Internal Book Value</h3>
<p>In the present case, MtGox was the contractual party that guaranteed to deliver an exchange of value, and in the mean time keep escrowed funds&nbsp;and/or&nbsp;BTC secure.</p>
<p>As can be seen from the following screen capture (Figure 3) taken from the Internet Archive, MtGox did in fact have a contract with the users to fully reserve their internal Bitcoin and currency accounts:</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr08"><img alt="Figure 3. MtGox Custodial Contract" src="http://cur.lv/7wr09" width="620" height="319"></a><p>Figure 3. MtGox Custodial Contract</p></div>
<p>As an Issuer MtGox failed to implement internal controls to ensure that their contract conditions were honored at all times.</p>
<p>Furthermore,&nbsp;<a title="Jesse Powell on MtGox - CoinDesk" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0a" target="_blank">recent revelations</a>&nbsp;(by a former MtGox insider who is now a competitor) allege that&nbsp;MtGox management may have knowingly operated the exchange on a fractional reserve basis since a major Bitcoin theft in 2011. If that proves to be true, then sadly, the management may have compounded the initial crime committed against them by secretly operating in breach of contract instead of simply reporting the theft and filing for bankruptcy. That followed by rise in the value of Bitcoin since&nbsp;2011&nbsp;has multiplied the impact of the original theft by one-hundred fold.</p>
<h3>MtGox Failed to Separate the Roles</h3>
<div><img alt="MtGox Failed to Separate Roles to Keep The Wrong Hands Out of the Cookie Jar" src="http://cur.lv/7wr0b" width="290" height="320"><p>MtGox Failed to Separate Roles to Keep The Wrong Hands Out of the Cookie Jar</p></div>
<p>MtGox appears to have had the same trading desk or Manager controlling both the creation of value on the internal books and the release of assets in the reserve accounts.</p>
<p>By merging two roles that should have been separated &mdash;&nbsp;Manager and Trustee &mdash; MtGox allowed the Manager to transfer out the reserve assets without first destroying an equivalent amount of internal value on their books.</p>
<p>If MtGox had been following the Five Parties Model from the beginning, it would have been impossible for a security breach or malleability attack to have stolen any more than the Manager&rsquo;s hot wallet balance. The customers&rsquo; funds would not have been jeopardized and the discrepancy would have become immediately apparent.</p>
<p>The failure of MtGox to separate the asset reserve from the Manager&rsquo;s trading accounts precipitated an epic disaster.</p>
<h3><a name="h.wpqqkbqqgcf7"></a>MtGox Failed to Arrange for Audit</h3>
<p>MtGox did not make their internal Bitcoin balances public, and did not have a quarterly third party audit in place, either. Consequently they operated as the largest Bitcoin exchange for three years with no one checking their books. &nbsp;That is like driving while blindfolded.</p>
<p>Ideally, MtGox would have displayed a balance sheet with references to cold wallets on one side, and their internal Bitcoin/Altcoin balances on the other side. The former is verifiable via the blockchain,&nbsp;while&nbsp;the latter could be made available by the operator via the API, and periodically audited by a third party to ensure the code providing the balance query was accurate.</p>
<h3><a name="h.tl7mohvvplxm"></a>MtGox Failed Because Nobody Was Watching Them</h3>
<div><img alt="The Public Failed to Demand an Audit from MtGox" src="http://cur.lv/7wr0c" width="500" height="330"><p>The Public Failed to Demand an Audit from MtGox</p></div>
<p>With the information above, you the Public as individuals or as media or other observers could have verified that things were as they should be, and if not, sound the alarm! That&rsquo;s what Twitter and media sites such as CoinDesk and Bitcoin Magazine are for.</p>
<p>As MtGox did not have a sufficient governance model in place, the public was startled to learn that more than $300 million worth of Bitcoin managed to disappear.</p>
<p>However, we the account holders may ultimately blame our own failure to insist on good governance for any losses we suffered from the failure of MtGox.</p>
<h2><a name="h.y31gku78j866"></a>How To Prevent MtGox From Happening Again</h2>
<p>If the digital currency community does not self-regulate, we will find ourselves placed under government regulations. (Which may well happen anyway.) Government regulations drive up operation costs, but ultimately do not provide additional safety or security. Consider how government regulation utterly failed to prevent the 2007 banking crisis.</p>
<p>Instead of regulation, the digital currency community should demand and apply the Five Parties Model of governance.</p>
<p>Public transparency is consistent with the ideals of Bitcoin&rsquo;s public blockchain, and can be expected to greatly improve the stability and reliability of the digital currency community.</p>
<p>Applying the Five Parties Model to Bitcoin exchanges need not be expensive. All it takes is for any exchange to appoint two trustees to control the reserve assets and the internal book value, limit the accounts the Trustees can transfer value to, and publish an API allowing public query of the total balance of their internal books.</p>
<p>We have websites such as&nbsp;<a title="Blockchain.info" href="http://cur.lv/7somd" target="_blank">blockchain.info</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a title="Bitcoincharts.com" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0d" target="_blank">bitcoincharts.com</a>&nbsp;that can&nbsp;easily&nbsp;support realtime charts using the information from the APIs of participating Bitcoin exchanges. Instead of merely providing price data, these websites can play an integral part of the governance of the Bitcoin community by collecting and displaying data concerning the reserve assets and total liabilities of exchanges and escrow services.</p>
<p>The media also play a very important part of the governance equation. Publications that cover the digital currency sector like&nbsp;<a title="Bitcoin Magazine" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx" target="_blank">Bitcoin Magazine</a>,&nbsp;<a title="Digital Gold Currency Magazine" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0e" target="_blank">DGC Magazine</a>, and&nbsp;<a title="Coin Desk" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0f" target="_blank">CoinDesk</a>&nbsp;should be asking hard questions of new and old exchanges about their governance procedures instead of merely producing shiney, happy write-ups in their zeal to promote Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The&nbsp;<a title="Bitcoin Foundation" href="http://cur.lv/7wr04" target="_blank">Bitcoin Foundation</a>&nbsp;and other&nbsp;<a title="Digital Asset Transfer Authority (DATA)" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0g" target="_blank">industry associations</a>&nbsp;would be well advised to encourage the development of an industry standard for governance of exchanges and escrow services using the Five Parties Model.</p>
<p>You, the public, should demand it.</p>
<p>To voice your support for the Five Parties Model, please use the hashtag&nbsp;<a title="Twitter Hashtag for Five Parties Model of Governance" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0h" target="_blank">#5PModel</a>.</p>
<hr><p>Update &ndash; As this article was going to press,&nbsp;BitQuick&nbsp;<a title="BitQuick updates API to Show Proof of Reserves in Real Time" href="http://cur.lv/7twsu" target="_blank">became the first</a>&nbsp;Bitcoin exchange to move towards implementing the Five Parties Model by making its internal balance and Bitcoin reserve addresses public through their API. (Perhaps that&rsquo;s why they are called Bit QUICK.)</p>
<hr><p><em><a title="Ian Grigg is the Author of FinancialCryptography.com" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0i">Ian Grigg</a>&nbsp;and Ken Griffith are the co-founders at&nbsp;<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0j">Dinero Limited</a>, which provides a secure multi-instrument platform for digital currency exchange. Since 1995 we have built real-time trading exchanges for precious metals, securities and digital currencies. Dinero&rsquo;s trading platform is a complete solution ideal for hosting crypto-currency exchanges.</em></p>
<p><em>This article is a modified version of the paper &ldquo;<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0k">HOW MTGOX FAILED THE FIVE PARTIES GOVERNANCE TEST</a>&rdquo; first published at&nbsp;<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0i">FinancialCryptography.com</a>&nbsp;on 2014-02-26.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wqzh">Don&rsquo;t Get Goxed &ndash; Use The Five Parties Model</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ken Griffith</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 05:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Regulation Update- 02/28/14]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr0l]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The last week in February took a turn for the worse for Bitcoiners as ailing exchange Mt. Gox finally closed its doors, leaving its customers with scant idea as to when (or whether) they might be able to recover their funds. Media outlets worldwide pounced on the news, prematurely taking the opportunity to declare the end of Bitcoin. Following the usual pattern, the hysteria prompted yet another round of denunciations, warnings and dire predictions that &ldquo;Bitcoin is nothing more than a scam!&rdquo; and users should &ldquo;get out while [they] can!&rdquo; Meanwhile, other exchanges and trading platforms worldwide continued their orderly conduct of business and the price of one bitcoin remained relatively stable at around $600. PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT FOR US [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0l">Bitcoin Regulation Update- 02/28/14</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0l"><img width="400" height="266" src="http://cur.lv/6kv4j" alt="ravenbit-physical-bitcoin-closeup-1015a-400"></a><p dir="ltr">The last week in February took a turn for the worse for Bitcoiners as ailing exchange Mt. Gox finally closed its doors, leaving its customers with scant idea as to when (or whether) they might be able to recover their funds. Media outlets worldwide pounced on the news, prematurely taking the opportunity to declare the end of Bitcoin. Following the usual pattern, the hysteria prompted yet another round of denunciations, warnings and dire predictions that &ldquo;Bitcoin is nothing more than a scam!&rdquo; and users should &ldquo;get out while [they] can!&rdquo; Meanwhile, other exchanges and trading platforms worldwide continued their orderly conduct of business and the price of one bitcoin remained relatively stable at around $600.</p>
<p dir="ltr">PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT FOR US TAXPAYERS:&nbsp; If you had a wallet with Mt. Gox during 2013, and if at any time during the year the account value exceeded $10,000, you should strongly consider filing a foreign bank account disclosure form &ndash; called a 90.22.1 form (also known as an FBAR).&nbsp; The US Department of Justice has subpoenaed Mt. Gox&rsquo;s records.&nbsp; While the focus of the investigation will be on potential criminal activity, it isn&rsquo;t a stretch to think that the government might take a detour to see who is following the rules and who is not.</p>
<p dir="ltr">United States Democratic Senator Joe Manchin submitted a letter to US federal regulators asking for an outright <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0m">ban</a> on Bitcoin in that country. The Senator&rsquo;s letter, which could charitably be assessed as &ldquo;ill-informed&rdquo;, or less charitably as ignorant and authoritarian, highlights Bitcoin&rsquo;s volatility and lack of central control as threats to consumers and seems to have been timed to coincide with the fall of Mt. Gox. It had no co-authors, though other US lawmakers (notably New York Democratic Senator Charles Schumer) have frequently spoken out against Bitcoin in the past. In his letter, Senator Manchin asked regulators for a ban for a variety of reasons, but offered no explanation concerning the legal basis for his request or a proposed mechanism for its implementation. Manchin is one of the Senate&rsquo;s most junior members, having only been elected for the first time in 2010, and has also developed a reputation as one of its most bipartisan.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoin Foundation issued an open <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0n">letter</a> in response to Senator Manchin, highlighting Bitcoin&rsquo;s many virtues and the willingness of the Bitcoin community to cooperate with legislative fact-finding in the recent past. The Foundation also asked Manchin not to discourage innovation by advocating untimely or ill-conceived regulatory action.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In what amounts to a quit-claim declaration on regulation, US Federal Reserve chairwoman Janet Yellen<a href="http://cur.lv/7sols"> testified</a> before the Senate Banking Committee that the central bank lacks the authority at present to regulate Bitcoin &ldquo;in any way.&rdquo; Though her comment may be true in a direct sense, it seems disingenuous to claim that the Fed is powerless to act &ldquo;in any way.&rdquo; As one of the primary regulators of the US banking system (the Fed has overlapping jurisdiction with the US Treasury, the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency, the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, state banking agencies and a number of smaller agencies) the Fed undoubtedly possesses the ability to influence Bitcoin by governing the points at which it comes into contact with financial institutions. The Federal Reserve has largely kept silent about crypto currency issues since Yellen took her seat as chairwoman of the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s Board of Governors last October. While it would likely be premature to interpret her stance as a show of support, either implicitly or explicitly, it could be an indication that the Fed is willing to take a &ldquo;wait and see&rdquo; approach on Bitcoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Australian government publicly disclosed that it has the ability to<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0o"> track</a> conversions from Bitcoin into Australian dollars. First reported by technology publication ZDNet, John Schmidt, CEO of Austrac (the Australian government&rsquo;s financial crimes tracking service), nonchalantly admitted in testimony before a committee of the Australian parliament that his organization uses a variety of intelligence sources to identify and monitor Bitcoin transactions and has already used the information as a resource in criminal prosecutions of money launderers. Though Australia is the only nation to have publicly acknowledged Bitcoin tracking, other nations are likely to also track citizens&rsquo; use of crypto currencies to varying degrees.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Bitcoin is not illegal,&rdquo; according to an unnamed<a href="http://cur.lv/7soni"> source</a> at the Central Bank of Cyprus. This comes as no surprise, as Cyprus has long been considered a favorable country by those looking to launder or hide money and Bitcoin provides a handy vector by which illicit funds can be safely moved in or out. The Mediterranean country has struggled in recent years with staggering debt and unemployment levels left over from the 2008-2009 financial crisis. The volume of foreign-owned assets held in the country prompted its government to declare a one-time levy (AKA theft) on deposits held in Cypriot banks in 2013. Cyprus&rsquo; wealth tax is just the kind of government overreach that has made Bitcoin very popular among crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0l">Bitcoin Regulation Update- 02/28/14</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Jason M. Tyra</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 05:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Are there any Ripplers in Ukraine/Russia?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr0p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I know this is kind of out of character for me but the world is dangerously getting close to a wider conflict that casts a shadow over the entirety of humanity right now and we ought to expect a network of people as both wide scope and involved in trading as ours ought to have a wide array of contacts on both possible sides.</p> <p>if </p> <p>1) Any of your ripple-using contacts are in Russia</p> <p>2) Any of your ripple-using contacts are in the Ukraine</p> <p>please post in this thread.</p> <p>We won't know what we can accomplish, how powerful this network is, here, until we try.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0p">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0p">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[India Under Bitcoin Regulation? Or Not?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr0q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Recently in December 2013, the Indian Central Bank (Reserve Bank of India, RBI) decided to not regulate, and stated clearly that they lacked expert knowledge on the subject at that time. So they cautioned people not to trade in Bitcoin or any other similar crypto-currency. A few days after, one exchange and a Bitcoin information (and dust holder) site closed down, BuySellBitCo.in and rbitco.in, respectively. These actions were undertaken by the RBI&rsquo;s own Enforcement Department (ED), which conducted the search and closure operations on two properties. These incidents occurred immediately after the following RBI announcement. &ldquo;Regulation comes only when people are doing certain business and we come to understand that something wrong is happening. First of all we don&rsquo;t understand [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0q">India Under Bitcoin Regulation? Or Not?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0q"><img width="558" height="306" src="http://cur.lv/7wr0r" alt="Bitcoin India"></a><p><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0q" title="click to read"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr0r" width="558" height="306" alt="India Under Bitcoin Regulation? Or Not? post image"></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Recently in December 2013, the Indian Central Bank (<a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0s">Reserve Bank of India, RBI</a>) decided to not regulate, and stated clearly that they lacked expert knowledge on the subject at that time. So they cautioned people <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0t">not to trade in Bitcoin</a> or any other similar crypto-currency. A few days after, one exchange and a Bitcoin information (and dust holder) site <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0u">closed down</a>, BuySellBitCo.in and rbitco.in, respectively. These actions were undertaken by the RBI&rsquo;s own <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0v">Enforcement Department</a> (ED), which conducted the search and closure operations on <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0w">two properties</a>. These incidents occurred immediately after the following RBI announcement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Regulation comes only when people are doing certain business and we come to understand that something wrong is happening. First of all we don&rsquo;t understand this subject.&rdquo; ~ <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0x">KC Chakrabarty, RBI deputy governor</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">This heavy-handed approach came with only the bank&rsquo;s statement that crypto-currency was to be free within India, unregulated, but free.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0y"><img alt="RBI-ED sealed the home of Nilam Doctor during the raid conducted on 26th December 2013" src="http://cur.lv/7wr0z" width="264" height="397"></a><p>RBI-ED sealed the home of Nilam Doctor during the raid conducted on 26th December 2013</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr10">RBI</a> has no plans to come up with a regulatory framework for Bitcoins, the virtual currency, which has risen sharply in value in the past few months, a top official said.&rdquo;~ <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr0x">The Times of India</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">You may guess that depends on one&rsquo;s given definition of &lsquo;free&rsquo;. With the world&rsquo;s second largest population at <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr11">1.237 billion</a>, nearly the majority of citizens in India are amongst <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr12">the unbanked</a>, crypto-currency could do very well to get a proper foothold within the Indian sub-continent. An excellent piece on the regulatory framework within India and how it relates to Bitcoin and crypto-currency can be found <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr13">here</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Summarizing that crypto-currency, under current regulation and legal framework, cannot be regulated, though with new regulation it may yet come under the umbrella of the political and banking powers. The RBI-ED then requested information on what these businesses actually do, the same businesses that they had just forced to close down. One of the affected businesses (rbitco.in), a website that explained the basics of Bitcoin and allowed registered customers to deposit &lsquo;dust&rsquo; Bitcoin that customers gained via visiting various &lsquo;free Bitcoin&rsquo; websites and promotions. The site allowed people to withdraw their dust once their account acquired a total of 0.5 or more. We can reveal that one of the individuals who had their house raided and closed (Nilam Doctor) ran this particular website, and after the property seizures the ED forwarded these questions.</p>
<ol><li>
<p dir="ltr">The official location of your company in India and the details of the company</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">The details of your clients and their KYC</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">The details of the sale and purchase of the Bitcoin.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">The details of your employees in India.</p>
</li>
</ol><p dir="ltr">In summary, the site neither sold nor purchased any Bitcoin, and it was run by a single person (Nilam), and KYC was registered emails (seeing as customers only deposited dust and then withdrew their own dust once it accumulated to the required amount). Could it be drawn from these questions that the RBI-ED in fact knew nothing about the investigation and closures they were enacting? Who was pulling the strings if a law enforcement department can be sent off with no investigation or any pre-knowledge of what they are doing?</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr14">Bitcoin Alliance India</a> (BAI) and Bitcoin community members discussed the issue and released a <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr15">press release</a> with regards to the RBI and RBI-ED approaches towards crypto-currency and the legitimacy of a free market. Nishith Desai of <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr16">Nishith Desai Associates</a> explains the illegality of Bitcoins within India post RBI-ED invasion, in that Bitcoin (in India) <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr17">is not illegal</a>, yet the governmental authorities have the responsibility to warn national residents of the dangers inherent within the Bitcoin economy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nilam Doctor has advocated for bitcoin through his media presence, <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr18">Paying in a different coin</a>, <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr19">Viable and attractive bitcoin</a> and <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1a">Towards a trading platform</a>. He also contested for the Bitcoin Foundation <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1b">individual seat</a>; transcript is available <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1c">here</a>.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1d"><img alt="Nilam Doctor - bitcoin pro India" src="http://cur.lv/7wr1d" width="183" height="183"></a><p>Nilam Doctor &ndash; Bitcoin Savant</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">He has been an outspoken pro-active Bitcoin supporter and advisory expert, and one of the individuals accosted has informed us that to date, the BAI are now waiting for the conclusion of an RBI central meeting with regards towards Bitcoin and their &lsquo;illegality&rsquo; and function within India. This meeting was to have occurred two weeks ago; the BAI and related Bitcoin experts and community participants are awaiting the RBI&rsquo;s conclusion to this meeting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">RBI was also issued a <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1e">letter</a> by Venugopal for assistance deciding about bitcoin&rsquo;s fate, but the BAI have been waiting for nearly a month for a response. Naavi.org (Vijayashankar Na) also published some <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1f">articles on bitcoin</a> during the RBI-ED inquiries. In personal correspondence on the ongoing situation within India, Nilam Doctor informed us that they recently opened his sealed property in India, for the purposes of <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1g">searching for bitcoin related money laundering</a> documents and similar incriminating materials.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Needless to say, they found nothing but decided to take 2x 240 MB HDD&rsquo;s (last used in 1998), after only taking 50 days to decide to finally open the property. These incidents point to the fact that regardless of RBI&rsquo;s only <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1h">communication policies</a>, lack of knowledge and experience within Bitcoin and the related space, the central bank of India used its law enforcement department to close businesses without any prior knowledge of the business activities, nor any expert knowledge of what Bitcoin entails. To help promote the accessibility and future of Bitcoin within India, Nilam Doctor is raising funds to help support Bitcoiners within India and to help educate the relevant authorities and governmental bodies within India, to explain the virtues and positives that can be gained from Bitcoin adoption. Key features to address during the visit to India:</p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr">To form Bitcoin Foundation (India) as a non-profit organization in India.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Hold meeting with senior government offices in major cities.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Hold meet-ups with pro-bitcoiners in Bangalore, Mumbai, New Delhi, Pune, Hyderabad, Jaipur, Ahmedabad, Calcutta, Nagpur.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Create awareness to the benefits for general public to use virtual currencies.</p>
</li>
</ul><p dir="ltr">During the tour to India, he will publish weekly reports of the development here on Bitcoin Magazine.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the most recent article from the <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1i">Sunday Guardian</a>, Nilam Doctor has been portrayed as the <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr1j">Master of Bitcoin</a> (in India) by the ED, clearly showing a strong lack of understanding of the concept behind decentralization and what Bitcoin really is.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>If you wish to contribute to the Bitcoin movement within India then please feel free to donate: (1BfindEetm8qpwJH2M7Ht7rgmLztwpX83P). When 40 BTC is raised Nilam will tour India, visiting the relevant authorities and establishments on behalf of Bitcoiners as a whole, and especially those within India. He has informed us that he will keep us updated on all progress. Nilam can be contacted directly via (nilamdoc AT gmail.com). Nilam is a Lifetime member of the Bitcoin Foundation, one of the Founders &amp; Directors of the Bitcoin Foundation India (chapter) and a Bitcoin Exchange developer.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7wr0q">India Under Bitcoin Regulation? Or Not?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Joel Dalais</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 04:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[In response to Senator Manchin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7uv18]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Dear Senator Manchin cc: Secretary Lew, Chairwoman Yellen, Commissioner Curry, Acting Chairman Wetjen, Chairman Gruenberg, Chairwoman White I understand and appreciate where you are coming from with your recent letter about Bitcoin, and I agree about the fundamental issues you address regarding the financial security of our country and the protection of hard-working Americans. As a US Marine Corps veteran of the Iraq war and a small business owner, these are values I share. Before I really understood Bitcoin, I had the same concerns that it was a get-rich-quick scheme for speculators and a currency only suited for nefarious individuals. But then I learned about the true brilliance underneath Bitcoin &ndash; the Blockchain &ndash; and this new understanding changed my [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7uv18">In response to Senator Manchin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7uv18"><img width="990" height="350" src="http://cur.lv/7uv19" alt="Photo of Senator Joe Manchin 2011"></a><p>Dear Senator Manchin</p>
<p>cc: Secretary Lew, Chairwoman Yellen, Commissioner Curry, Acting Chairman Wetjen, Chairman Gruenberg, Chairwoman White</p>
<p>I understand and appreciate where you are coming from with your recent letter about Bitcoin, and I agree about the fundamental issues you address regarding the financial security of our country and the protection of hard-working Americans. As a US Marine Corps veteran of the Iraq war and a small business owner, these are values I share. Before I really understood Bitcoin, I had the same concerns that it was a get-rich-quick scheme for speculators and a currency only suited for nefarious individuals.</p>
<p>But then I learned about the true brilliance underneath Bitcoin &ndash; the Blockchain &ndash; and this new understanding changed my opinion. I urge you to consider the gravity of this innovation, which in my opinion is on par with the internet itself, and my hope is that instead of prohibition, you will champion an environment conducive to the incredible potential prosperity it makes possible.</p>
<p>Let me address your specific concerns and then I&rsquo;ll share why the Blockchain itself really changed my mind.</p>
<h2>Concern #1: Bitcoin is a haven for scams and black market sales and helps criminals to hide from law enforcement.</h2>
<p>Let&rsquo;s first agree that despite laws and regulations, there will always be some people who engage in malicious activity. Since that is the case, the key question is how Bitcoin compares to other currencies, and how it intersects with criminal behavior.</p>
<p>Yes, Bitcoin enables frictionless transfer of money over the internet and the transactions are irreversible. But they are not anonymous. The blockchain is in fact a publicly visible ledger, in which all transactions are completely visible to everyone. Transactions are pseudonymous, meaning that the sender and receiver are labeled with an address that can be used to connect them to their identity. Before these concepts were widely understood (and it became public knowledge that the NSA has access to all of the information coming in and out of our computers) it appeared as though Bitcoin was a great tool for illicit activities. But now, law enforcement agencies have suggested that Bitcoin could actually be beneficial to their investigations &ndash; by subpoenaing ISP records to demonstrate ownership of a Bitcoin wallet and combining that information with the records in the public blockchain, law enforcement can actually provide evidence of criminal activity &ndash; evidence that the blockchain itself will never allow to be destroyed. What happened with the Silk Road is an excellent example of the transparency of the system supporting efficient action from law enforcement and it has since become understood that Bitcoin is actually a very poor vehicle for illicit activity.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s look at the numbers. Before they were shut down by authorities, the Silk Road and other illicit drug markets combined handled about <a title="Lightspeed Venture Partners: About half a percent of Bitcoin transactions are to buy drugs." href="http://cur.lv/75g3p" target="_blank">$50M in annual sales</a>, which seems like a big number. But for context, it only accounts for .01% of the international drug trade annually (based on an estimated annual worldwide drug trade of <a title="CNBC: Global drugs trade 'as strong as ever' as fight fails" href="http://cur.lv/7uv1a" target="_blank">around $435B</a>). And for a little more context, the Bitcoin network handles about $10B in annualized transaction volume, which means only .5% of Bitcoin transactions went through these black market exchanges. So it turns out that the amount of illicit activity conducted in Bitcoin is really quite small, no matter how it&rsquo;s measured.</p>
<p>I shared your concern about the potential for hackers and scammers to steal Bitcoins from average folks like myself. But then I learned about the two aspects that make the Bitcoin protocol more secure than anything we have seen before: #1) It is maintained by a massive decentralized network of computers in which no single computer can decide it wants to alter or break the rules, and if it tried it&rsquo;s work effort would simply be rejected by the rest of the network. As long as at least 50% of of those participating are doing so without bad intentions, all goes smoothly. But even if a bad actor comes along and spends hundreds of millions of dollars in hardware to control more than half of the network, their power would be limited to reversing a transaction within 10 minutes of it being initiated. #2) It uses a &ldquo;push&rdquo; system whereas most traditional financial transactions use a &ldquo;pull&rdquo; method. In traditional transactions I hand over my personal and banking information and trust that the business I am transacting with will only take the amount of money we agreed to and will keep my private information safe. This method has proven again and again to be profoundly vulnerable to hackers; just recently hackers stole the personal information of 70 million Target customers. Bitcoin&rsquo;s &ldquo;push&rdquo; system means that I, as the consumer, am able to send the money for the transaction to the business directly without revealing any of my personal information and I have complete control over the amount that is sent.</p>
<h2>Concern #2: Bitcoin is highly unstable, disruptive to the economy, and is being banned by other countries.</h2>
<p>Describing Bitcoin&rsquo;s exchange price as unstable is a fair characterization, but there are several factors to consider for a more broad understanding. First, like most currencies, it&rsquo;s price has been growing more stable as it&rsquo;s market cap has increased and, according to the Washington Post, it is &ldquo;highly likely&rdquo; that Bitcoin&rsquo;s price will stabilize over time. And for a little more context, Bitcoin&rsquo;s price is in fact less unstable than <a title="The Cato Institute: The Troubled Currencies Project" href="http://cur.lv/7uv1b" target="_blank">many other national currencies</a> with annual inflation rates of 12% (Egypt), 54% (Argentina) or even 300% (Venezuela). Second, viewed as an investment, Bitcoin was a big winner in the past year, increasing in value by at least a factor of ten. Third, Bitcoin holds the promise of a new kind of economy, one that offers much more stability than our current system. While there will be some rockiness in the road to getting there, it&rsquo;s potential is far more stable than the system we have now which has required our central bank inflate our money supply by more than $80,000,000,000 per month for years to support the continuing operation of our largest banks. Finally, despite it&rsquo;s price fluctuations, Bitcoin has proven to be incredibly resilient. Even with all of the market moving news recently &ndash; the possible theft or loss of around <a title="The Daily Beast: Inside Japan&rsquo;s Bitcoin Heist" href="http://cur.lv/7uv1c" target="_blank">850,000 Bitcoins and the collapse of the once largest exchange</a> &ndash; the price has recovered within a few days, climbing above $550 already. This is just the most recent example of many that illustrate the incredible resilience of the Bitcoin protocol itself and the longterm bullishness on the part of its supporters and users.</p>
<p>Your concern that the deflationary nature of Bitcoin&rsquo;s value will encourage hoarding also makes sense, especially since some of the largest proponents in Bitcoin have admitted to hoarding their holdings. However, <a title="MIT Technology Review: Show Me the Bitcoins" href="http://cur.lv/7gsrk" target="_blank">MIT has just released a report</a> that dispels these fears in which they assert that the vast majority of new Bitcoins are spent (circulated into the economy) within 24 hours.</p>
<p>And as far as Bitcoin being disruptive to our economy, I enthusiastically say &ndash; yes please! Our manufacturing base has been <a title='Zero Hedge: The Chart That No "US Manufacturing Renaissance" Believer Wants To See' href="http://cur.lv/7uv1d" target="_blank">almost completely off-shored</a> and our actual unemployment rate is <a title="U-6 Total unemployed, plus all persons marginally attached to the labor force, plus total employed part time for economic reasons, as a percent of the civilian labor force plus all persons marginally attached to the labor force" href="http://cur.lv/7uv1e" target="_blank">staggeringly high</a>. If you ask me, our economy needs some disrupting, and Bitcoin is just the ticket to bring about the positive change we so desperately need.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is highly beneficial to legitimate businesses. Business owners appreciate the financial advantages of Bitcoin &ndash; frictionless transactions that are safe, fast and good for the bottom line. Bitcoin transactions are virtually free compared to the two to four percent charged for an average credit or debit card transaction, which amounts to huge savings for businesses. It also reduces costs for consumers, as observed by former Treasury Secretary Larry Summers who recently said, &ldquo;It seems bizarre that at this late date, one has to pay as much as one does to use a debit card or to get cash from an ATM or to transfer money to one&rsquo;s child living abroad.&rdquo; He went on to say, &ldquo;Very serious economists thought that the Internet was going to be no more important than the fax machine, so I&rsquo;m not willing to dismiss Bitcoin,&rdquo; and called it a &ldquo;very, very important development.&rdquo;</p>
<p>I honestly don&rsquo;t really understand why you are looking to China and other countries for their position on Bitcoin. China also bans Twitter, YouTube and Facebook, all very significant tools for the sharing of information and valuable parts of the American economy. I&rsquo;m grateful to live in a country that values innovation and freedom and I hope that our policies will continue to reflect these values. I think the larger concern in this respect is that as Bitcoin is banned in other countries, businesses will leave those countries, looking for a place that embraces innovation. Countries that appreciate and embrace the value of the blockchain are going to be the home to billions of dollars in new economic activity. But don&rsquo;t take my word for it &ndash; consider the wisdom of 20-year Wall Street veteran Bruce Fenton who says that countries that ban or over-regulate Bitcoin will suffer &ldquo;fewer startups. A drain of top talent. Jobs and opportunities pushed overseas.&rdquo; Or the inventor of Netscape, the first web browser, Marc Andreesen who said, &ldquo;the amount of hardware and innovation that is put behind it is going to be gigantic.&rdquo; In other words, Bitcoin isn&rsquo;t just an economic boon, it&rsquo;s a job creator and we don&rsquo;t want to miss out on the prosperity it will create by banning or over-regulating it in it&rsquo;s early days.</p>
<p>That something is unregulated isn&rsquo;t, in and of itself, evidence that it needs to be regulated. Bitcoin is revolutionary exactly because of it&rsquo;s transparent and open nature, and, for the first time enables a market to be authentically regulated directly by consumers themselves.</p>
<h2>The Blockchain is what it&rsquo;s really all about.</h2>
<p>Bitcoin was just the first &ndash; a proof of concept &ndash; of a growing and dynamic market of blockchains designed to take advantage of the shared computational resources of people around the planet to encourage social improvement and positive change in a variety of ways. What has really blown my mind about Bitcoin isn&rsquo;t the currency itself, it&rsquo;s the technology it introduced. The blockchain can be applied to any system of transactions and it&rsquo;s structure of incentivized, distributed computing can have far reaching benefits. Here are some of my favorite examples:</p>
<p>PrimeCoin is being used to find new prime numbers. SolarCoin incentivizes the adoption of alternative energy. CureCoin is distributing the work of protein folding to help cancer researchers find a cure. Permacredits support the building of permaculture developments, backed by real commodities like housing, agriculture and business.</p>
<p>My company is in the design and manufacturing business &ndash; and I have been very unhappy with the two options currently available to me to make our products; we could either manufacture overseas where questionable labor practices, unregulated toxic materials, and big quality control issues dominate or we could be essentially priced-out of the marketplace by choosing to manufacture domestically and responsibly. We are currently developing a blockchain called Makercoin &ndash; it&rsquo;s purpose is to encourage collaborative development of goods and to decentralize, distribute &amp; localize manufacturing. It&rsquo;s end goal is to capture the creativity and innovation of the brightest minds in design and bring manufacturing back into our local communities, rather than simply where the cheapest and most exploitable labor is concentrated.</p>
<p>Marc Andreesen is convinced that the technology behind Bitcoin is as significant as the web, saying, &ldquo;Bitcoin, or cryptocurrency, the general concept is the first thing I&rsquo;ve described &lsquo;like the Internet&rsquo; since the Internet. So I&rsquo;ve been waiting 20 years to be able to say, &ldquo;Ahaaa this is like the Internet,&rdquo; and this is the first one that I&rsquo;ve seen.&rdquo;</p>
<p>My hope in writing this letter is that you will reconsider your position, and welcome the next technological revolution by advocating for policy that supports an environment of innovation and prosperity for all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7uv18">In response to Senator Manchin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Devon Read</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Added OTASCIIArmor.hpp so OT builds w/ keyring ON.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Added OTASCIIArmor.hpp so OT builds w/ keyring ON.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Added OTASCIIArmor.hpp so OT builds w/ keyring ON.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 21:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[OT wasn't building when keyring configured on.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1l]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>OT wasn't building when keyring configured on.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>OT wasn't building when keyring configured on.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Demonoid.me]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvf8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[We will rebuild! Coming back soon, please check back later. Thanks for your visit!! Donate bitcoins: 169zefQKDhfouLXwyk8QAfqeYHPVeGyKYs How to get bitcoins?]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Acknowledgement (data networks) - Wikipedia, the free ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2j(data_networks)]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[In data networking, an acknowledgement (or acknowledgment) is a signal passed between communicating processes or computers to signify acknowledgement, or receipt of ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[fixes for Android res/raw folder (no subfolders.)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1m]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>fixes for Android res/raw folder (no subfolders.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>fixes for Android res/raw folder (no subfolders.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 12:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #37 from da2ce7/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1n]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #37 from da2ce7/master

Open Transactions Header Clean-up. Tested successfully on Mac/Mountain Lion/chai4/C++03</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #37 from da2ce7/master

Open Transactions Header Clean-up. Tested successfully on Mac/Mountain Lion/chai4/C++03</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 11:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[add &lt;cstdlib&gt; to OTLog.hpp]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>add <cstdlib> to OTLog.hpp</cstdlib></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>add <cstdlib> to OTLog.hpp</cstdlib></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[fix for TR1 with shared_ptr]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>fix for TR1 with shared_ptr</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>fix for TR1 with shared_ptr</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[add &lt;cerrno&gt; to OTLog.hpp]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>add <cerrno> to OTLog.hpp</cerrno></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>add <cerrno> to OTLog.hpp</cerrno></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[add &lt;cinttypes&gt; to &lt;MemoryWrapper.hpp&gt;]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1r]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>add <cinttypes> to <memorywrapper></memorywrapper></cinttypes></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>add <cinttypes> to <memorywrapper></memorywrapper></cinttypes></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[add colour to test output]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1s]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>add colour to test output</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>add colour to test output</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[fix assert fail where script allows blank message]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>fix assert fail where script allows blank message</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>fix assert fail where script allows blank message</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[no C++11 fixes]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1u]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>no C++11 fixes</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>no C++11 fixes</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[OTLog now logs, once initalized]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1v]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>OTLog now logs, once initalized</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>OTLog now logs, once initalized</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[OTAssert and Lucre Fix]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1w]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>OTAssert and Lucre Fix</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>OTAssert and Lucre Fix</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[now working linux]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1x]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>now working linux</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>now working linux</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[fix swig exports for linux]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1y]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>fix swig exports for linux</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>fix swig exports for linux</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[complete windows]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr1z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>complete windows</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>complete windows</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[fix build warnings]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr20]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>fix build warnings</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>fix build warnings</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[started work on otapi]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr21]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>started work on otapi</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>started work on otapi</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[windows OT (no swig) complete]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr22]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>windows OT (no swig) complete</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>windows OT (no swig) complete</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[completed header cleanup for otlib (windows)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr23]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>completed header cleanup for otlib (windows)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>completed header cleanup for otlib (windows)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Jupiter Colony]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgc7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Jupiter Broadcasting Community Resources]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[比特信 BitMessage]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yj8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[&#27604;&#29305;&#20449;&#65288;Bitmessage&#65289;&#26159;&#19968;&#31181;&#29992;&#26469;&#21521;&#21478;&#19968;&#20010;&#20154;&#25110;&#32773;&#20854;&#23427;&#22810;&#20010;&#35746;&#38405;&#32773;&#21457;&#36865;&#21152;&#23494;&#28040;&#24687;&#30340;&#21327;&#35758;&#12290;&#23427;&#26159;&#19968;&#20010;p2p&#30340;&#21435;&#20013;&#24515;&#21270;&#21644;&#26080;&#39035;&#31532;&#19977;&#26041;&#25552;&#20379; ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Ghost in the Machine at MtGox]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7uv45]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Getting deeper into the ongoing investigation of what's going on with MtGox: more pieces are falling into place.  <p></p> Speculation into the mishaps are presented by <b>Adam B. Levine</b> and <b>Napoleon Cole</b> among others.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 03:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Your Central Bank Steals Your Money. Here’s How.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twry]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Your Central Bank Steals Your Money. Here&rsquo;s how. We operate in a particular financial paradigm: a centralised order with extraordinary power concentrated at the top. However, Bitcoin has created what was once unimaginable: a working, resilient and voluntary financial system with power distributed evenly according to contribution. It may or may not be possible to reconcile the legacy financial order with this new system. The jury&rsquo;s still out. Even without reconciliation one would assume that the majority would flock to the new system. In flattening the financial structure you offer a greater value proposition to the majority. Assuming, of course, the majority can see that value proposition. But it is not always obvious. It would be if people understood that [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twry">Your Central Bank Steals Your Money. Here&rsquo;s How.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7twry"><img width="507" height="338" src="http://cur.lv/7twrz" alt="E008582"></a><p dir="ltr"><strong>Your Central Bank Steals Your Money. Here&rsquo;s how.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">We operate in a particular financial paradigm: a centralised order with extraordinary power concentrated at the top.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Bitcoin has created what was once unimaginable: a working, resilient and voluntary financial system with power distributed evenly according to contribution.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It may or may not be possible to reconcile the legacy financial order with this new system. The jury&rsquo;s still out. Even without reconciliation one would assume that the majority would flock to the new system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In flattening the financial structure you offer a greater value proposition to the majority. Assuming, of course, the majority can see that value proposition. But it is not always obvious. It would be if people understood that their central bank stole from them.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;At the top of the existing structure is the central bank. They do indeed steal from you. They steal from you in disgusting quantities and every day. The theft is insidious and indirect. So, it is not obvious. But the theft is still very real.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The theft is not particularly complicated. Although it is dressed in confusing language: &lsquo;quantitative easing&rsquo;, &lsquo;operation twist&rsquo;, and &lsquo;bailout&rsquo;. Realizing how the theft works is important.</p>
<p dir="ltr">When the methods of the thief (central bank) are understood, the value proposition for the Bitcoin system becomes much more obvious.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Culturally and collectively we seem to instinctively understand that &lsquo;printing money&rsquo; is bad. Arbitrarily increasing the supply of currency is incredibly detrimental to an economy. In essence this is what your central bank does. But why is it detrimental?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Money is not wealth. Goods and services are wealth. Money is how you represent and transfer that wealth. Printing money does not increase wealth (the quantity of available goods and services). Printing money simply divides the existing wealth into a greater number of pieces.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is because the dollar you hold does not represent your share of the available goods and services. Rather, it only represents your share of the total money supply. That is the key.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Life is Like Monopoly</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/7tws0">Paul Mckeever&rsquo;s</a> Monopoly game <a href="http://cur.lv/7tws1">analogy</a> offers a useful illustration. Take four players in a monopoly game. Each player, including the banker, has $100. The total money supply is therefore: $400. Each player has a &frac14; share of the money supply.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The banker suddenly issues himself an extra $400. The total money supply is now $800.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The banker has $500 (this is now 5/8ths of the total money supply). Each of the 3 other players is still left only with their $100 of savings. This now only represents 1/8th of the total money supply.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Each of the other players has effectively had 1/2 of their money stolen. This was done when the banker increased the money supply and gave the new money to himself. He has unjustly enriched himself at your direct expense.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Each of the other 3 players money has had &nbsp;1/8th of value absorbed directly into the banker&rsquo;s newly issued money, moving him to 5/8ths of the money supply.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The effect would be exactly the same if the banker had instead kept his $100, not introduced any new money into the system, reached over and taken dollars from each player. Of course, that theft would be too obvious. You&rsquo;d slap him.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notice that the total wealth (available properties) in the Monopoly game never increases. The only thing that increases is the banker&rsquo;s capacity to purchase that wealth (properties) over the other players.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The act of arbitrarily increasing the amount of money in circulation simply transfers the capacity to purchase the existing wealth from those who hold money (workers and savers), to those who create additional money (bankers). The banker&rsquo;s new money absorbs that stolen money.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a neat trick and a very interesting form of thievery.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Of course, it is a zero sum game. The central bank gains directly at your expense, whereas real wealth increases benefit everyone. But they can only ever occur from productivity, creating more goods and services of higher value at a lower cost.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>How does Bitcoin Solve This?</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Quite simply, no one can arbitrarily increase the supply of Bitcoins and steal from you in this way. The central bank&rsquo;s power to increase the supply of money and give it to themselves and their friends is gone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The money creation process instead mimics the mining of a natural resource like Gold. Entrepreneurs must efficiently organise land, labour and capital to create the tools needed to dig Bitcoins out of the digital crust. It is an expensive and risky exercise.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoins take time, effort, resources and sacrifice to dig up from the virtual ground. So it is true that over the next 100+ years those who mine Bitcoin will be creating new money. However, and, most importantly, it is not out of thin air &ndash; at zero cost.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The newly created Bitcoins will absorb value from the existing Bitcoins in circulation. This is true. But they will do this completely predictably over time and at a decreasing rate, minimising the negative effects on those who hold Bitcoins.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Most importantly however, the people who want to dig the Bitcoins out of the virtual crust must first spend Bitcoins and take on risk in order to do this. This money creation is not arbitrary. The central bank takes on no risk and increases the supply of money at no cost.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And of course, eventually, one day in 2140, the creation of new Bitcoins will stop and that is all there can ever be, mathematically. Can we say the same of the US dollar?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is often understood to be both dangerous and an unreliable store of value. In the worst logical leap it is claimed that Bitcoin is as worthless as centrally issued fiat paper. This accusation is more outrageous and egregious when one understands the particular aspects of how central banks steal your money.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twry">Your Central Bank Steals Your Money. Here&rsquo;s How.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Tristan Winters</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The 8BITMIME extension]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2i]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[D. J. Bernstein Internet mail SMTP: Simple Mail Transfer Protocol The 8BITMIME extension Users send billions of 8-bit messages every year. As far as I know, all ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Sex &amp; Science Hour #3 &ndash; SaDOGEi Nakamoto]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7tws3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Stephanie Murphy</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin to Shake up Austin, Texas Next Week]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twsh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>On Thursday, March 6, Bitcoiners from across the United States and around the world will gather in Austin, Texas for the first Texas Bitcoin Conference. Attendees will have a stellar line-up of speakers to look forward to with ample time to network and take part in over 30 workshops and tutorials. The Texas Bitcoin Conference Team issued the following press release: Mt. Gox and the Future of Bitcoin Demystified Texas Bitcoin Conference Premier Two-Day Event March 5th and 6th 2014 Features over 30 workshops and tutorials for consumer friendly Bitcoin adoption, a $1 Million Hackathon for advancing the development of Distributed Autonomous Applications (DAA), A diverse list of distinguished speakers. The conference will be making history in the arts with [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twsh">Bitcoin to Shake up Austin, Texas Next Week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7twsh"><img width="270" height="270" src="http://cur.lv/7twsi" alt="texas-bitcoin-conference-logo1-270x270"></a><p dir="ltr">On Thursday, March 6, Bitcoiners from across the United States and around the world will gather in Austin, Texas for the first Texas Bitcoin Conference. Attendees will have a stellar line-up of speakers to look forward to with ample time to network and take part in over 30 workshops and tutorials.</p>
<p>The Texas Bitcoin Conference Team issued the following press release:</p>
<p><strong>Mt. Gox and the Future of Bitcoin Demystified</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Texas Bitcoin Conference</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Premier Two-Day Event</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>March 5th and 6th 2014</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Features over 30 workshops and tutorials for consumer friendly Bitcoin adoption, a $1 Million Hackathon for advancing the development of Distributed Autonomous Applications (DAA), A diverse list of distinguished speakers. The conference will be making history in the arts with the world&rsquo;s first Bitcoin-exclusive concert featuring Grammy-nominated Carolyn Malachi. Bitcoin will be used as a force for good at this event with all concert proceeds supporting Bitcoin accepting charities!</p>
<p dir="ltr">AUSTIN, DATE &mdash; The Texas Bitcoin Conference www.texasbitcoinconference.com is rapidly approaching. The event will be held March 5th and 6th at the Technology and Conference Center at the Circuit of the Americas Formula 1 complex (9201 Circuit of the Americas Blvd., Austin, TX. 78617).</p>
<p dir="ltr">In light of the recent Mt. Gox debacle, the Texas Bitcoin Conference has added a &ldquo;Mt. Gox Explained&rdquo; panel discussion on March 5th. The recent events surrounding Mt. Gox underscore the need for honest, transparent and auditable exchanges and Bitcoin endeavors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Texas Bitcoin Association looks forward to educating merchants, consumers and the curious public about Bitcoin adoption. Networking is a priority for the organization, with space and program time set aside for inventors, entrepreneurs, engineers and all attending to connect.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoin 2.0 Hackathon: Building Next Generation Decentralized Applications &amp; Protocols will take place both days. Teams will compete for more than $1 million in prizes and contracts in an event organized by the Mastercoin Foundation, Open-Transactions (Monetas), Ethereum, BitAngels, Ripple and others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Texas Bitcoin Conference will be making music history with the first ever BitCoinCert! www.bitcoincert.org The concert features Grammy-nominated Carolyn Malichi, the first known recording artist to accept Bitcoin payments for her music along with local favorites such as Eric Tessmer and Kalu James. The concert takes place Thursday, March 6th at 8:30 p.m. Volunteers are ready to help concertgoers new to Bitcoin quickly get empowered to purchase tickets with Crypto-currency. The suggested donation price is $25USD in Bitcoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Proceeds from the concert will support local and national service organizations. From a local perspective, the concert will support Without Regrets www.withoutregrets.org and Austin&rsquo;s own Capital Area Food Bank. The Capital Area Food Bank is a Federal Reserve of food pantries and food banks across Texas.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Three organizations powered solely by Bitcoin will also be featured beneficiaries, including Sean&rsquo;s Outpost homeless sanctuary in Florida, www.seansoutpost.com &nbsp;Bitcoin not Bombs www.bitcoinnotbombs.com &nbsp;and Fr33aid &nbsp;www.fr33aid.com Sean&rsquo;s Outpost founder Jason King &nbsp;is running an ultra-marathon across the country that began in Miami on Jan. 26. He is expected to make an appearance at the Texas Bitcoin Conference on March 6.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin as technology, Bitcoin as an ecomonic force, Bitcoin as a Force for Good. All aspects of this exciting community will be explored during the two day event.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For more information and ticket pricing, please visit the Texas Bitcoin Conference website, www.texasbitcoinconference.com</p>
<p dir="ltr"># # #</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twsh">Bitcoin to Shake up Austin, Texas Next Week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Elizabeth Ploshay</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 22:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Cooperation Within Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twsk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[The basis of Bitcoin is cooperation with other people and entities to achieve goals. Using consensus - not exactly unanimity - we can reach agreements using the tools we have within Bitcoin and protocols built on top of it.

<b>Ryan Nill</b> uses some real world examples of this while explaining how this works.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Visiting Author</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 21:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Do You Need Payment Protocol Support? – Now You Can Have It]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twt9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Last week BitPay launched a support platform for the Bitcoin Payment Protocol, working to make Bitcoin payments easier than ever for merchants and users. The payment protocol eliminates much of the human error in completing a bitcoin payment, while providing a streamlined approach to the transaction process. A user can simply click on the payment link or scan the QR-code and offers two payment choices, either &lsquo;pay&rsquo; or &lsquo;don&rsquo;t pay,&rsquo; which means that there is no need to copy the address and amount into their wallet. BitPay&rsquo;s Payment Protocol Support provides multiple solutions that reduce human error and make it easy for merchants to start accepting Bitcoin with BitPay. Payment Protocol Support will include Native Address Refund Support, Secure, Signed [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twt9">Do You Need Payment Protocol Support? &ndash; Now You Can Have It</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7twt9"><img width="950" height="350" src="http://cur.lv/7twta" alt="paymentProtocol"></a><p dir="ltr">Last week <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">BitPay</a> launched a support platform for the Bitcoin Payment Protocol, working to make Bitcoin payments easier than ever for merchants and users. The payment protocol eliminates much of the human error in completing a bitcoin payment, while providing a streamlined approach to the transaction process.</p>
<p>A user can simply click on the payment link or scan the QR-code and offers two payment choices, either &lsquo;pay&rsquo; or &lsquo;don&rsquo;t pay,&rsquo; which means that there is no need to copy the address and amount into their wallet. BitPay&rsquo;s Payment Protocol Support provides multiple solutions that reduce human error and make it easy for merchants to start accepting Bitcoin with BitPay.</p>
<p>Payment Protocol Support will include Native Address Refund Support, Secure, Signed Payment Requests, User Friendly QR Codes (BIP-73), and Direct Payment Communication; all aimed at making payments to BitPay merchants easier.</p>
<p><strong>Secure, Signed Payment Requests</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">The payment protocol also offers confidence to users that they are sending their payment to the intended recipient, which is made possible by optional SSL signatures (X.509 signatures) on payment requests. Because BitPay signs all payment requests, when using a wallet supported by the payment protocol (Bitcoin-QT and Android Bitcoin Wallet) the user will notice that BitPay is requesting payment for the transaction.</p>
<p>By establishing the party who is requesting payment, this helps ensure continued security of all bitcoin transactions simply because the user knows exactly who they are doing business with.</p>
<p><strong>Native Address Refund Support</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Through the Payment Protocol the wallet supplies a refund address in addition to the payment, eliminating the potential of error in refund situations. Native Address Refund Support is a streamlined approach to refunds that works on the block chain, with any wallet software and doesn&rsquo;t require the buyer to have a BitPay account. This ensures the accuracy of every bitcoin transaction and increases reliability between the buyer and the merchant.</p>
<p><strong>User Friendly QR Codes (BIP-73)</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">BitPay has also improved the usability of QR Codes for Bitcoin payments through the use of BIP-73. This user-friendly QR Code utilizes BIP-73 to reduce the information required for payment requests and reduce the density of each code. According to a recent article, less dense QR Codes are easier to use in low-light or from long distances. These lower density codes are normal HTTP URLs, offering an opportunity to provide additional information and instructions to users who don&rsquo;t already have a wallet installed on their device.</p>
<p>With BitPay, users and merchants alike can view both the backwards compatible, older QR Code as well as the newer payment protocol QR Code. Each invoice allows the user to toggle between the two codes by clicking or tapping directly on the QR Code. User-friendly QR Codes can help spread knowledge of Bitcoin by being able to provide additional information to users who scan each code. BitPay&rsquo;s support of BIP-73 will help create streamlined invoicing for merchants, making payments even more universal and easy to transact.</p>
<p><strong>Direct Payment Communication</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Another exciting aspect of the payment protocol is the elimination of the use of the mesh network to communicate a payment from sender to recipient. The Bitcoin mesh network serves two main purposes &ndash; communicating payments from sender to recipient and communicating payments from originators to miners. The payment protocol directly communicates payments from sender to recipient, which allows the mesh network to continually communicate transactions between originators and miners.</p>
<p>This means that the network can broadcast and ignore transactions without effecting interaction between the sender and recipient. According to a BitPay spokesperson, &ldquo;Direct Payment Communication allows for the emergence of a true market in transaction fees.&rdquo; The payment protocol helps improve Bitcoin&rsquo;s scalability by utilizing the mesh network to focus on those transactions that are profitable for miners, reducing the load on the mesh network.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>BitPay&rsquo;s Payment Protocol Support provides merchants and users with a streamlined approach to completing Bitcoin payments. These solutions will allow the Bitcoin community to continue its growth and rapid adoption, while providing a reliable platform that gives payment protocol support &ndash; making payments to merchants easier than before.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twt9">Do You Need Payment Protocol Support? &ndash; Now You Can Have It</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam Hofman</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 19:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripplesingapore.com launches fractional bullion bar product line to enhance bullion liquidity onto ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twtc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>On ripple you can buy any fraction of an ounce of gold, silver or platinum. However to increase total bullion liquidity on ripple ripplesingapore.com now directly sells newly issued XAU and XPT down to 1oz and down to 50oz for XAG. Ripple makes bullion money again. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700yl"> Bonface </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7twtc">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7twtc">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 19:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[PassportParking Becomes First Parking Company to Accept Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twtn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>CHARLOTTE, NC &mdash; PassportParking, Inc. announced a new service that allows customers to pay for parking with Bitcoin through its Mobile Pay service. Partnering with BitPay, a payment processor for digital currencies, PassportParking is the first company in the world to facilitate the acceptance of Bitcoin for metered parking spaces and off-street lots. PassportParking, Inc. delivers fully integrated cloud-based parking solutions using the latest technology and equipment to streamline the parking process. The company&rsquo;s decision to accept bitcoin benefits parking operators with near-zero merchant processing fees, which increases revenues without creating additional cost to parking customers. Paying with Bitcoin allows privacy-conscious customers to make secure and reliable payments, without having to share personal banking or credit card information. &ldquo;We make [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twtn">PassportParking Becomes First Parking Company to Accept Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/7twtn"><img width="842" height="277" src="http://cur.lv/7twto" alt="Passport-Parking-"></a><p dir="ltr"><strong>CHARLOTTE, NC</strong> &mdash; <a href="http://cur.lv/7lveg">PassportParking, Inc</a>. announced a new service that allows customers to pay for parking with Bitcoin through its Mobile Pay service. Partnering with <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">BitPay</a>, a payment processor for digital currencies, PassportParking is the first company in the world to facilitate the acceptance of Bitcoin for metered parking spaces and off-street lots.</p>
<p>PassportParking, Inc. delivers fully integrated cloud-based parking solutions using the latest technology and equipment to streamline the parking process. The company&rsquo;s decision to accept bitcoin benefits parking operators with near-zero merchant processing fees, which increases revenues without creating additional cost to parking customers. Paying with Bitcoin allows privacy-conscious customers to make secure and reliable payments, without having to share personal banking or credit card information.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We make it easy for businesses like the Passport Mobile Pay to accept bitcoin as a form of payment,&rdquo; said Stephanie Wargo, Vice President of Marketing for BitPay.</p>
<p>PassportParking&rsquo;s <a href="http://cur.lv/7twtp">Mobile Pay</a> service allows customers to pay for parking via mobile device, either with mobile app or by phone. Passport has partnered with BitPay to provide a seamless payment experience for its customers, providing a payment solution wherein customers using the mobile app will have the option of paying with Bitcoin.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7twtq">BitPay&rsquo;s Bitcoin Payment Gateway API</a> is the most advanced and reliable bitcoin-processing platform for e-commerce and brick-and-mortar merchants. In addition to eliminating chargebacks and lowering processing fees, BitPay also allows merchants like PassportParking to settle each transaction in USD and receive next-day payments directly into their bank account. This greatly decreases the merchant risk in regards to price volatility.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Brad Powers, Senior Developer at PassportParking and Project Lead for Passport&rsquo;s Bitcoin integration, &ldquo;Accepting bitcoin is just the latest example about how Passport uses cutting-edge technology to improve how customers can pay for parking.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The company combines cloud-based parking solutions with their Mobile Pay platform, providing a web-based console that allows for in-depth data analysis, real time reporting and rate management. For the customer, Mobile Pay enables fast and easy payment directly from any type of mobile phone, with cutting-edge technology that gives the customer the ability to start a parking session through app, SMS or phone call.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Passport will initially launch this service with a prominent parking operator in its hometown of Charlotte, NC. <a href="http://cur.lv/7twtr">Park Charlotte</a>, which operates parking lots in the Charlotte area, has announced they will begin using PassportParking&rsquo;s Bitcoin service in 2014. Providing parking facilities the ability to cut out the middleman and accept payment directly from customers is a win-win for companies and their customers.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Bitcoin is superior for online payments and today many traditional brick and mortar payments are moving online &ndash; you pay for your taxi using Square and for your parking using PassportParking,&rdquo; said Michael Gronager, COO of Payward. &ldquo;We have always used coins for parking so using bitcoin is the natural successor.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>About PassportParking</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">PassportParking, Inc (Passport) &ndash; headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina &ndash; is the industry&rsquo;s leading provider of integrated cloud-based parking solutions. The company provides the most advanced technology and equipment in an enterprise suite that allows parking providers and owners to manage parking and enforcement operations more effectively and efficiently. Passport is backed by a highly respected group of investors, including Grotech Ventures and Relevance Capital. For more information, please visit <a href="http://cur.lv/7twts">www.passportparking.com</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>About BitPay</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">BitPay is a Payment Service Provider (PSP) specializing in eCommerce, B2B, and enterprise solutions for virtual currencies. Visit <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">http://cur.lv/700yv</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/7twtn">PassportParking Becomes First Parking Company to Accept Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam Hofman</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 18:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ed &amp; Ethan&rsquo;s Live Bitcoin Report 4]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7twty]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ed And Ethan</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 18:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ten Skype alternatives with a hugely secure P2P platform ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yjm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[The original name for the platform was Sky Peer-to-Peer, which was then merged to make the name 'Skype'.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Kraken Halts USD Transactions, Asks Customers to Switch to Euros]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7soj8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7soj9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7soj8">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Something’s Not Right at ‘Gox]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sol5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[What in the world is going on at MT GOX?  After last nights <a href="http://cur.lv/7sol6">wild episode</a> we told you the party wasn't over, and here's the next installment in the ongoing drama.  <p></p>Things move fast in the world of Bitcoin and today LTB is pleased to present an interesting email, curated by <b>Charlie Schrem</b> describing some possible hypothesis for the trouble at MT GOX]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Charlie Shrem</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 21:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What Would Jeff Bezos Do?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7solc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[More and more merchants, especially eCommerce merchants, are accepting bitcoin as payment. Some of the larger merchants like Overstock have jumped on board, but everyone is waiting to see what Amazon will do with Bitcoin, if anything.

<b>Hayden Gill</b> explores some thoughts behind such an endeavor, and how that could be accomplished.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Hayden Gill</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E87 – The Captive and The Mountain]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sol6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to the Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin Show, or&nbsp;Subscribe to The LTB Network for free, and never miss an episode again! Shownotes for Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin Episode 87 &ndash; The Captive and the Mountain Segment 1 &ndash; Brooklyn Captive with Charlie Schrem, Andreas M. Antonopoulos, Stephanie Murphy and Adam B. Levine &ndash; RECORDED 2/20/2014 Highlights Include: [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 05:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there any trade bot for Ripple.com?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7soou]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I am not a good computer programmer. Is there a trade bot with API easily to plug in Ripple.com? I only set up the strategy and the trade bot will automatic execute the order? Thanks. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7soov"> spacetime2 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7soou">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7soou">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 23:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Trading bitcoin in Ripple.com is free. Why does Bitstamp want to be a gateway for Ripple?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7soox]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>You can trade bitcoin in Ripple.com almost at no fee. Why does Bitstamp want to be a gateway for Ripple.com? More and more people trade bitcoin in Ripple then they will not trade in Bitstamp at 0.5% fee. So Ripple ultimately kills Bitstamp business model. Does it make sense?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7soov"> spacetime2 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7soox">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7soox">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 22:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Contacting someone with Bitmessage.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sooy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>How do two people connect in Bitmessage? Does one have to tell the other an address to start things off? Is there some way two people can connect without first knowing the other's address?</p> <p>Edit - I was thinking it wouldn't be a good idea to send my address through unencrypted channels. I'm starting to think that this shouldn't be a concern. Is there any reason why I shouldn't just post a BM address here? Could it compromise the privacy of the message to do so?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7sooz"> btcnewbquestion </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sop0">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sooy">[8 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 21:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How do I get BTC into Ripple?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sopt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I told myself if the price dipped below 500 again I'd buy a decent amount and what do you know :). I bought on Coinbase and overall goal is to end up with Bitstamp:BTC.</p> <p>I know about DividendRippler and I love the idea, but I also know there is very little volume there and the rates are shaky at best. This is my first choice so far as I'm willing to provide liquidity to such an awesome gateway but I don't feel fully comfortable holding a majority of my BTCs in DividendRippler:BTC.</p> <p>I also know Bitstamp lets you buy XRP but I'm not willing to give out as much personal info as they want. Or maybe there's a way to do what I want without full verification?</p> <p>So what do? As far as I know, those are the best options atm but I made this post to see if I was missing something obvious. Any thoughts?</p> <p>Thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9w"> AlistorMcCoy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sopt">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sopt">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 08:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[New Android app for tracking currency price in Ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7soqh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7soqi"> p3bble </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7soqj">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7soqh">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 21:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin bounty for adding IPv6 support]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sorg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I'd like to try an experiment and set a bounty for adding IPv6 support to PyBitmessage. I will pay 0.015 BTC to whoever gets a pull request accepted which adds this. To claim the bounty add a comment to the pull request stating your preferred Bitcoin address. I'll only pay if the pull request gets accepted into the official repo and it does the following:</p> <ul><li>Connections can be made to IPv6 addresses</li> <li>It can listen on an IPv6 address for incoming connections</li> <li>It checks for the AAAA record in the DNS bootstrap request </li> <li>IPv6 addresses are forwarded to other peers in the addr message</li> <li>The IPv6 address for localhost and local networks are filtered out</li> </ul></div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorh"> farasep </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sori">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorg">[16 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 00:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Cryptocontracts Will Turn Law Into a Programming Language | Thought Infection]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sorj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sork">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorj">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 23:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Someone is stealing XRPs - Ripple Forum]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sorn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokl"> ThePiachu </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7soro">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorn">[14 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[API Broken?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sorq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>It appears as if the API is broken..........</p> <p>When calling api.sendMessage(address, subject, message) it errors with</p> <pre><code>API Error 0021: Unexpected API Failure - local variable 'encodingType' referenced before assignment </code></pre> <p>Looking at the output from the pyBitmessage running in a terminal window, it says the error is on line 906 of api.py but when I looked, there's no references to encodingType... any help would be greatly appreciated! (:</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorr"> doctorsn0w </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sors">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorq">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 03:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Building the Future: The Best Pitches From DeveloperWeek]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sorv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9w"> AlistorMcCoy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sorw">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sorv">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 06:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What happens to deleted messages]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sos9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hi, a noob here with a noob question :) What happens to deleted messages, do they dissapear from the blockchain? Or maybe they aren't even stored in a blockchain like cryptocurrency transactions?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7sosa"> dille71 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sosb">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sos9">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Centralized and decentralized mailing lists]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sot1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hi <a href="http://cur.lv/75g50">/r/bitmessage</a>.</p> <p>I am currently researching how to use Bitmessage's mailing list functionality for my upcoming master's thesis.</p> <p>Since I couldn't find any good comparisons of the two different types of mailing lists, I decided to inspect the wiki and the source to try to make my own comparison.</p> <p>I wrote about my findings here, and would be very glad if some of you would read it and tell me if I got it right or not. I would love some comments :-)</p> <p>Anyways, for those of you who are interested to read it: <a href="http://cur.lv/7sot2">http://cur.lv/7sot2</a></p> <p>Thank you!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700z2"> jesperbb </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sot3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sot1">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 14:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[USD Deposits Temporarily Disabled : Kraken]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sot4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sot5">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sot4">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 11:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is Ripple/ how do I get XRP?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7sot6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I just found out about ripple last Friday, and I do not completely understand the difference between ripple and other cryptocurrencies that use the block chain. I know that ripple is more than just XRP but can someone elaborate on this? Also where can I get XRP? I made a wallet and my address is rpN8uu1XrpgT5Q8iwS9BrKF8RwrusGp6zK </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7sot7"> redneckwonder </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7sot6">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7sot6">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 05:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Open XRP Talk: A Ripple Social Network]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvbh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vj"> busterzzz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvbi">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvbh">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 18:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA["Encryption key was requested earlier", says PyBM client. So was my message delivered or not?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvfb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Can someone kindly explain? Thanks in advance.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsw0"> pptyx </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfc">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfb">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 02:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Chief Cryptographer David Schwartz Talks About Malleability In Bitcoin | Newfination]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvfd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfe">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfd">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 00:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Implosion of Rippln - News - XRP Talk]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvfp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfq">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfp">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 19:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple Hub for Android [Updated 1.1] - Projects - XRP Talk]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvfr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfs">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvfr">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 19:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fees for bitcoind sendmany, limits for number of end addresses]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr24]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have two questions, both about <code>sendmany</code>.</p>

<p>First, is there any limit on how much transactions can I send with sendmany? (Apart from bash's limit with maximal parameter length.) Is sending about 500 transactions OK?</p>

<p>Second, what will be the fees used when I send a lot of transactions (and thus, probably creating a big transaction)?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Karel Bílek</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 18:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Modified Linux "compilation" instructions for Fedora 20/RedHat]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvg4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Not sure where to post this and creating a login on the wiki fails so I can't propose the change there.</p> <p>The instructions for Fedora and RedHat (and their variants) has the user create a static, permanent LD_LIBRARY_PATH variable. After fighting with this for a week on Fedora 20 and even going so far as to burn 2 days trying to rebuild a "non-hobbled" RPM, I finally tracked down the problem (it just wasn't using the variable) and the solution.</p> <p>Instead of setting s global/permanent variable, use a wrapper script and set the variable in a slightly different manner. The following will actually work:</p> <p>export LD_LIBRARY_PATH="/opt/openssl-compat-bitcoin/lib${LD_LIBRARY_PATH:+:$LD_LIBRARY_PATH}" /home/&lt;yourusername&gt;/PyBitmessage/src/bitmessagemain.py &gt; /dev/null 2&gt;&amp;1 &amp;</p> <p>Using the above code to set the variable...it actually uses the preferred/correct library. The second part (for anyone non-Linuxy) starts the process in the background and then dumps all output (STDERR and STDOUT) to /dev/null so you don't have a continual "waterfall" of output should you start the client from a shell prompt.</p> <p>If anyone would be willing to propose the change on the wiki/site, I'm SURE it would help others.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvg5"> DarkLight72 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvg6">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvg4">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 04:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Open Libernet: a Bitcoin-based fully encrypted mesh networking protocol]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvgd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yow"> galapag0 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvge">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgd">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 16:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Message latency (when growing the network)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvgf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Sending messages between firewalled clients currently seems to take a minute or 2 for several lines of text.</p> <p>Do we know how this is predicted to scale with more clients?</p> <p>If, say, mass-adoption were to occur - possibly by building a more advanced service on top of bitmessage - would we predict this latency to increase or decrease with number? (more contributing to the network, but more data to sync)</p> <p>Presuming this still all fits in 1 stream. No doubt multiple streams would complicate this answer.</p> <p>I guess this is still also presuming that all messages are of a "reasonable" length (a few thousand characters at most)</p> <p>How would this answer change if messages started becoming larger? (say 10x that size)</p> <p>Thanks :] xx</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgg"> ProPuke </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgf">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[PSA: peercover.com is scamming people]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7lvgi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgj"> epSos-DE </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgk">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7lvgi">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 08:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Secure chess and go games]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i55t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>If anyone is interested in playing a game of correspondence chess or go where all blunders are hidden from the public, send me a message at BM-NBK4NmqiZNq7kv4b7Yz3qgjGWn3E93yT. You can send me a first move, or ask me to go first. :)</p> <p>We will use algebraic notation.</p> <p>Edit: I can also mention that my strenght in Go is around 9k, and in chess around 1800 FIDE ELO.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7i55u"> twinzen </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7i55v">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7i55t">[7 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 22:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3671 from gavinandresen/txn_conflicts]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i58c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3671 from gavinandresen/txn_conflicts

Report transaction conflicts, and tentative account balance fix</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3671 from gavinandresen/txn_conflicts

Report transaction conflicts, and tentative account balance fix</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 13:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Notbit - An alternative minimal client for Linux using your existing mail client]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i58g]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yol"> bpeel </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7i58h">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7i58g">[9 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 12:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Mega Millions Lottery Stock MML Peercover/ Ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i58p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>MML (Mega millionaire lottery) stock is now available for purchase on ripple. 1000 XRP per share of initial issuance of 10k shares. Basically, it is a lottery pool so all proceeds sold from this stock will go towards the 400 million lottery jackpot. Each share represents .001 percent of a pool. </p> <p>If the stock wins and you own one share you are entitled to 40k dollars of the pool. If all issuance of 10k shares sell @ 1k xrp then the owners will purchase approx 150k tickets and exponentially increase the changes of winning. </p> <p>All ticket receipts and copies of tickets will be distributed upon request and for full disclosure we are making copies of the receipts. </p> <p>It only takes 1 share and 1 ticket to change everyone's life. </p> <p>TO PURCHASE use the Peercover (PCV) as the issuer of MML/XRP under the trade tab. </p> <p>GOOD LUCK!! FIRST DRAWING IS TUESDAY! </p> <p>Also...Mega Millions is for Education funds so were all doing a good thing. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/75g4v"> rippillionaire </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7i58p">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7i58p">[6 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 07:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Charting Bitcoin's Unsteady Rise]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gsp8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gsp9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsp8">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 00:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Track and report wallet transaction clones]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i58x]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Track and report wallet transaction clones

Adds a "walletconflicts" array to transaction info; if
a wallet transaction is mutated, the alternate transaction id
or ids are reported there (usually the array will be empty).

Metadata from the original transaction is copied to the mutant,
so the transaction time and "from" account of the mutant are
reported correctly.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Track and report wallet transaction clones

Adds a "walletconflicts" array to transaction info; if
a wallet transaction is mutated, the alternate transaction id
or ids are reported there (usually the array will be empty).

Metadata from the original transaction is copied to the mutant,
so the transaction time and "from" account of the mutant are
reported correctly.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 23:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3669 from gavinandresen/dead_txns]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i592]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3669 from gavinandresen/dead_txns

Handle "conflicted" transactions properly</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3669 from gavinandresen/dead_txns

Handle "conflicted" transactions properly</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 19:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[qt: GUI for conflicted transactions]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i593]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>qt: GUI for conflicted transactions

- Exclamation mark icon for conflicted transactions
- Show mouseover status for conflicted transactions as "conflicted"
- Don't show inactive transactions on overview page overview</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>qt: GUI for conflicted transactions

- Exclamation mark icon for conflicted transactions
- Show mouseover status for conflicted transactions as "conflicted"
- Don't show inactive transactions on overview page overview</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 18:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3659 from jgarzik/zapall]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i596]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3659 from jgarzik/zapall

Add -zapwallettx function, a diagnostic tool to assist in wallet repair</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3659 from jgarzik/zapall

Add -zapwallettx function, a diagnostic tool to assist in wallet repair</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>jgarzik</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 17:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Add -zapwallettxes cli/config option, used for wallet recovery]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i597]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Add -zapwallettxes cli/config option, used for wallet recovery

This diagnostic tool removes all "tx" records from the wallet db,
then forces a full rescan, to rebuild "tx" records accurately.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Add -zapwallettxes cli/config option, used for wallet recovery

This diagnostic tool removes all "tx" records from the wallet db,
then forces a full rescan, to rebuild "tx" records accurately.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>jgarzik</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 16:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Handle &quot;conflicted&quot; transactions properly]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i598]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Handle "conflicted" transactions properly

Extend CMerkleTx::GetDepthInMainChain with the concept of
a "conflicted" transaction-- a transaction generated by the wallet
that is not in the main chain or in the mempool, and, therefore,
will likely never be confirmed.

GetDepthInMainChain() now returns -1 for conflicted transactions
(0 for unconfirmed-but-in-the-mempool, and &gt;1 for confirmed).

This makes getbalance, getbalance '*', and listunspent all agree when there are
mutated transactions in the wallet.

Before:
 listunspent: one 49BTC output
 getbalance: 96 BTC (change counted twice)
 getbalance '*': 46 BTC (spends counted twice)

After: all agree, 49 BTC available to spend.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Handle "conflicted" transactions properly

Extend CMerkleTx::GetDepthInMainChain with the concept of
a "conflicted" transaction-- a transaction generated by the wallet
that is not in the main chain or in the mempool, and, therefore,
will likely never be confirmed.

GetDepthInMainChain() now returns -1 for conflicted transactions
(0 for unconfirmed-but-in-the-mempool, and &gt;1 for confirmed).

This makes getbalance, getbalance '*', and listunspent all agree when there are
mutated transactions in the wallet.

Before:
 listunspent: one 49BTC output
 getbalance: 96 BTC (change counted twice)
 getbalance '*': 46 BTC (spends counted twice)

After: all agree, 49 BTC available to spend.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 16:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3667 from gavinandresen/rpctest_osxcompat]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i599]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3667 from gavinandresen/rpctest_osxcompat

Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3667 from gavinandresen/rpctest_osxcompat

Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 16:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Lecture requested by the bitcoin education project]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gssw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gssx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gssw">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 06:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple for Freicoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gstb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Greetings,</p> <p>I am looking to initially fund my ripple wallet. Is any one interested in trading Freicoin for some XPR? </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7gstc"> oneinch </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gstb">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gstb">[8 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 02:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX

Reworked send.sh, so it works properly on my Mac (killall send.sh
doesn't work, because the process name is 'bash' not 'send.sh').
So now send.sh writes a .send.pid file, and invoking it as
send.sh -STOP (as the bitcoind -walletnotify) signals that PID.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX

Reworked send.sh, so it works properly on my Mac (killall send.sh
doesn't work, because the process name is 'bash' not 'send.sh').
So now send.sh writes a .send.pid file, and invoking it as
send.sh -STOP (as the bitcoind -walletnotify) signals that PID.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3662]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59e]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3662

0542619 Rename IsConfirmed to IsTrusted to better match the intended behavior. (Gregory Maxwell)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3662

0542619 Rename IsConfirmed to IsTrusted to better match the intended behavior. (Gregory Maxwell)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 19:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple network forks - Protoshares, Netpay, and Splash]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gstv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gstw">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gstv">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 18:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3668]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59g]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3668

3a1c20b Add raw transaction hex to `gettransaction` wallet RPC (Wladimir J. van der Laan)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3668

3a1c20b Add raw transaction hex to `gettransaction` wallet RPC (Wladimir J. van der Laan)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 17:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Add raw transaction hex to `gettransaction` wallet RPC]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Add raw transaction hex to `gettransaction` wallet RPC

This allows getting raw transaction data from the wallet even if the
transaction is no longer in the blockchain / mempool (for example if it
got orphaned due to malleability abuse).</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Add raw transaction hex to `gettransaction` wallet RPC

This allows getting raw transaction data from the wallet even if the
transaction is no longer in the blockchain / mempool (for example if it
got orphaned due to malleability abuse).</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59i]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX

Reworked send.sh, so it works properly on my Mac (killall send.sh
doesn't work, because the process name is 'bash' not 'send.sh').
So now send.sh writes a .send.pid file, and invoking it as
send.sh -STOP (as the bitcoind -walletnotify) signals that PID.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Make qa/rpc-tests/ compatible with OSX

Reworked send.sh, so it works properly on my Mac (killall send.sh
doesn't work, because the process name is 'bash' not 'send.sh').
So now send.sh writes a .send.pid file, and invoking it as
send.sh -STOP (as the bitcoind -walletnotify) signals that PID.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 15:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3657]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3657

fdbc2b1 If requested, actually treat uncomfirmed change as being uncomfirmed (b6393ce9-d324-4fe1-996b-acf82dbc3d53)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3657

fdbc2b1 If requested, actually treat uncomfirmed change as being uncomfirmed (b6393ce9-d324-4fe1-996b-acf82dbc3d53)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 11:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Reloading keys.dat]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gsvv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I am working on a project based on bitmessage where I'll be externalizing totally the keys (or die trying...) The idea is to create an address, pass it to the user in the form of an encrypted token, delete it from the server's keys.dat and restore it when the user comes back (providing he comes back before the 2.5 days limit). </p> <p>This would establish a (more) "trustless relationship" between the user and the server. The user doesn't have to trust the security of the server, he doesn't have to trust the admin to be honest, etc... The server would simply not have your keys (as it should be anyway...it is your key)</p> <p>It should be quite easy to implement. I added a method to the python API to be able to call shared.reloadMyAddressHashes() on demand but it doesn't work. I get the debug message saying 'reloading keys from keys.dat file' but it seems the keys.dat is not reloaded. </p> <p>Here is how I test and fail :</p> <ol><li>I cut the last address block of keys.dat and paste it in a file</li> <li>run the daemon, loads the keys</li> <li>Try to send a message using the address I just deleted =&gt; fails</li> <li>Restore the address block in keys.dat</li> <li>Call reloadMyAddressHashes via the API</li> <li>Try to send a message using the address I just deleted =&gt; fails again</li> </ol><p>I am obviously missing something... What am I doing wrong?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5fy"> ReversedK </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gsvw">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsvv">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 01:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Rename IsConfirmed to IsTrusted to better match the intended behavior.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Rename IsConfirmed to IsTrusted to better match the intended behavior.

This doesn't change the functionality at all.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Rename IsConfirmed to IsTrusted to better match the intended behavior.

This doesn't change the functionality at all.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gmaxwell</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 00:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple at risk of ECC private key reuse attacks?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gsvx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gsvy">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsvx">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Interesting alt-blockchain suggestion over at /r/bitcloud - applicable to BM too?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gsvz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsw0"> pptyx </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gsw1">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsvz">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 21:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Create and address, delete it, recreate it]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gsw9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Let's consider the following case :</p> <ol><li>I create a deterministic address,</li> <li>I delete it</li> <li>I send a message to the address created in 1. from another address</li> </ol><p>Question 1 : If I later recreate the same deterministic address will I be able to access to the message sent to that address while it was deleted from my keys.dat?</p> <p>Is there a time limit ? What if I recreate the address 1 month later, will I be able to get my messages in messages.dat?</p> <p>Question 2 : does deleting an address also deletes the messages of that address ?</p> <p>Thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5fy"> ReversedK </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gswa">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsw9">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage needs a light client]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7gswb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Is a light weight BM client, along the lines of a HTML5 browser plugin (like the excellent Kryptokit) possible?</p> <p>I'm no dev but I can't see why this shouldn't be possible if light wallets work seamlessly for the enormous Bitcoin blockchain.</p> <p>There are numerous light/html5 wallets in production for on Android &amp; iOS too -- so wouldn't this in theory be a solution to BM's lack of phone client issue also?</p> <p>Friendly non-dev criticism: I'm a fan of bitmessage but I keep encountering a tendency from its dev community to look for 'workarounds' instead of <em>solving</em> issues, and adding simple feature requests. BM needs to be better than that if it's to become a genuine email alternative.</p> <p>Edit: I would have posted this to BM forums but it doesn't let me register using tor.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7gsw0"> pptyx </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7gswc">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7gswb">[15 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[If requested, actually treat uncomfirmed change as being uncomfirmed]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>If requested, actually treat uncomfirmed change as being uncomfirmed

This commit strengthens 1bbca249b202c4802cc2c4d4de4a26e6392b4d92 by updating the CWalletTx::IsConfirmed() function.

If (bSpendZeroConfChange==false), then IsConfirmed() should actually treat unconfirmed change as being unconfirmed.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>If requested, actually treat uncomfirmed change as being uncomfirmed

This commit strengthens 1bbca249b202c4802cc2c4d4de4a26e6392b4d92 by updating the CWalletTx::IsConfirmed() function.

If (bSpendZeroConfChange==false), then IsConfirmed() should actually treat unconfirmed change as being unconfirmed.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>b6393ce9-d324-4fe1-996b-acf82dbc3d53</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 05:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3651]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59r]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3651

1bbca24 Add option to avoid spending unconfirmed change (Wladimir J. van der Laan)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3651

1bbca24 Add option to avoid spending unconfirmed change (Wladimir J. van der Laan)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3025 from sipa/noncanpush]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59s]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3025 from sipa/noncanpush

Make signatures with non-canonical data pushes non-standard.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3025 from sipa/noncanpush

Make signatures with non-canonical data pushes non-standard.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gmaxwell</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 20:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Add HasCanonicalPushes(), and use it in IsStandardTx]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Add HasCanonicalPushes(), and use it in IsStandardTx</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Add HasCanonicalPushes(), and use it in IsStandardTx</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 20:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Move IsPushOnly() to script.cpp]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7i59v]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Move IsPushOnly() to script.cpp</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Move IsPushOnly() to script.cpp</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Deterministic addresses in the API]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7d5fx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>When I send a "getDeterministicAddress("passphrase".encode("base64"),3,1)" to the API it always returns me the same address for a given passphrase but when I create a deterministic address with "createDeterministicAddresses("passphrase".encode("base64"),1,0,0) I don't get an address matching the one I got from getDeterministicAddress.</p> <p>I understand that when creating an address the passphrase is used as a seed for the random generator but in that case what is the adress I got from getDeterministic ? And what can I do with it?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5fy"> ReversedK </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7d5fz">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5fx">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 22:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Feature Request: Password Protected bitmessage]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7d5ht]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Even after the encryption usage in communication, a simple password/pin to open/read bitmessage would help.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5hu"> nighthawk24 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7d5hv">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5ht">[7 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 23:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[If you are german, please help improving the german wikipedia article about bitmessage]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7d5kr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5ks"> Sibbo </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7d5kt">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5kr">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 18:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Double messages in 0.4.2]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7d5l1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Communicating with my friend we experience double messages all the time. Any solutions for this annoying problem?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5l2"> purplemaid </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/7d5l3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/7d5l1">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The bitmessage E-Mail gateway (bitmessage.ch) now accepts dogecoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/75g4i]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I thought it would be a good idea to have a secondary sort of coin listed as donation options since the service runs completely on donations.</p> <p>I have chosen dogecoin. While difficult to take seriously at first it has a great community.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yjr"> AyrA_ch </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/75g4j">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/75g4i">[14 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage Pen Pals]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/75g4w]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Bitmessage is a marvelous new piece of technology. Unfortunately, I don't know anyone in real life or even internet acquaintances that care. </p> <p>If you're tired of something other than chans feel free to give me a ring. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/75g4x"> Misanthropic_Marmot </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/75g4y">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/75g4w">[6 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 08:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Just a reminder]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/75g4z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hello <a href="http://cur.lv/75g50">/r/bitmessage</a>, I am just here to remind you all that bitmessage, as awesome as the idea is, is still a work in progress. Most importantly, the authors state that the current implementation, due to the libraries used, is <strong>not necessarily cryptographically secure</strong>. Be aware of this when using it!</p> <p>Otherwise, it's pretty neat, and I am with the user who posted recently that they would be happy to donate toward its development. Please, developers, give us some crypto-currency wallet addresses! I think it'll be worth your while. Thanks for all that you do!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/75g51"> friendly_heretic </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/75g52">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/75g4z">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Very impressed with multi device behavior of Bit Message]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700vy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I just started testing BitMessage across my multiple computers. I aes-256 encrypted my keys.dat file and put in the cloud. I've got multiple machines now with the same keys.</p> <p>So far the behavior of sending and receiving messages across multiple devices has been exactly as one would expect. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/700vz"> zmanian </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/700w0">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/700vy">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to check status of an order on BTC-e API?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700wf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>It would appear there is no way of obtaining fill notifications for active orders.</p>

<p>If I am mistaken, please enlighten me!</p>

<p>When orders are submitted to a BTC-e account, either via API or their website, and they are NOT instantly filled, they get assigned an OrderID integer. I can query the authenticated API for account info, which will give me back a list of all Active Orders and associated OIDs, but aside from having my program maintain a list of what it "thinks" are Active, versus what actually is active on the account by sending a query every X seconds, I do not know of a simpler/faster way to determine what orders got filled or when.</p>

<p>I also would like some clarification on the <code>status</code> field of the order response from API. it would appear <code>0</code> is <code>active</code> and <code>1</code> is <code>filled</code>. What are the values for <code>partial fill</code> and <code>cancelled</code>? </p>

<p>There is also a way to see <code>All</code> orders on the website by going to <code>Finances</code>-&gt;<code>Orders History</code> and then the drop down for <code>Show All</code>, is there a corresponding API call for that?</p>

<p>I need to be able to monitor for partial and complete fills.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>ACVentures</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[cgminer api-allow using dns instead of IP address]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/700x3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I am wondering why cgminer is not accepting dns instead of IP addresses</p>

<p>I need to allow a server by it's dns...is it possible?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Royi Mindel</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 14:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[how to transfer bitcoins to my Indian bank or PayPal account]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b19]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have recently joined free bitcoin and open an account in Blockchain.info.I have studied the FAQ but still I am not sure about to transfer in PayPal and can't able to understand if can I withdraw directly to my PayPal account or should I need a exchanger.</p>

<p>Because this is a very new currency so I am not sure how to transfer my bit coins in to my paypal account or in my Indian bank account,and please let me know the minimum withdrawal limit.</p>

<p>Sir I have referred lot of peoples so Please provide me detail answer of my queries.</p>

<p>Thanks and Regards</p>

<p>Atul</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>atul</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 22:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How does proof-of-stake &quot;mining&quot; work?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yhs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I know and understand the concept of proof-of-stake. Instead of requiring users to do a certain amount of power-intensive hashing "work", it requires you to own a certain stake of the currency in order for you to mine new coins. </p>

<p>But how does the actual mining process work? In PoW mining, people "find" blocks by generating a hash that fulfills a certain condition. How can one mine a PoS block? Is a miner required? Or does just anyone holding coins get their share after a certain amount of time? </p>

<p>In Peercoin specifically, is PoW and PoS mining done independently or do they interfere or influence one another? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Steven Roose</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 01:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can someone explain this double spend on blockchain.info?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm confused by double-spend linked below, in which both transactions ended up in blocks mined by different miners.  Specifically, I'm wondering if there's any way to tell what exactly happened based on the available information.</p>

<p><a href="http://cur.lv/7010i" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7010i</a></p>

<p>Based on my limited understanding of bitcoin, I'm assuming this could have happened in one of the following three ways. If I'm wrong, or if I'm missing other possibilities, could someone please let me know?</p>

<p>1) The double-spender broadcast the first transaction to the network, and then mined his own block containing a transaction using the same output.  He ultimately wasn't able to "outrun" the honest blockchain, but he managed to mine his block quickly enough that some nodes in the network received it before receiving the longer blockchain. So both blocks were briefly accepted by parts of the network, and one was eventually "orphaned" (so its transactions are unconfirmed).</p>

<p>2) Same situation, but the double-spender's blockchain prevailed and the block containing the first transaction broadcast to the network was orphaned.</p>

<p>3) The double-spender didn't mine anything, he just tried a normal double-spend against someone who doesn't require confirmations. Both transactions happened to be included in blocks that were mined simultaneously by different miners in the network, and one was orphaned.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>craw</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 01:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[My MultiBit is unable to connect]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010l]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have installed my MultiBit wallet and there is red "connecting" sign in left bottom corner. Wallet never connects. When I try it from another place (my friends house) everything is ok.</p>

<p>It is obvious that its network problem in my place. I have public IP and port 8333 is properly forwarded. I am using Mac OS X 10.8.5.</p>

<p>I have no idea what else to try or where to look for some error messages. Do you have any ideas what else to try or where to look for some clues?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Macejkou</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Mining a primecoin based currency (datacoin). How do I find out how much hash power im doing?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010m]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>How do I find out how much hashing power am I providing to the network? What is the command to find it out? </p>

<p>Currently I see this: <a href="http://cur.lv/7010n" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7010n</a></p>

<p>when I run:  <strong>watch 'datacoind listaccounts &amp; datacoind getmininginfo'</strong></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>duckx</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 16:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How can I mine PeerCoin?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr25]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I was wondering how I could mine peercoin - I already have experience mining Bitcoins and Litecoins, yet I can't seem to find any software where I can mine them - I would like to be able to mine them on my mac with a GPU, so any applications, or terminal commands would be a great help... I already have my Peercoin wallet and everything set up. I have tried CGMiner except in the recent update they completely dumped support for GPU mining.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Domenico</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 03:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Running bitcoind on VPS, won't speak to my web server]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have a VPS with bitcoind set up, synced the blocks and its all running fine. I have set up the bitcoin.conf file and allowed the IP of my web host server.</p>

<p>I am running a script on my web host that communicates to the wallet but it just won't connect! </p>

<pre><code>Fatal error: Uncaught exception 'Exception' with message 'Unable to connect to http://cur.lv/7wr26 in /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/driver_test.php:61 Stack trace: #0 /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/index.php(16): jsonRPCClient-&gt;__call('getbalance', Array) #1 /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/index.php(16): jsonRPCClient-&gt;getbalance() #2 {main} thrown in /home/1234/public_html/gm/install/driver_test.php on line 61
</code></pre>

<p>Any suggestions? I have run out of ideas.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Tau11</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 14:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Opening Wallet with a different App]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010r]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I just bought a couple of bitcoins. I got my wallet from Bitcom.org but I learned that there is this Electrum wallet which Id like to try. How do I open my wallet with the new App?</p>

<p>thanks!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user9903</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 12:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Not getting enough Hashrate]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have an i3-3220 processor which i am using for mining. 
I know that you're supposed to use a GPU and all that. But currently i'm just trying it out before spending money.</p>

<p>I'm using CPUMiner, mining at middlecoin.com, 24 hours a day.</p>

<p>The problem is that i'm recieving very less hashrate.
This <a href="http://cur.lv/7010u" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/7010u</a> points out that an i3 processor (which is actually a lower model than mine) recieves almost 8.5 MH/s and i receive about 5.5 KH/s on each thread that is about 27 KH/s in total.Why such a large difference?</p>

<p>What do i need to tweak? Is my program useless? Are the settings wrong? Is it problem with the pool?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Harry King</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 22:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How much time does it take to transfer BTC into btc-e hosted wallet?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr27]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>If i'm buying BTC in person from someone and he sends it to my btc-e hosted wallet, how much time does it usually take to appear in the account balance? Is it like any regular transfer or are they doing some extra confirmations? Thanks!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Uri Abramson</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 14:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[/r/Bitcoin FAQ - Newcomers please read]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68bfo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>This posts explains some dos and don'ts about what to post on <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokc">/r/Bitcoin</a> .</p> <p>First lets start with...</p> <hr><p><strong>Messaging mods</strong></p> <p>Modmail is for:</p> <ul><li>Problems with the subreddit (some sidebar links are broken for example)</li> <li>Problems with submissions (spam filter sometimes catches too much, we sort things a few times a day. If you have an <strong>urgent</strong> submission, contact us)</li> <li>Requests that need mod support - if you need us to verify your identity for say, AMA, or that you represent an organization, contact us and we'll do our best to help you</li> </ul><p>Modmail is <strong>not</strong> for:</p> <ul><li>Asking general questions</li> <li>Reporting obvious spam submissions (that's what the <strong>Report</strong> button is for)</li> <li>Advertisements on the subreddit (it is handled <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfp">through Reddit</a>, not us)</li> <li>Help with shadowbans (again, that's Reddit, not us. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfq">Contact them</a>)</li> </ul><p><strong>Frequent requests:</strong></p> <ul><li>"Can I get a flair?" - No, at the moment we are <strong>not</strong> giving anyone flair on the subreddit</li> <li>"Can you add my subreddit to the sidebar?" - If you are a local Bitcoin subreddit, we can add you to the wiki. If you are not a Bitcoin-related subreddit, 99% chance the answer is no. If you are a Bitcoin-related subreddit, we only add subreddits that are established - if you have less than a few hundred subscribers and less than a post a day, the answer is most likely no. Beyond that, we can talk.</li> <li>"Can you link to my website from the sidebar?" - No</li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Submissions</strong></p> <p><strong>Please don't post:</strong></p> <ul><li>Ask to be stickied - it's like asking for upvotes. People don't like it when you ask for upvotes.</li> <li>General questions about how Bitcoin works - go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfr">/r/BitcoinBeginners</a> or search in <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfs">http://cur.lv/68bfs</a> .</li> <li>General newcomer questions, like "which client should I use?", "how do I buy Bitcoin?" - again, <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfr">/r/BitcoinBeginners</a></li> <li>Questions about mining - go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bft">/r/bitcoinmining</a></li> <li>"Is it profitable to mine?" - punch your numbers into <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfu">a calculator</a> or go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bft">/r/bitcoinmining</a></li> <li>"Should I buy Bitcoin?" / "Is it still worth investing in Bitcoin?" - You shouldn't take financial advice from the Internet, you need to figure this out for yourself</li> <li>"What about altcoin X?" / "Should I buy altcoin X?" / "You should buy altcoin X!" - This is a very big topic in itself. Short answer is no under most circumstances. For a longer explanation, please read <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfv">my blog entry</a> and the accompanying <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfw">reddit submission</a> for discussion on the topic.</li> <li>Asking for money - unless you are a reputable charity, your post will be treated like spam</li> <li>Complaints about not buying Bitcoins when they were $X/BTC - nobody cares</li> <li>Referral links - your post will be treated like spam</li> <li>"BUYBUYBUY"/"SELLSELLSELL" - you will be treated like a troll</li> <li>Submissions or posts with curse words directed at someone - don't insult other people. Your posts will be treated like spam otherwise. Occasional expressions like "holy shit this is awesome!" are tolerated in moderation.</li> <li>"Can I buy less than 1 bitcoin?" - The answer is "yes, you can purchase as little as 0.00000001 BTC at a time, you don't have to buy a whole coin, similarly how you can buy a gram of gold, you don't need to buy a whole gold bar"</li> <li>"What happens after all 21M BTC are mined?" - Either Bitcoin will be long gone before then (if the system doesn't catch on), or <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfx">miners will be earning their money from transaction fees instead</a>.</li> <li>"What happens to lost coins?" - Lost coins remain lost, unless someone finds a private key for them. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfy">This is <strong>ONLY</strong> viable if quantum computers become strong enough</a>. Otherwise, <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfz">the numbers used by Bitcoin are too big to be brute forced - heat death of the universe will occur before a colission is found.</a>. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg0">As for re-mining old bitcoins, there are many reasons to not return lost coins back to circulation.</a></li> </ul><p><strong>Take heed when posting:</strong></p> <ul><li>Memes - memes are allowed, but some people may not like you for posting them. Be sure to use <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg1">/r/Bitcoinmemes</a> as well</li> <li>Information about all-time-highs, price spikes, crashes and so forth - 90% of the time, someone has already posted about it. Check <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg2">/r/bitcoin/new</a> first before posting.</li> <li>Questions about help with a particular website or business - <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokc">/r/Bitcoin</a> is not tech support for any business, you're better off contacting the support of the business in question through their forums or ticket system</li> </ul><p><strong>What to do if you see...</strong></p> <ul><li>Spam - click "report" underneath the submission, vote accordingly. Don't message mods unless the spam is subtle or needs context</li> <li>Repost - vote accordingly, click "report"</li> <li>A post from the "don't" list above - direct the posted to a proper subreddit if applicable (for questions and newbie posts), vote and report accordingly otherwise</li> <li>A post that is allowed on this subreddit but you don't like it being here - vote accordingly, don't report it. If it is allowed, the mods will not remove the post. Your votes shape what submissions get the most exposure - upvote the posts you want to see more of, downvote the ones you want to see less of.</li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Some good guides you should look into:</strong></p> <ul><li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg3">Will I earn money by mining?</a></li> <li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg4">Basic Bitcoin security guide</a></li> <li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg5">The straightforward Bitcoin safety and security guide</a></li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Please do</strong></p> <ul><li>Read the sidebar for community rules - following them will make everyone's day better.</li> <li>Be sceptical of any news without credible sources - a lot of bad people are trying to play on your emotions by fabricating fake stories. Be sceptical of any story without a credible citation, especially when it is related to economic or legal side of things.</li> </ul><hr><p>Thank you for your attention. Post responsibly, vote on all submissions, live and let live, have fun.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokl"> ThePiachu </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/68bfo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfo">[235 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 04:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yokm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yqt"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>November 02, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokp" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yqt"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr28(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr29">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to integrate a Bitcoin payment service in my auction site]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7010z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>So, if I wanted to have Bitcoin as a form of method where users could pay, how would I do this? Obviously, there is paypal, where the buyer sends money through pp, which disperses to the seller. So, I need to have this type of system on my site as well. Is there anything like it for Bitcoins? </p>

<p>Thanks!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>ramboramos</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 04:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yokw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>26 lines (14 sloc)</span><span>1.232 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>Join our Bitmessage chan! First, download the client from bitmessage.org. Then, go to file --&gt; Join/Create chan --&gt; Join Chan and enter the following details (use the full name of the chan including the "created by" part)</p>
<p><strong>Name of chan:</strong> Bitcoin Crowdfunding incubator (Created by BM-2cVPTkVZo2mDoJyXmaGkujtJNovVhu6W1H)<br><strong>Chan address:</strong> BM-2cVVS3U9zdfDyQRxP8wsLUG3epavsqsDja<br></p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoky" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://cur.lv/5yoky"></a><br><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokz" rel="nofollow"><br>Image created by </a><a href="http://cur.lv/5yol0" rel="nofollow">Jack Z</a></p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2a(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2b">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yol4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>November 01, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yol6" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2c(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2d">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yola]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>15 lines (12 sloc)</span><span>0.604 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>You can <em>visit any project in the browser</em> by surfing to entrances.github.com/[ProjectName].html</p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2e(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2f">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yole]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>October 28, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolf" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2g(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2h">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[18 lines (13 sloc)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div><div>
<span>18 lines (13 sloc)</span><span>0.598 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>These are our crowdfunding entries:</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolk" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/5yolk</a><br></p></article></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2i(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2j">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2k(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2l">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysa"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>October 19, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolv" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysa"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2m(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2n">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>14 lines (11 sloc)</span><span>0.509 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>You can visit any project in the browser by surfing to entrances.github.com/[ProjectName].html</p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2o(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2p">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 05:24:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yom3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysj"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>September 24, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yom5" rel="nofollow">Update README.md</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysj"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>14 lines (10 sloc)</span><span>0.408 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p></p>
<p></p>
<p></p>
<p>Hey! Welcome to the Web Developer's group!</p>
<p>We build stuff together. Have a look at the projects at entrances.github.com</p>
<p>If you want to discuss contracts, payments or other sensitive information, send a Bitmessage to <strong>BM-2D7XVMiTuyLtSGF6t4NERnUDrfbZvTdtG4</strong></p>
<p></p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/7wr2q(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/7wr2r">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BBC News - Snowden link to encrypted email service closes]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ysm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Two encrypted email services have closed down for reasons linked to US intelligence leaker Edward Snowden. Texas-based Lavabit service has shut down but ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How much memory and bandwidth does bitcoind take up on a CentOS Linux system?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7011k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm thinking about installing <a href="http://cur.lv/7011l" rel="nofollow">bitcoind</a> on my web server that runs on <a href="http://cur.lv/7011m" rel="nofollow">CentOS</a>. How much memory and bandwidth might it take up and would it affect my other sites on my server?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>duckx</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 16:04:37 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage is the Bitcoin of online communication - CoinDesk]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgdc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage is a protocol that implements some of the ideas of Bitcoin into communications.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 09:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[OSX Vanitygen error: pattern.c:32:10: fatal error: 'pcre.h' file not found]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr2s]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I get the error below when I try to <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr2t" rel="nofollow">make vanitygen according to the instructions listed in "install"</a></p>

<p><strong>Error from make</strong> (short version)</p>

<pre><code>27 warnings generated.
cc -ggdb -O3 -Wall   -c -o pattern.o pattern.c
pattern.c:32:10: fatal error: 'pcre.h' file not found
#include &lt;pcre.h&gt;
         ^
1 error generated.
</code></pre>

<p><strong>Full output of make</strong></p>

<pre><code>my-MacBook-Pro:git-vanitygen admin$ make
cc -ggdb -O3 -Wall   -c -o vanitygen.o vanitygen.c
vanitygen.c:76:11: warning: 'EC_KEY_get0_group' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
        pgroup = EC_KEY_get0_group(pkey);
                 ^
vanitygen.c:77:9: warning: 'EC_GROUP_get0_generator' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
        pgen = EC_GROUP_get0_generator(pgroup);
               ^
vanitygen.c:80:13: warning: 'EC_POINT_new' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                ppnt[i] = EC_POINT_new(pgroup);
                          ^
vanitygen.c:86:14: warning: 'EC_POINT_new' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
        pbatchinc = EC_POINT_new(pgroup);
                    ^
vanitygen.c:92:2: warning: 'BN_set_word' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
        BN_set_word(&amp;vxcp-&gt;vxc_bntmp, ptarraysize);
        ^
vanitygen.c:93:2: warning: 'EC_POINT_mul' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
        EC_POINT_mul(pgroup, pbatchinc, &amp;vxcp-&gt;vxc_bntmp, NULL, NULL,
        ^
vanitygen.c:95:2: warning: 'EC_POINT_make_affine' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
        EC_POINT_make_affine(pgroup, pbatchinc, vxcp-&gt;vxc_bnctx);
        ^
vanitygen.c:124:4: warning: 'EC_KEY_generate_key' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        EC_KEY_generate_key(pkey);
                        ^
vanitygen.c:128:4: warning: 'EC_GROUP_get_order' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        EC_GROUP_get_order(pgroup, &amp;vxcp-&gt;vxc_bntmp,
                        ^
vanitygen.c:130:4: warning: 'BN_sub' is deprecated [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        BN_sub(&amp;vxcp-&gt;vxc_bntmp2,
                        ^
vanitygen.c:132:11: warning: 'EC_KEY_get0_private_key' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                               EC_KEY_get0_private_key(pkey));
                               ^
vanitygen.c:133:15: warning: 'BN_get_word' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        rekey_at = BN_get_word(&amp;vxcp-&gt;vxc_bntmp2);
                                   ^
vanitygen.c:138:4: warning: 'EC_POINT_copy' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        EC_POINT_copy(ppnt[0], EC_KEY_get0_public_key(pkey));
                        ^
vanitygen.c:138:27: warning: 'EC_KEY_get0_public_key' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        EC_POINT_copy(ppnt[0], EC_KEY_get0_public_key(pkey));
                                               ^
vanitygen.c:145:5: warning: 'EC_POINT_add' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                                EC_POINT_add(pgroup,
                                ^
vanitygen.c:154:5: warning: 'EC_POINT_add' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                                EC_POINT_add(pgroup,
                                ^
vanitygen.c:173:5: warning: 'EC_POINT_add' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                                EC_POINT_add(pgroup,
                                ^
vanitygen.c:192:3: warning: 'EC_POINTs_make_affine' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                EC_POINTs_make_affine(pgroup, nbatch, ppnt, vxcp-&gt;vxc_bnctx);
                ^
vanitygen.c:196:10: warning: 'EC_POINT_point2oct' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        len = EC_POINT_point2oct(pgroup, ppnt[i],
                              ^
vanitygen.c:203:4: warning: 'SHA256' is deprecated [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        SHA256(hash_buf, hash_len, hash1);
                        ^
vanitygen.c:204:4: warning: 'RIPEMD160' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        RIPEMD160(hash1, sizeof(hash1), &amp;vxcp-&gt;vxc_binres[1]);
                        ^
vanitygen.c:236:4: warning: 'EC_POINT_free' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        EC_POINT_free(ppnt[i]);
                        ^
vanitygen.c:238:3: warning: 'EC_POINT_free' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                EC_POINT_free(pbatchinc);
                ^
vanitygen.c:419:18: warning: 'EC_POINT_hex2point' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        pubkey_base = EC_POINT_hex2point(
                                      ^
vanitygen.c:420:5: warning: 'EC_KEY_get0_group' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                                EC_KEY_get0_group(pkey),
                                ^
vanitygen.c:422:4: warning: 'EC_KEY_free' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                        EC_KEY_free(pkey);
                        ^
vanitygen.c:528:9: warning: 'RAND_load_file' is deprecated
      [-Wdeprecated-declarations]
                opt = RAND_load_file(seedfile, opt);
                      ^
27 warnings generated.
cc -ggdb -O3 -Wall   -c -o pattern.o pattern.c
pattern.c:32:10: fatal error: 'pcre.h' file not found
#include &lt;pcre.h&gt;
         ^
1 error generated.
make: *** [pattern.o] Error 1
</code></pre>

<hr><p><strong>UPDATE</strong> </p>

<p>I suspect that PCRE that is listed <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr2u" rel="nofollow">also has a OSX port that is listed here</a>, and when I compile according to the instructions I get this error:</p>

<pre><code>make  install-am
 ./install-sh -c -d '/usr/local/lib'
 /bin/sh ./libtool   --mode=install /usr/bin/install -c   libpcre.la libpcreposix.la libpcrecpp.la '/usr/local/lib'
libtool: install: /usr/bin/install -c .libs/libpcre.1.dylib /usr/local/lib/libpcre.1.dylib
install: /usr/local/lib/libpcre.1.dylib: Permission denied
make[2]: *** [install-libLTLIBRARIES] Error 71
make[1]: *** [install-am] Error 2
make: *** [install] Error 2
</code></pre>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>makerofthings7</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 04:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Where is Bitcoin information (wallet.dat) stored on OS X?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/7wr2v]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Is there a wallet.dat for OSX? Where is it located?</p>

<p>Taken from <a href="http://cur.lv/7wr2w">http://cur.lv/7wr2w</a></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Alex Waters</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 17:52:05 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>