<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://cur.lv/5xyoe">
<channel>
  <title>RSSMix.com Mix ID 3845704</title>
  <generator>RSSMix</generator>
  <link>http://cur.lv/65yf1</link>
  <description>This feed was created by mixing existing feeds from various sources.</description>
  <language>en-gb</language>
  
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [ANN][VOLT] *CRAZY Giveaway* 5,0000-1000,0000 or BTC 0.0001 goodluck]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxv2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6qxv3" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/6qxv3</a><br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxv4" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/6qxv4</a><br><br>QfceXfsLmJF4JjR6Fa9QbX1n22mu3yEDxR<br>thx]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [ANN][DOGE] Dogecoin - very currency many coin - v1.4 Released MANDATORY UPDATE]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxv5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxv6">Quote from: freddyfarnsworth on <b>Today</b> at 04:50:03 AM</a></div><div>Do hope the sled has custom logo... DOGESLED <img src="http://cur.lv/6qxv7" alt="Smiley" border="0"><br></div>I hope so too; however, the IOC/Olympics require any ads at the olympics to be official sponsors only. &nbsp;If s...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 04:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [ANN][MOON] Mooncoin: You know where it's headed! WE HAVE LIFTOFF!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxv8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Just tell them about doge and bobsleigh. They probably heard about it, so they'll believe that it's real. Tell them that Mooncoin market cap is already $4,000,000, and we want to donate $20,000 to them, just to make some kid's dream come true.<br><br>It's a c...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 04:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: HashFast BabyJet users thread]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxv9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Has anyone tried the new image for MinePeon?<br><br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxva" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/6qxva</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 04:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Re: [GIVEAWAY] @ThisWeeksCoin DOGE coins. Say Hi, get 100 doge!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Address - DUGWYf5JF4sNX1RqBW7Qvz2HfMeHy88rt4<br><br>Thanks. <img src="http://cur.lv/6qxv7" alt="Smiley" border="0">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 04:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[I've been waiting 3 years for this, and it was delicious!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvc"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxvd" alt="I've been waiting 3 years for this, and it was delicious!" title="I've been waiting 3 years for this, and it was delicious!"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxve"> teflon121 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvf">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvc">[8 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 04:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple’s Distributed Exchange and the High Frequency Trading Arms Race]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yjf"> alwillis </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvg">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 02:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[4 New Bitcoin Features Revealed by Core Developer Mike Hearn]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvi"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxvj" alt="4 New Bitcoin Features Revealed by Core Developer Mike Hearn" title="4 New Bitcoin Features Revealed by Core Developer Mike Hearn"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvk"> Beleeth </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvl">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvi">[11 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 02:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Jamie Dimon/JPMorgan Chase has more to lose than you think if Bitcoin wins]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvm"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxvn" alt="Jamie Dimon/JPMorgan Chase has more to lose than you think if Bitcoin wins" title="Jamie Dimon/JPMorgan Chase has more to lose than you think if Bitcoin wins"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvo"> montseayo </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvp">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvm">[7 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merged mining: are there any ways to prevent it?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Supporting merged mining allows a cryptocurrency A to improve the security its blockchain (increase the hash rate) by accepting work done on the blockchain of cryptocurrency B through insertion of a hash of a valid A-block.</p>

<p>Is it possible for cryptocurrency B (say Bitcoin) to prevent its blockchain from being used to effectively enhance the security of a rival coin? (I am assuming the 'A'-hash insertion takes place in the coinbase, which is normally used for entropy).</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Johannes Tynes</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 01:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Tracking a specific Bitcoin to make it represent something else, which could then be traded without trust]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine if one could follow the movements of a specific Bitcoin (or fraction thereof) in the block chain. Then that would mean that I could make that specific Bitcoin represent something else, which people could then freely trade just as other Bitcoins. </p>

<p>For example, I could mark 100 Bitcoins and define that these represent 100% of the equity of my company. I could then put them up for sale for something I felt was reasonable given the value of my company + the value of the Bitcoins themselves. People would know that they could freely and almost anonymously resell the equity of my company without trusting anything else than what the Bitcoins represented. No need for lawyers, no need for contracts regarding selling and buying of equity, no need to meet at all to do the exchange. My company could also pay the owners dividend, because I would always know which wallets owned the special Bitcoints.</p>

<p>My question is therefore: Is this currently possible, given all the nice <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvs" rel="nofollow">scripting features</a> in Bitcoin. And if not, then are there currently any plans to modify Bitcoins to enable such a feature? </p>

<p>Needless to say, I believe that there is a huge potential in this, because one could basically mark the owner of billions of things (virtual or not) by assigning something like 0.00000001 Bitcoins to each thing. This way one would always know who was the true owner of that specific thing. </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>David</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Import bitaddress.org screenshot into Bitcoin-Qt client?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I've received some bitcoins in a wallet created by bitaddress.org, and I've saved a screenshot of the webpage that has the public/private keys and the QR codes:</p>

<p><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxvu" alt="enter image description here"></p>

<p>I've now downloaded the Bitcoin-Qt client, how do I import what I have into it as a wallet?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sashoalm</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 23:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MtGox Transaction IDs are internal or bitcoin issued?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Why did MtGox issue me a transaction ID (and charge a fee) for funds that have not "transacted" to the address I provided (but have been withdrawn from MtGox)?</p>

<p>Do they issue some kind of internal transaction ID which does not lead anywhere when I search it in blockchain?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>val</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 23:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[what is hash 160 in blockchain summary]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>If I search an address on blockchain I get a summary that includes "Hash 160". What is "Hash 160" ... for a transaction that has yet to occurr (i.e. it's not listed and neither is it in the unconfirmed listing)?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>val</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 23:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Transactions not showing up in bitcoind log?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have a bitcoind running on a server behind the www box which I poll every minute for new transactions and save new data into a table. </p>

<p>Something strange is happening sometimes. If i send 1 btc from my wallet to an address on the bitcoind server, it gets through just fine and shows up right away in the log when downloading transactions via RPC.</p>

<p>If however I send from an exchange, it does not show up (at least not for a day or two). I've noticed that these exchanges add another address and amount to the same txid, could that be the cause? </p>

<p>Is there a workaround for this?</p>

<p>TIA</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Nick M</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 23:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitnoind- JSON- RPC- PHP user handling]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxvy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I asked this question on bitcoin forum too (just for the record):
<a href="http://cur.lv/6qxvz" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/6qxvz</a></p>

<p>I am trying to develop a php web application (a game, and not a gambling site) where users can make in-game purchases. Now if I am understanding it right, The architecture (using bitcoind and Json-rpc api) should be: </p>

<ul><li><p>When a new user registers - generate a new address for the new user: </p>

<blockquote>
  <p>$bitcoin-&gt;getnewaddress("username");</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Store that wallet address for later use in my DB.</p>

<p>Display that address and let a user send bitcoins to that address. </p>

<p>Check the balance of that address using the </p>

<blockquote>
  <p>$bitcoin-&gt;getbalance($username,0)</p>
</blockquote>

<p>for unonfirmed balance  and </p>

<blockquote>
  <p>getbalance($username,6)</p>
</blockquote>

<p>confirmed balance.    </p>

<p>Now I can let the user buy my in-game items
and use </p>

<blockquote>
  <p>$bitcoin-&gt;move($useraddress, $myaddress, $amount)</p>
</blockquote>

<p>to debit his account and give him the stuff he needs.</p></li>
</ul><p>Questions: </p>

<pre><code>1. Does this sound about right?  Or am I completely off here! 
2. How long does it take for the unconfirmed balance to show up?  [$bitcoin-&gt;getbalance($username,0)] 
3. $bitcoin-&gt;move($useraddress, $myaddress, $amount)  is a change of bitcoins between addresses within my wallet, so this should be
offchain and instantaneous, right? 
4.  How can some gambling dice sites like coinroll.it ( http://cur.lv/6qxw0) accept unconfirmed
transactions and lets  people play instantly? are they just taking
the risk or there is something that I am not aware of. 
5. How can I test out my bitcoind/php application with testnet? Anyone has any experience of this?
6. Suggestions on Security are welcome...
</code></pre>

<p>I am going to make parts of my code open source when I figure this shit out</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>EnderWiggins</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 23:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The BitPay Lamborghini]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxw1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw1"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxw2" alt="The BitPay Lamborghini" title="The BitPay Lamborghini"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw3"> zomg_pwn </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw4">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw1">[14 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage E-Mail Gateway]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3v]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Register | Setup Guide | FAQ | E-Mail access | E-Mail settings | Terms and conditions Bitmessage Mail Gateway This is a service to connect Bitmessage with E-Mail ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Not only is TigerDirect taking bitcoins as payment but they are actively promoting it!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxw5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw5"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxw6" alt="Not only is TigerDirect taking bitcoins as payment but they are actively promoting it!" title="Not only is TigerDirect taking bitcoins as payment but they are actively promoting it!"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw7"> ths1977 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw8">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw5">[3 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin Is Here To Stay]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxw9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Bitcoin is here to stay. Detractors will be proven wrong, no matter how many Nobel-prizes they won.</p> <p>There's enough detractors. "It is a bubble" (Jamie Dimon, Alan Greenspan, Robert Shiller). "It offers people places to hide" (Jack Lew), "Bitcoin is Evil" (Paul Krugman), "it's too volatile"....</p> <p>To be sure, some of these detractors are undoubtly very smart, but still it seems that they Just Don't Get It.</p> <p>And that's what <em>I</em> don't get. It is crystal clear that bitcoin is not just a fancy technology, but a new paradigm that <em>will</em> change the world.</p> <p>For starters, for the first time in human history, it is possible to store wealth such that it is private and secure. In other words, bitcoin offers the possibility to store wealth such that it can not be stolen or confiscated. This on its very own is an important <em>raison d'etre</em> for bitcoin. Plus that you can transfer value as easily as sending an e-mail, without needing anyones permission, at virtually no cost and without having to trust or rely on a third party. This is unprecedented in human history. This has enormous utility, as Wikileaks can attest.</p> <p>Ultimately, bitcoin is the enemy of <em>every</em> government in the world. I find it unsurprising that its inventor choses to remain anonymous for the time being.</p> <p>It is strangely amusing to see Jack Lew brushing off bitcoin as "offering a place to hide" and at the same time calling for a raise of the US debt ceiling. It can be disturbing to see Nobel laureates trolling bitcoin. And that is just the start of it.</p> <p>What will happen next, is a full-on attack on bitcoin by governments worldwide, under the guise of money laundering, terrorism, drugs, child porn, organ trading, you name it. I also expect the US government to become a lot less welcoming to bitcoin rather sooner than later.</p> <p>What can they do? Well, for instance, the US could declare it to be illegal for businesses to accept bitcoin as a payment. Obviously this will cause the value of bitcoin to plummet.</p> <p>But, to paraphrase Jamie Dimon, that will not "be the end of it". For starters, such draconic measure will raise a lot of hard questions, because then just as well outlaw cash payments. But that's not even the point.</p> <p>Because - you might as well outlaw bad weather. It is pointless. Bitcoin is designed to be fully resilient against governmental hostility. And it better be. It must be resilient, and it is, making it unstoppable, just as free speech is unstoppable. There is no way the government can prevent from two people meeting up and exchanging bitcoin and cash or goods. There is no way a government can force to keep wealth in a way that it can be confiscated. And that is what governments historically do: confiscate wealth, through inflation, through confiscation, through force.</p> <p>Governments are important, but unfortunately: power corrupts. Bitcoin has the ability to give back many of the powers of government to the people. This is also a history-first. In the future, it will force governments to serve the community. Bitcoin has the potential for people to tolerate governments, instead of the current situation in which governments are endured.</p> <p>Perhaps you find that the last paragraph sounds too far-fetched. It is not. Perhaps bitcoin will be not bitcoin but a different, improved crypto-currency. That's very unlikely, but most importantly - even if bitcoin would be replaced by a superior crypto-currency, this story would remain exactly the same except for the word 'bitcoin'.</p> <p>What I want to achieve with this post is to give some historical perspective. There is a large group of people either dismissing bitcoin as a fad, or even be hostile. This is fully understandable, because it is not that easy grasp the potential, or to have an opinion differing from that of various Nobelprize laureates.</p> <p>To bitcoin adopters I'd like this to say if you allow me. Be patient and try to explain the concept to people who are critical towards bitcoin. Don't attack them when they understandably dismiss bitcoin. Don't troll them back when they troll you. Defend bitcoin on its merits, that's plenty enough. Stick to facts.</p> <p>What must be avoided is polarisation between those who have bitcoin and those who don't. Right now such polarisation doesn't matter much. But it must be avoided. There is no point in rubbing in that the other person is stupid because <em>you</em> bought bitcoin for a tenth of the current price. All it will do is create envy and hostility. Instead, explain why bitcoin might be useful, on its merits.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwa"> trilli0nn </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxw9">[102 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Legal Cannabis Businesses to Open Up in WA, Ours Are Debating Accepting Bitcoin.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Greetings, My family is in the process of opening one (if not three) of these businesses. I'm just a lurker on here, excuse my format of this post, etc. I am familiar with some of the websites (coinbase, bitpay, etc) that could aid in this but I want to put together a portfolio to the team basically saying why this is good for them. Do you guys have any recommendations on physical POS systems and/or which websites have been working well for physical/in-store retail. </p> <p>Basically, I am proposing to be the digital currency manager for the cannabis business (I have an in as the son of the initial investor), and would like some feedback from others who have incorporated Bitcoin into physical stores. Perhaps some Coloradans could let me know any issues they have ran into? </p> <p>I feel like using Bitcoin would be pretty hassle-free, but figured I would use this as an excuse to join in on r/Bitcoin too. :) </p> <p>OH also legality..? Issues... idk.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwc"> 123taylerlee </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwb">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwb">[28 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Transaction Vs. Trade Volume]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Many 'stats/charts' sites are reporting trade volumes, without ever specifying which trade volume they are referring to:</p>

<ul><li>Number of Sent Bitcoins / 24h (Transaction Volume)</li>
<li>Number of Bitcoins sent to a Bitcoin/USD/EUR/etc exchange. (Trade Volume)</li>
</ul><p>I'm trying to gauge exactly what both BTC volumes are using sites like <a href="http://cur.lv/68b9l" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>, but I can't tell whether the USD Trade Volume figures are for the number of BTC exchanged for USD/EUR/etc or simply a dollar-conversion for the total number of BTC sent to any address over 24h.</p>

<p>Any help? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Newb</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Tiger Direct will be carrying Butterfly Labs mining equipment in near future.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwe]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwe"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxwf" alt="Tiger Direct will be carrying Butterfly Labs mining equipment in near future." title="Tiger Direct will be carrying Butterfly Labs mining equipment in near future."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwg"> Imaginize </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwe">[21 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[1 hour left to submit your suggestions to Google Moderator's "What do I want Google to do with bitcoin?"]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey guys,</p> <p>The <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow2m">What would I want Google to do with bitcoin?</a> is set to end in about an hour as Ariel @ Google has suggested to me.</p> <p>Be sure to get your best suggestions, ideas and votes in. Make them worthwhile.. Google listens. They're not aloof nor oblivious.</p> <p>As of right now the stats are: 5,862 people have submitted 1,378 suggestions and cast 51,817 votes.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow2t"> JasonBored </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwi">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwi">[10 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 21:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[TigerDirect has bought top ad for "Bitcoin" Google search results]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwj"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxwk" alt='TigerDirect has bought top ad for "Bitcoin" Google search results' title='TigerDirect has bought top ad for "Bitcoin" Google search results'></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwl"> dogshirt </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwm">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwj">[22 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 21:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[My new altcoin wallet shows hashespersec : 0.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwn]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Hello All,<br>I want to preface this question by saying that I have no interest in creating another shitcoin. This is purely and academic venture that I am undertaking in order to better understand how the Bitcoin system works. I do not have much experien...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 21:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin A Bubble?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>As the World Economic Forum (WEF) gathers in Davos, Switzerland this week, Bitcoin appears to be merely a blip on the radar for the international political and financial elite.&nbsp; Even so, comments from leaders in these fields have been less than enthusiastic Perhaps the most attention garnering sentiments have come from Robert Shiller, Nobel laureate [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxwo">Is Bitcoin A Bubble?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwp"><img alt="Bitcoin labeled 'a bubble.'" src="http://cur.lv/6qxwp" width="419" height="214"></a><p>Bitcoin met with harsh critics at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. Image: &nbsp;modified from TheBitMom</p></div>
<p>As the World Economic Forum (WEF) gathers in Davos, Switzerland this week, Bitcoin appears to be merely a blip on the radar for the international political and financial elite.&nbsp; Even so, comments from leaders in these fields have been less than enthusiastic</p>
<p>Perhaps the most attention garnering sentiments have come from Robert Shiller, Nobel laureate and Yale Professor of Economics.&nbsp; An expert in the nature of market excesses, Shiller is <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwq">quoted</a> as saying &ldquo;It is a bubble, there is no question about&hellip; It&rsquo;s just an amazing example of a bubble.&rdquo;</p>
<p>While Shiller himself suggests that Bitcoin is a return to the dark ages of currency due to the lack of clarity surrounding its use and <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">regulation</a>, he acknowledges that he understands how others may find the computer science behind the virtual currency &ldquo;inspirational.&rdquo;&nbsp; Shiller also concedes that the jump in value over the past year is &ldquo;logical&rdquo; because it follows human interest in high votility markets.</p>
<p>Treasure Secretary Jack Lew and JP Morgan Chairman and CEO Jamie Dimon had similar attitudes regarding the digital currency.&nbsp; Both admitted to sharing an &ldquo;incredulity&rdquo; about Bitcoin, with Dimon calling it a &ldquo;terrible store of value.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;The question isn&rsquo;t whether we accept it,&rdquo; Dimon <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwr">told CNBC</a>, &ldquo;[t]he question is do we even&nbsp;participate [with] people who&nbsp;facilitate bitcoin?&rdquo;&nbsp; Once Bitcoin is made to follow the same standards as other payment systems, that will &ldquo;probably be the end of them,&rdquo; he concluded.</p>
<p>Lew added to this his <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxws">concerns</a> about a virtual currency&rsquo;s potential to be misused by criminals or for terrorist activities, saying the anonymity of Bitcoin &ldquo;offers places for people to hide.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Lew has made it clear that the government will look at Bitcoin and similar transactions and will &ldquo;enforce all the rules on illegal money activity.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwt">World Economic Forum</a> is held annually in Davos-Klosters, Switzerland, and wraps up tomorrow with the Global Economic Outlook for 2014, followed by a multimedia performance titled, quite fittingly, &ldquo;A Leap of Faith.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxwo">Is Bitcoin A Bubble?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 21:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[FrontierVapor.com accepts Bitcoin! You can create your own customized eLiquid flavors for use in your favorite eCigarettes! Discount code and Free Satoshi inside.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwu]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hello fellow Bitcoin enthusiasts!</p> <p>I run an electronic cigarette site, <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwv">FrontierVapor.com</a>, which specializes in customized Made-To-Order eLiquid. Our <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxww">eLiquid Lab</a> even allows you to create your own custom flavors! We also carry a small selection of eCig hardware aimed mostly toward beginners. <strong>It is with great pleasure that I announce our grand opening and acceptance of Bitcoin!</strong> </p> <p>We've implemented Bitcoin payments through the bitpay framework, and we're ready to start mixing your custom eLiquid creations right away. You can even switch your currency to BTC and view our prices natively in Bitcoin! For the moment this is handled through the Mt.Gox API, so you may notice a slight difference in the price displayed in your cart and the final price from Bitpay's checkout service. We're working on getting it set up on the Bitpay API for more accurate on-site pricing! </p> <p>It is my <em>honor</em> to offer a 10% discount on anything in our store, whether paying with Bitcoin or not! Simply enter the coupon code "reddit" at checkout to receive your discount. At this point we're only able to accept orders within the United States, but we're working on getting set up with a global package carrier!</p> <p>I'm <em>proud</em> to serve such a wonderful community! Please, feel free to ask any questions you may have about our site or services, or even about electronic cigarettes in general. Good questions and suggestions may even get some free Satoshi!</p> <p>Thank you for your time!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwx"> FrontierVapor </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwu">[24 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[6dollarshirts.com now accepting Bitcoin!!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxwy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>It's official. 6DollarShirts, probably the best t-shirt site on the web, is accepting Bitcoin via Bitpay (like TigerDirect), so unlike Overstock, 6dollarshirts actually receives bitcoins, then puts them back into the bitcoin community.</p> <p>Every order paid in Bitcoin get a free Bitcoin hat too!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwz"> natex3000 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwy">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxwy">[22 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Orange Lamborghini - license plate "Bitpay"]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxx0]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx0"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxx1" alt='Bitcoin Orange Lamborghini - license plate "Bitpay"' title='Bitcoin Orange Lamborghini - license plate "Bitpay"'></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx2"> bruce_fenton </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx0">[31 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BUY MINING SHARES SPEND $120 RECIEVE $300]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxx4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[CLICK THIS LINK AND BUY MINING SHARES<br><br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx5" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/6qxx5</a><br><br><br>No hidden fees or mining equipment to purchase<br>14 day 100% money back guarantee!<br>No pre-orders (10 KnC Neptune #1 batch miners already ordered)<br>Outstan...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BUY MINING SHARES SPEND $120 RECIEVE $300]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxx6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[CLICK THIS LINK AND BUY MINING SHARES<br><br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx5" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/6qxx5</a><br><br><br>No hidden fees or mining equipment to purchase<br>14 day 100% money back guarantee!<br>No pre-orders (10 KnC Neptune #1 batch miners already ordered)<br>Outstan...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[These Angel Investors Want to Make Bitcoin 'Sexy' for Average People]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxx7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjrk"> anthonykantara </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx8">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxx7">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[I transferred BTC from mtgox and they have disappeared - What should/can I do?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxx9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I sent 3 btc from mtgox to cavirtex. The address used is correct and I was given a transaciton ID by mtgox. Yet blockchain.info shows no record of a transaction and 3 btc are missing.
I have written to both mtgox and cavirtex to ask about them - still no replies.</p>

<p>What can I do? How do I know if they have been stolen?</p>

<p>This question with an accepted answer is related - or more to the point mine is a duplicate of it:
<a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxa">Transaction not found</a></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>val</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 20:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[I forgot my llitecoin-qt password :( I have a .bat backup thou!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I forgot my llitecoin-qt password :( I have a .bat backup thou! Im on a mac is there anything I can do to recover password or access my coins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user12647</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 19:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Location of blockchain locally on different platforms, and structure of blockchain file?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I just downloaded Bitcoin-QT, and torrented a snapshot of the block chain that is a couple weeks old. I put the bootstrap.dat in ~/Library/Application Support/Bitcoin and started up the app. Right now it is "Importing blocks from disk". Where do the blocks goes once they've been imported? A friend of mine says that the Bitcoin app makes a Merkle tree out of the blocks in the block chain. How is this stored? I want to write a program that takes snapshots of the block chain every couple hours. It would be much better if I could just update a copy of the block chain as needed instead of making an entire new copy and deleting the old copy.</p>

<p>How do I make a bootstrap.dat out of the blkXXXXX.dat files?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Broseph</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 19:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[If I backup my wallet.dat once, am I forever safe?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have a dogecoin (though should be similar to bitcoin/altcoins) wallet and I encrypted and backed up my wallet.dat file to a few different places (different cloud providers). </p>

<p>Now, assuming I never create a completely new wallet, do I ever need to update the wallet.dat file that I have backed up? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Earlz</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 19:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can I trust the peers I am connected to?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxe]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>From my understanding of Bitcoin, it operates on a P2P network. Having just downloaded a wallet app, I see it is connected to 6 peers. Does the Bitcoin protocol rely on trusting these peers? What does it mean if these 6 peers turn out to be fake, and I'm part of a 'micro-economy' rather than Bitcoin proper?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Brendon</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there any way to &quot;revoke&quot; a bitcoin address?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Given e.g. one lost the private key to a specific bitcoin address, is there any way to make sure no more bitcoins can be transferred to it since it effectively became a bitcoin-furnace?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Tobias Kienzler</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 18:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[My Drunk Kitchen about Bitcoins!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxg"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxxh" alt="My Drunk Kitchen about Bitcoins!" title="My Drunk Kitchen about Bitcoins!"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxi"> linuxbman </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxj">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxg">[22 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[This is What it's Like to Be a Woman at a Bitcoin Meetup]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxk"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxxl" alt="This is What it's Like to Be a Woman at a Bitcoin Meetup" title="This is What it's Like to Be a Woman at a Bitcoin Meetup"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxm"> hightorque </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxn">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxk">[259 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 18:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Richard Branson: 6 Bitcoin Customers Confirmed for Virgin Space Filght]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxo"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxxp" alt="Richard Branson: 6 Bitcoin Customers Confirmed for Virgin Space Filght" title="Richard Branson: 6 Bitcoin Customers Confirmed for Virgin Space Filght"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv0a"> DigSomeMore </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxq">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxo">[21 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 18:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Branson on http://cur.lv/6qxxr Take that, Mr. Dimon]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxs"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxxt" alt="Branson on http://cur.lv/6qxxr Take that, Mr. Dimon" title="Branson on http://cur.lv/6qxxr Take that, Mr. Dimon"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxu"> BitcoinBigMoney </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxv">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxs">[54 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[im new in bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<br>hi, i'm new on bitcoin, someone can explain me some things??!?<br><br><br>I try to use my GPU for mining with cgminer version 3.7.2<br>how I set the GPU temperature visible?<br>How I know mining something?<br><br><br>bat: cgminer.exe -o <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxx" target="_blank">http://cur.lv/6cg91</a> -u user -p pass...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[FYI for Bitcoiners: Stock markets falling sharply today because of currency crises in emerging markets.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxxy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxy"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxxz" alt="FYI for Bitcoiners: Stock markets falling sharply today because of currency crises in emerging markets." title="FYI for Bitcoiners: Stock markets falling sharply today because of currency crises in emerging markets."></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy0"> drcode </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy1">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxxy">[50 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E78 – Bitcoin Boots on the Ground]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxy2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E78 &ndash; Bitcoins&rsquo; Boots on the Ground Michael Yeung is the founder of the Simon Fraser Bitcoin Club (http://cur.lv/6qxy3), located in Vancouver, Canada. From ATMs, to events to the growth of user adoption, I spoke with Mike earlier this month about [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Let's Talk Bitcoin!</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[World's first bitcoin ATM processed $1 million in transactions last month, brokers to install more machines]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxy4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy4"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxy5" alt="World's first bitcoin ATM processed $1 million in transactions last month, brokers to install more machines" title="World's first bitcoin ATM processed $1 million in transactions last month, brokers to install more machines"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy6"> directlinkz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy7">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy4">[29 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Newegg Contemplating Bitcoin Acceptance]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxy8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy8"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxy9" alt="Newegg Contemplating Bitcoin Acceptance" title="Newegg Contemplating Bitcoin Acceptance"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy6"> directlinkz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxya">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxy8">[33 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Just arrived to Miami for the NA bitcoin conference and spotted this in the wild! :)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyb"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxyc" alt="Just arrived to Miami for the NA bitcoin conference and spotted this in the wild! :)" title="Just arrived to Miami for the NA bitcoin conference and spotted this in the wild! :)"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyd"> maraoz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxye">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyb">[18 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can you help test it?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Hello. Please visit our new <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyg" title="Provably fair Bitcoin casino">bitcoin casino</a>. It'll be great if you comment what you like/dislike. Or find some bugs))</p>
<p>Thank you guys.</p>
<p>Link: <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyh" title="Best bitcoin roulette"></a><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyg">http://cur.lv/6qxyi</a></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>lalabum</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[NoFiatCoin | XNF; Crypto currency backed by bullion (Gold &amp; Silver)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyj(gold-silver)/msg7310/#msg7310]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<br><br>The year of 2014, as expected, has seen new crypto currencies among them is <strong>NoFiatCoin | XNF</strong> which is backed by bullion. The coin is first among others which is backed by something (Bullion). As per the [url=http://cur.lv/6qxyk...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 14:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Do you now best bitcoin casino?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyl]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Anybody plays in this casino? <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyg">http://cur.lv/6qxyi</a></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>lalabum</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 14:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[WikiLeaks just tweeted out that the majority of their public funding is coming in via Bitcoin and Litecoin. Great job guys, keep it up!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxym]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyn"> jamh </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxym">[101 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 14:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[TigerDirect processes $250,000 in Bitcoin Payments in first 17 hours]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyp"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxyq" alt="TigerDirect processes $250,000 in Bitcoin Payments in first 17 hours" title="TigerDirect processes $250,000 in Bitcoin Payments in first 17 hours"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyr"> vistabrownerd </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxys">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyp">[318 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 11:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Multipath support discussion thread [pre-Ripple Labs design discussion]]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyt">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How can I delete Identities?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>As I can't find the file 'keys.dat' anywhere in the new Bitmessage my question is: Where it is gone?</p> <p>On the whole I think that the identities should be deleted where they are. They could be 'protected' but you should be able to make an identity just for one to talk and to delete it then.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyw"> berndfleisig </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyv">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Scaling Cryptocurrency With Ripple | P2P Connects Us]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxyy]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyz">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxyy">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 06:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Brian Chesky, CEO of Airbnb asks if they should accept Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxz0]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<table><tr><td> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz0"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxz1" alt="Brian Chesky, CEO of Airbnb asks if they should accept Bitcoin" title="Brian Chesky, CEO of Airbnb asks if they should accept Bitcoin"></a> </td><td> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz2"> bitcoinbravo </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz3">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz0">[95 comments]</a> </td></tr></table>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 04:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is Bitcoin and why should you care?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxz4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>What is Bitcoin, and why do you care? Bitcoin is freedom for money. Let me explain: Bitcoin is third &ldquo;democratization&rdquo; that I&rsquo;ve had the privilege of living through. The first was the Internet of course, the democratization of communication. No longer did you need a printing press, runners, trucks, call boys in order to make your voice heard. Now all you needed is WordPress and a good story. Look at Matt Drudge. He has singlehandedly revolutionized political reporting. His influence is at times stronger than the New York Times. And it&rsquo;s just him and an assistant and a very, very simple website. The second democratization is 3d printing, or &ldquo;additive manufacturing&rdquo;. It is the democratization of manufacturing and its in [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxz4">What is Bitcoin and why should you care?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz4"><img width="1024" height="640" src="http://cur.lv/6qxz5" alt="Bitcoin Networked"></a><p>What is Bitcoin, and why do you care?</p>
<p>Bitcoin is freedom for money.</p>
<p>Let me explain: Bitcoin is third &ldquo;democratization&rdquo; that I&rsquo;ve had the privilege of living through.</p>
<p>The first was the Internet of course, the democratization of communication. No longer did you need a printing press, runners, trucks, call boys in order to make your voice heard. Now all you needed is WordPress and a good story. Look at Matt Drudge. He has singlehandedly revolutionized political reporting. His influence is at times stronger than the New York Times. And it&rsquo;s just him and an assistant and a very, very simple website.</p>
<p>The second democratization is 3d printing, or &ldquo;additive manufacturing&rdquo;. It is the democratization of manufacturing and its in full swing. You no longer need a factory to make a product. You can already manufacture in plastic from your desk. In less than 10 years you&rsquo;ll be able to do it in metal, in color with moving parts.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is the third democratization, the democratization of money. Right now, your money, the money you worked for, saved and earned isn&rsquo;t really yours. The banks charge you fees for holding it (and sometimes lose it). Governments have confiscated it at times (remember Cyprus?). If you want to move it, there are restrictions as to how much and when, and if you want to spend large amounts of it, you must account for how you got it.</p>
<p>Bitcoin, and crypto currencies in general solve this problem. They are in essence a &ldquo;trusted distributed public transaction ledger&rdquo;. Imagine a hotel register. Guests sign in, date, room, etc &hellip; That is a transaction ledger. Distributed means that the machines that process that ledger, the &ldquo;book&rdquo; if you will, are spread throughout the world with many different ownership hands so that it is very, very difficult for them to collaborate to cheat. Public, because it is open for anyone to inspect.</p>
<p>And trusted, because that is the most important thing of all. Do I trust that you really have the money? That you haven&rsquo;t spent it already, maybe even a second ago? Ensuring all of that is what the &ldquo;mining&rdquo; machines really do. The miners are the unseen heroes of Bitcoin. Without miners there is no coin.</p>
<p>The adoption of Bitcoin will drastically reduce the amount of financial control anyone can exert over your money. And without that control they can&rsquo;t tax you and if they can&rsquo;t tax you they can&rsquo;t control you. They know this, they are scared and they should be.</p>
<p>With Bitcoin there are no borders to money. It flows as easily as water from a spilled cup upsetting the plans of the bankers to monitor, control, restrict, tax and otherwise devalue YOUR money.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is freedom for money. Switch to Bitcoin, free your money.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxz4">What is Bitcoin and why should you care?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>David Mondrus</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 01:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Viewing .bit Domain Names in Firefox]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxz6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm following the instructions on <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz7" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/6qxz7</a> and I have installed foxy proxy and I have gone to several .bit sites. But all of them I see are exactly the same. All of the .bit sites say the following?</p>

<p>Namecoin is a peer-to-peer, alternative distributed Domain Name System based on Bitcoin software. It provides cheap .bit domain names that are not regulated by any central authority.</p>

<p>Download the Namecoin client
Install the Namecoin client on your computer to access the Namecoin network and register your .bit domains.</p>

<p>Configure your DNS
Change your DNS settings on your computer or on your whole network to enable access to .bit websites.</p>

<p>Spread the word
Namecoin is still growing. Use the Facebook and Twitter share buttons on this page to spread the word and help it grow even faster!</p>

<p>Have the site owners not put any websites up and I'm seeing the default installation pages? Or have I configured my browser wrong?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ben P. Dorsi-Todaro</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 01:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Moneyness: What equity markets can learn from bitcoin and ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxz8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxz8">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 01:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[[bitmessage.ch] Subscribing to a channel?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovvv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Hey, is it somehow possible to subscribe to a channel of a certain person with bitmassage adress from bitmessage.ch? </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovvw"> throwawy021392 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovvx">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovvv">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ethereum: A Next-Generation Cryptocurrency and Decentralized Application Platform]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovx6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of this article, Vitalik Buterin, is also the founder of Ethereum, and this article is intended as an expository piece and not a review. Over the past year, there has been an increasingly large amount of discussion around so-called &ldquo;Bitcoin 2.0&Prime; protocols &ndash; alternative cryptographic networks that are inspired by Bitcoin, but which intend to make the underlying technology usable for far more than just currency. The earliest implementation of this idea was Namecoin, a Bitcoin-like currency created in 2010 which would be used for decentralized domain name registration. More recently, we have seen the emergence of colored coins, allowing users to create their own currencies on the Bitcoin network, and more advanced protocols like Mastercoin, Bitshares and [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovx6">Ethereum: A Next-Generation Cryptocurrency and Decentralized Application Platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovx6"><img width="1024" height="604" src="http://cur.lv/6ovx7" alt="Screen Shot 2014-01-21 at 4.03.11 PM"></a><p><em><small>The author of this article, Vitalik Buterin, is also the founder of Ethereum, and this article is intended as an expository piece and not a review.</small></em></p>
<p>Over the past year, there has been an increasingly large amount of discussion around so-called &ldquo;Bitcoin 2.0&Prime; protocols &ndash; alternative cryptographic networks that are inspired by Bitcoin, but which intend to make the underlying technology usable for far more than just currency. The earliest implementation of this idea was Namecoin, a Bitcoin-like currency created in 2010 which would be used for decentralized domain name registration. More recently, we have seen the emergence of <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovx8">colored coins</a>, allowing users to create their own currencies on the Bitcoin network, and more advanced protocols like <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovx9">Mastercoin</a>, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxa">Bitshares</a> and <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxb">Counterparty</a> which intend to provide features such as financial derivatives, savings wallets and decentralized exchange. However, up until these point all of the protocols that have been invented have been specialized, attempting to offer specific and rich feature sets targeted toward specific industries or applications usually financial in nature. Now, a group of developers including myself have come up with a project that takes the opposite track: a cryptocurrency network that intends to be as generalized as possible, allowing anyone to create specialized applications on top for almost any purpose imaginable. The project: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxc">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<h3>Cryptocurrency Protocols Are Like Onions&hellip;</h3>
<p>One common design philosophy among many cryptocurrency 2.0 protocols is the idea that, just like the internet, cryptocurrency design would work best if protocols split off into different layers. Under this strain of thought, Bitcoin is to be thought of as a sort of <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxd">TCP</a>/<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxe">IP</a> of the cryptocurrency ecosystem, and other next-generation protocols can be built on top of Bitcoin much like we have SMTP for email, HTTP for webpages and XMPP for chat all on top of TCP as a common underlying data layer.</p>
<p>So far, the three main protocols that have followed this model are colored coins, Mastercoin and Counterparty. The way the colored coins protocol works is simple. First, in order to create colored coins, a user tags specific bitcoins as having a special meaning; for example, if Bob is a gold issuer, he may wish to tag some set of bitcoins and say that each satoshi represents 0.1 grams of gold redeemable from him. The protocol then tracks those bitcoins through the blockchain, and in that way it is possible to calculate who owns them at any time.</p>
<p>Mastercoin and Counterparty are somewhat more abstract; they use the Bitcoin blockchain to store data, so a Mastercoin or Counterparty transaction is a Bitcoin transaction, but the protocols interpret the transactions in a completely different way. One can have two Mastercoin transactions, one sending 1 MSC and the other 100000 MSC, but from the point of view of a Bitcoin user that does not know how that Mastercoin protocol works they both look like small transactions sending 0.0006 BTC each; the Mastercoin-specific metadata is encoded in the transaction outputs. A Mastercoin client then needs to search the Bitcoin blockchain for Mastercoin transactions in order to determine the current Mastercoin balance sheet.</p>
<p>I personally have had the privilege of talking directly to many of the originators of the colored coins and Mastercoin protocol, and have participated considerably in the development of both projects. However, over about two months of research and particpation, what I eventually came to realize is that, while the underlying idea of having such high-level protocols on top of low-level protocols is laudable, there are fundamental flaws in the implementations, as they stand today, that may well prevent the projects from ever gaining anything more than a small amount of traction.</p>
<p>The reason is not that the ideas behind the protocols themselves are bad; the ideas are excellent, and the response of the community alone is proof that they are trying to do something that is very much needed. Rather, the reason is that the low-level protocol that they are trying to build their high-level protocols on top of, Bitcoin, is simply not cut out for the task. This is not to say that Bitcoin is bad, or is not a revolutionary invention; as a protocol for storing and transferring value, Bitcoin is excellent. However, as far as being an effective low-level protocol is concerned, Bitcoin is less effective; rather than being like a TCP on top of which one can build HTTP, Bitcoin is like SMTP: a protocol that is good at its intended task (in SMTP&rsquo;s case email, in Bitcoin&rsquo;s case money), but not particularly good as a foundation for anything else.</p>
<p>The specific failure of Bitcoin is particularly concentrated in one place: scalability. Bitcoin itself is as scalable as a cryptocurrency can be; even if the blockchain balloons to over a terabyte, there is a protocol called &ldquo;simplified payment verification&rdquo;, described in the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxf">Bitcoin whitepaper</a> that allows &ldquo;light clients&rdquo; with only a few megabytes of bandwidth and storage to securely determine whether or not they have received transactions. With colored coins and Mastercoin, however, this possibility disappears. The reason is this. In order to determine what color a colored coin is, you need to not just use Bitcoin simplified payment verification to prove that it exists; you also need to trace it all the way back to its genesis, and do an SPV check each step of the way. Sometimes, the backward scan is exponential; and with metacoin protocols there is no way to know anything at all without verifying every single transaction.</p>
<p>And this is what Ethereum intends to fix. Ethereum does not intend to be a Swiss Army knife protocol with hundreds of features to suit every need; instead, Ethereum aims to be a superior foundational protocol, and allow other decentralized applications to build on top of it instead of Bitcoin, giving them more tools to work with and allowing them to gain the full benefits of Ethereum&rsquo;s scalability and efficiency.</p>
<h3>Contacts, Not Just For Difference</h3>
<p>At the time that Ethereum was being developed, there was a large amount of interest in allowing financial contracts on top of cryptocurrencies; the basic type of contract being a &ldquo;contract for difference&rdquo;. In a contract for difference, two parties agree to put in some amount of money, and then get money out in a proportion that depends on the value of some underlying asset. For example, a CFD might have Alice put in $1000, Bob put in $1000, and then after 30 days the blockchain would automatically return to Alice $1000 plus $100 for every dollar that the LTC/USD price went up during that time period and send Bob the rest. These contracts allow people to speculate on assets at high leverage, or alternatively protect themselves from cryptocurrency volatility by canceling out their exposure, without any centralized exchange.</p>
<p>At this point, however, it is clear that contracts for difference are really only one special case of a much more general concept: contracts for formula. Instead of having the contract take in $x for Alice, $y from Bob, and return to Alice $x plus an additional $z for every dollar that some given ticker went up, a contract should be able to return to A an amount of funds based on any mathematical formula, allowing contracts of arbitrary complexity. If the formula allows random data as inputs, these generalized CFDs can even be used to implement a sort of peer-to-peer gambling.</p>
<p>Ethereum takes this idea and pushes it one step further. Instead of contracts being agreements between two parties that start and end, contracts in Ethereum are like a sort of autonomous agent simulated by the blockchain. Each Ethereum contract has its own internal scripting code, and the scripting code is activated every time a transaction is sent to it. The scripting language has access to the transaction&rsquo;s value, sender and optional data fields, as well some block data and its own internal memory, as inputs, and can send transactions. To make a CFD, Alice would create a contract and seed it with $1000 worth of cryptocurrency, and then wait for Bob to accept the contract by sending a transction containing $1000 as well. The contract would then be programmed to start a timer, and after 30 days Alice or Bob would be able to send a small transaction to the contract to activate it again and release the funds.</p>
<p>Aside from this narrow contract-for-difference model, however, the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxg">whitepaper</a> outlines many other transaction types that will become possible with Ethereum scripting, of which a few include:</p>
<div>
<br>
Code example of an Ethereum currency contract, written in a high-level language.<br><br><small>
<pre>
if tx.value 
<p></p></pre></small>
</div>
<ul><li><strong>Multisignature escrows</strong>, of a similar spirit to the Bitcoin arbitration service <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxh">Bitrated</a>, but with more complex rules than Bitcoin. For example, there will be no need for the signers to pass around partially signed transactions manually; people can authorize a withdrawal asynchronously over the blockchain one at a time and then have the transaction finalized automatically once enough people make their authorizations.</li>
<li><strong>Savings accounts</strong> - one interesting setup works as follows. Suppose that Alice wants to store a large amount of money, but does not want to risk losing everything if her private key is lose or stolen. She makes a contract with Bob, a semi-trustworthy bank, with the following rules: Alice is allowed to withdraw up to 1% per day, Alice with Bob approval can withdrawn any amount, and Bob alone can withdraw up to 0.05% per day. Normally, Alice will only need small amounts at a time, and if Alice wants more she can prove her identity to Bob and make the withdrawal. If Alice's private key gets stolen, she can run to Bob and move the funds into another contract before the thief gets away with more than 1% of the funds. If Alice loses her private key, Bob will eventually be able to recover her funds. And if Bob turns out to be evil, Alice can withdraw her own funds twenty times faster than he can. In short, all of the security of traditional banking, but with almost none of the trust.</li>
<li><strong>Peer-to-peer gambling</strong> - any kind of <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxi">peer-to-peer gambling</a> protocol can be implemented on top of Ethereum. A very basic protocol would simply be a contract for difference on random data such as a block hash.</li>
<li><strong>Creating your own currency</strong> - using Ethereum's internal memory store, you can create an entire new currency inside of Ethereum. These new currencies can be constructed to interact with each other, have a decentralized exchange, or any other kind of advanced features.</li>
</ul><p>This is the advantage of Ethereum code: because the scripting language is designed to have no restrictions except for a fee system, essentially any kind of rules can be encoded inside of it. One can even have an entire company manage its savings on the blockchain, with a contract saying that, for example, 60% of the current shareholders of a company are needed to agree to move any funds (and perhapps 30% can move a maximum of 1% per day). Other, less traditionally capitalistic, structures are also possible; one idea is for a democratic organization with the only rule being that two thirds of the existing members of a group must agree to invite another member.</p>
<h3>Beyond the Financial</h3>
<p>The financial applications, however, only scratch the surface of what Ethereum, and cryptographic protocols on top of Ethereum, can do. While Ethereum's financial applications may be what initially excites many people in the cryptocurrency community, the long-term promise is arguably in the ways that Ethereum can work together with other, non-financial, peer-to-peer protocols. One of the main problems that non-financial peer-to-peer protocols have faced so far is the lack of incentive - that is to say, unlike centralized for-profit platforms, there is no financial reason to participate. In some cases, participation is in some sense its own reward; it is for this reason that people continue to write open source software, contribute to Wikipedia, and make comments on forums and write blog posts. In the context of peer-to-peer protocols, however, participation is often not a "fun" activity in any meaningful sense; rather, it consists of putting in a large quantity of resources, letting a daemon run in the background potentially hogging CPU and battery power, and forgetting about it.</p>
<p>For example, there have already for a long time been data protocols such as Freenet that essentially provide everyone with decentralized uncensorable static content hosting; in practice, however, Freenet is very slow, and few people contribute resources. File sharing protocols all suffer from the same problem: although altruism is good enough for spreading popular commercial blockbusters around, it becomes markedly less effective for those with less mainstream preferences. Thus, perversely, the peer-to-peer nature of file sharing may actually be helping the centralization of entertainment and media production, not hindering it. All of these problems, however, can potentially be solved if we add incentivization - empowering people to build not just nonprofit side projects, but also businesses and livelihoods, around participating in the network.</p>
<ul><li><strong>Incentivized data storage</strong> - essentially, a decentralized Dropbox. The idea works as follows: if a user wants to have a 1GB file backed up by the network, they would construct a data structure known as a Merkle tree out of the data. They would then put the root of the tree, along with 10 ether, into a contract and upload the file onto another specialized network that nodes wishing to rent out their hard drive space would listen for messages on. Every day, the contract would automatically pick a random branch of the tree (eg. "left -&gt; right -&gt; left -&gt; left -&gt; left -&gt; right -&gt; left"), ending at a block of the file, and give 0.01 ether to the first node to provide that branch. Nodes would store the entire file to maximize their chance of getting the reward.</li>
<li><strong>BitMessage and Tor</strong> - <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxj">Bitmessage</a> is a next-generation email protocol that is both fully decentralized and encrypted, allowing anyone to send messages to any other Bitmessage user securely without relying on any third parties except for the network. However, Bitmessage has one large usability flaw: instead of sending messages to human-friendly email addresses, like "bob@gmail.com", you need to send to garbled 34-character Bitmessage addresses (eg. "BM-BcbRqcFFSQUUmXFKsPJgVQPSiFA3Xash"). Ethereum contracts offer a solution: people can register their names on a special Ethereum contract, and Bitmessage clients can query the Ethereum blockchain to get the 34-character Bitmessage address associated with any name behind the scenes. The online anonymizing network Tor suffers from the same problems, and thus can also benefit from this solution.</li>
<li><strong>Identity and Reputation Systems</strong> - once you can register your name on the blockchain, the logical next step is obvious: have a web of trust on the blockchain. Webs of trust are a key part of an effective peer to peer communication infrastructure: you don't just want to know that a given public key refers to a given person; you also want to know that the person is trustworthy in the first place. The solution is to use social networks: if you trust A, A trusts B, and B trusts C, then there is a pretty good chance that you can trust C, at least to some extent. Ethereum can serve as the data layer for a fully decentralized reputation system - and potentially ultimately a fully decentralized marketplace.</li>
</ul><p>Many of the above applications consist of actual peer-to-peer protocols and projects that are already well under development; in those cases, we intend to establish partnerships with as many of these projects as we can, and help fund them in exchange for bringing their value into the Ethereum ecosystem. We want to help not just the cryptocurrency community, but also the peer to peer community as a whole, including file sharing, torrents, data storage and mesh networking. We believe that there are many projects, especially in the non-financial area, that can potentially bring great value to the community, but for which development is underfunded precisely because they lack an opportunity to effectively introduce a financial component; perhaps Ethereum may be what ultimately pushes dozens of these projects to the next stage.</p>
<p>Why are all of these applications possible on top of Ethereum? The answer lies in the currency's internal programming language. An analogy here may be made with the internet. Back in 1996, the web was nothing but HTML, and all people could do with it was serve static web pages on sites like Geocities. Then, people decided that there was a great need for people to submit forms in HTML, so HTML added a forms feature. This was like a "colored coins" of web protocols: try to solve a specific problem, but do it on top of a weak protocol without looking at the larger picture. Soon, however, we came up with Javascript, a programming language inside the web browser. And it was Javascript that solved the problem: because Javascript is a universal, Turing-complete programming language, it can be used to build apps of arbitrary complexity; Gmail, Facebook and even Bitcoin wallets have all been made with the language. And this was not because the Javascript developers decided that they wanted people to build Gmail, Facebook, and Bitcoin wallets; they just wanted a programming language. What we can do with the language is up to our own imaginations. And that is the spirit that we want to bring to Ethereum. Ethereum does not intend to be the end of all cryptocurrency innovation; it intends to be the beginning.</p>
<h3>Further Innovations</h3>
<p>Along with its main feature of a Turing-complete, universal scripting language, Ethereum will also have a number of other improvements over existing cryptocurrency:</p>
<ul><li><strong>Fees</strong> - Ethereum contracts will regulate its Turing-complete functionality and prevent abusive transactions such as memory hogs and infinite loop scripts by instituting a transaction fee for each computational step of script execution. More expensive operations, such as storage accesses and cryptographic operations, will have higher fees, and there will also be a fee for every item of storage that a contract fills up. To encourage contracts to clean up after themselves, if a contract reduces the amount of storage that it uses a negative fee will be charged; in fact, there is a special <code>SUICIDE</code> opcode to clear a contract and send all funds and the hefty negative fee back to its creator.</li>
<li><strong>Mining algorithms</strong> - there has been a lot of interest into making cryptocurrencies whose mining is resistant against specialized hardware, allowing ordinary users with commodity hardware to participate without any capital investment and helping to avoid centralization. So far, the main antidote has been Scrypt, a mining algorithm that requires a large amount of both computational power and memory to compute; however, Scrypt is not memory-hard enough, and there are companies building specialized devices for it. We have come up with <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxk">Dagger</a>, a prototype proof of work that is even more memory-hard than Scrypt, as well as prototype proof-of-stake algorithms such as <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxl">Slasher</a> that get around the issue of mining entirely. Ultimately, however, we intend to host a contest, similar to the contests that determined the standards for AES and SHA3, where we invite research groups from universities around the world to devise the best possible commodity-hardware-friendly possible mining algorithm.</li>
<li><strong>GHOST</strong> - GHOST is a new block propagation protocol <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxm">pioneered by Aviv Zohar and Yonatan Sompolinsky</a> that allows blockchains to have much faster block confirmation times, ideally in the range of 3-30 seconds, without running into the issues of centralization and high stale rate that fast block confirmations normally bring. Ethereum is the first major currency to integrate a simplified single-level version of GHOST as part of its protocol.</li>
</ul><h3>The Plan</h3>
<p>Ethereum is potentially a massive and wide-reaching undertaking, and will take months to develop. With that in mind, the currency will be released in multiple stages. The first stage, the release of the whitepaper, has <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxg">already happened</a>. <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxn">Forums</a>, a <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxo">wiki</a> and a <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxp">blog</a> have been set up, and anyone is free to visit them and set up an account and comment on the forums. On January 25, a 60-day fundraiser will launch at the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxq">confrence in Miami</a>, during which anyone will be able to purchase ether, Ethereum's internal currency, for BTC much like the Mastercoin fundraiser; the price will be 1000 ether for 1 BTC, although early investors will get roughly a 2x benefit to compensate for the increased risk that they're taking for participating in the project earlier. The fundraiser participants will not just get ether; there will also be a number of additional rewards, likely including free tickets to conferences, a spot to put 32 bytes into the genesis block, and for the top donors even the ability to name three sub-units of the currency (eg. the equivalent of the "microbitcoin" in BTC).</p>
<p>The issuance of Ethereum will not be any single mechanism; instead, a compromise approach combining the benefits of multiple approaches will be used. The issuance model will work as follows:</p>
<ul><li>Ether will be released in a fundraiser at the price of 1000-2000 ether per BTC, with earlier funders getting a better price to compensate for the increased uncertainty of participating at an earlier stage. The minimum funding amount will be 0.01 BTC. Suppose that X ether gets released in this way</li>
<li>0.225X ether will be allocated to the fiduciary members and early contributors who substantially participated in the project before the start of the fundraiser. This share will be stored in a time-lock contract; about 40% of it will be spendable after one year, 70% after two years and 100% after 3 years.</li>
<li>0.05X ether will be allocated to a fund to use to pay expenses and rewards in ether between the start of the fundraiser and the launch of the currency</li>
<li>0.225X ether will be allocated as a long-term reserve pool to pay expenses, salaries and rewards in ether after the launch of the currency</li>
<li>0.4X ether will be mined per year forever after that point</li>
</ul><p>There is an important distinction compared to Bitcoin and most other cryptocurrencies: here, the eventual supply is unlimited. The "permanent linear inflation" model is designed to make ether neither inflationary nor deflationary; the lack of a supply cap is intended to dampen some of the speculative and wealth inequality effects of existing currencies, but at the same time the linear, rather than traditionally exponential, inflation model will mean that the effective inflation rate tends to zero over time. Additionally, because the initial currency supply will not start from zero, the currency supply growth in the first eight years will actually be slower than Bitcoin, giving fundraiser participants and early adopters a chance to benefit substantially in the medium term.</p>
<p>At some point in February, we will release a centralized testnet - a server which anyone can use to send transactions and create contracts. Soon after that, the decentralized testnet will come, which we will use to test different mining algorithms and make sure that the peer to peer daemon works and is secure, and take measurements to look for optimizations to the scripting language. Finally, once we are sure that the protocol and the client is secure, we will release the genesis block, and allow mining to begin.</p>
<h3>Looking Forward</h3>
<p>Since Ethereum includes a Turing-complete scripting language, it can be mathematically proven that it can do essentially anything that a Bitcoin-like blockchain-based cryptocurrency potentially can do. But there are still problems that the protocol, as it stands today, leaves unresolved. For example, Ethereum offers no solution for the fundamental scalability problem in all blockchain-based cryptocurrencies - namely, the fact that every full node must store the entire balance sheet and verify every transaction. Ethereum's concept of a separate "state tree" and "transaction list", borrowed from Ripple, mitigates this to some extent, but nevertheless no fundamental breakthrough is mine. For that, technology like Eli ben Sasson's <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxr">Secure Computational Integrity and Privacy</a> (SCIP), now under development, will be required. </p>
<p>Additionally, Ethereum offers no improvements on traditional proof-of-work mining with all its flaws, and proof of excellence and Ripple-style consensus are left unexplored. If it turns out that <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgaj">proof of stake</a> or some other proof of work algorithm is a better solution, then future cryptocurrencies may use proof of stake algorithms like <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxs">MC2</a> and <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovxl">Slasher</a> instead. If there is room for an Ethereum 2.0, it is in these areas that it the improvements will lie. And ultimately, Ethereum is an open-ended project; if the project gets enough funding, we may even be the ones to release Ethereum 2.0 ourselves, carrying over the original account balances onto an even further improved network. Ultimately, just as is our slogan for the currency itself, the only limit is our imaginaion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovx6">Ethereum: A Next-Generation Cryptocurrency and Decentralized Application Platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Vitalik Buterin</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 19:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[TigerDirect: First Major Internet Retailer to Accept Bitcoin Via BitPay]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovy3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, TigerDirect announced its embrace of Bitcoin through BitPay, Inc. TigerDirect has met the needs of customers for over 25 years and is known for high quality, discount electronics. TigerDirect is a subsidiary of Systemax Inc. (NYSE: SYX), a Fortune 1000 company. There was no lack of excitement from the Tiger Direct Team as the front end of the website clearly displays their embrace of bitcoin with a backdrop of physical bitcoins. Who will the next high profile merchant be! BitPay and Tiger Direct Issued the following press release: FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE TIGERDIRECT IS THE FIRST MAJOR INTERNET RETAILER TO ACCEPT BITCOIN VIA BITPAY Online superstore to be largest retailer to accept new form of&nbsp;digital currency as payment Miami, FL [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovy3">TigerDirect: First Major Internet Retailer to Accept Bitcoin Via BitPay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy3"><img width="1024" height="486" src="http://cur.lv/6ovy4" alt="Tiger Direct!"></a><p dir="ltr">Today, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy5">TigerDirect </a>announced its embrace of Bitcoin through <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">BitPay, Inc</a>. TigerDirect has met the needs of customers for over 25 years and is known for high quality, discount electronics. TigerDirect is a subsidiary of Systemax Inc. (NYSE: SYX), a Fortune 1000 company. There was no lack of excitement from the Tiger Direct Team as the front end of the website clearly displays their embrace of bitcoin with a backdrop of physical bitcoins. Who will the next high profile merchant be!</p>
<p dir="ltr">BitPay and Tiger Direct Issued the following press release:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>TIGERDIRECT IS THE FIRST MAJOR INTERNET RETAILER TO ACCEPT BITCOIN VIA BITPAY</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>Online superstore to be largest retailer to accept new form of&nbsp;digital currency as payment</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Miami, FL (Monday, January 20, 2014) &ndash; <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy5">TigerDirect.com</a> has announced today that they will be accepting <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy6">Bitcoin</a>- a peer-to-peer digital currency- as a method of payment on over 200,000 products. TigerDirect is the first major US electronics retailer and largest company to date to accept the digital currency Bitcoin via BitPay.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Bitcoin has become a modern-day sensation, boasting a payment technology that competes with traditional payment methods. By cutting out the middleman, buyers and sellers of Bitcoins can deal with one another using direct deposits into electronic wallets.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;TigerDirect has always been on the forefront of alternative online payment methods and delivering the most convenient ways for our customers to shop,&rdquo; says Steven Leeds, Director of Corporate Marketing at TigerDirect. &ldquo;With individuals building their own high-powered PCs with parts offered on our site to mine Bitcoins, it&rsquo;s a logical fit.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>After several months of reviewing the options for processing Bitcoin, TigerDirect has chosen <a href="http://cur.lv/63iha">BitPay</a> to provide its customers the most reliable means of transacting Bitcoin payments on their website. &nbsp;&nbsp;TigerDirect will not only accept the digital currency as payment, but will also sell the computer components used to mine the currency as well. &nbsp;&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve partnered with AMD to build the largest assortment of mining graphic cards from Sapphire, MSI, VisionTek, Diamond and XFX in the industry.&rdquo; Customers will be able to utilize Bitcoin as payment on both the desktop and mobile websites.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>This non-traditional move should come as no surprise for those familiar with TigerDirect as a trusted name for computers and consumer electronics. In 2013, TigerDirect made waves with their presentation of the Second Annual Tech Bash, showcasing the latest in electronics to over 12,000 consumers at Miami Marlins&rsquo; Park; enjoyed over seven million views on the &ldquo;Epic Rap Battle: &nbsp;Nerd vs Geek&rdquo; viral video written and directed by Rhett &amp; Link; expanded their product offerings to new categories; and offered select customers free shipping through ShopRunner.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Staying ahead of the competition as the go-to spot for all things tech, TigerDirect&rsquo;s BitPay acceptance is another example of the online superstore&rsquo;s dedication to customer satisfaction, and using innovative technologies for the best shopping experience, in-store and on-line. TigerDirect will start accepting Bitcoin on Thursday, January 23rd.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Details regarding the acceptance of Bitcoin at TigerDirect can be found at <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy7">http://cur.lv/6ovy7</a>. &nbsp;Bitcoin will not be accepted for payment at TigerDirect physical retail locations, only online.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>About TigerDirect: For over 25 years, TigerDirect. (<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy5">http://cur.lv/6ovy8</a>) has served the needs of both personal and business computer users, selling consumer electronics, computers, digital media technology and peripherals via eCommerce, business to business, and retail channels. TigerDirect is a subsidiary of Systemax Inc. (NYSE: SYX).</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>About Systemax Inc.: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy9">Systemax Inc</a>. a Fortune 1000 company, sells personal computers, computer components and supplies, consumer electronics and industrial products through a system of branded e-Commerce websites, retail stores, relationship marketers and direct mail catalogs in North America and Europe. The primary brands are TigerDirect, MISCO, WStore and Global Industrial.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Media Contact:</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Megan Pope</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>The Workshop</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>323.397.5667</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Megan@workshopcollective.com</em></p>
<p><em>&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovy3">TigerDirect: First Major Internet Retailer to Accept Bitcoin Via BitPay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Elizabeth Ploshay</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 18:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Not A Gamble In Vegas]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxza]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The flashy lights and star-studded shows of the Las Vegas strip are about to be joined by the rising celebrity of currency, Bitcoin.&nbsp; As of next week, two of Sin City&rsquo;s casinos, The D Las Vegas Casino Hotel and Golden Gate Hotel &amp; Casino, the city&rsquo;s oldest, will be accepting Bitcoin in five of their [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxza">Bitcoin Not A Gamble In Vegas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The flashy lights and star-studded shows of the Las Vegas strip are about to be joined by the rising celebrity of currency, Bitcoin.&nbsp; As of next week, two of Sin City&rsquo;s casinos, The D Las Vegas Casino Hotel and Golden Gate Hotel &amp; Casino, the city&rsquo;s oldest, will be accepting Bitcoin in five of their locations.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzb"><img alt="Bitcoin in Vegas Casinos" src="http://cur.lv/6qxzb" width="477" height="268"></a><p>Bitcoin to be accepted in two Las Vegas casinos. Image: Getty Images</p></div>
<p>Golden Gate, the first casino in the city to install a telephone and the first to offer shrimp cocktails on its menu, prides itself on being ahead of the curve.&nbsp; Derek Stevens, co-owner of both casinos, acknowledges that consumer interest coupled with pressure from the presence of other forward-thinking businesses in the area have played no small part in the decision.&nbsp; &ldquo;Zappos is only a block away from us,&rdquo; he told Cade Metz of <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzc">Wired</a>. &ldquo;People started asking me: &lsquo;Do you accept bitcoin?&rsquo;&rdquo;</p>
<p>According to Jerry Brito, senior research fellow at the Mercatus Center of George Mason University, the immediacy of processing and absence of transaction fees offered by Bitcoin affords the virtual currency the potential to catch up to other payment forms. In an interview with <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzd">USA Today</a>, Brito likened an increased use of Bitcoin to the arrival of credit cards in the 60s, when people had previously only used cash and checks.&nbsp; He reinforced the public&rsquo;s embrace of new payment options and the willingness of businesses to promote technology by adding, &ldquo;and then Paypal came along.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Though the move to include Bitcoin in casinos is receiving equal amounts of enthusiasm and press, its use will be limited to the gift shops, hotels and bistros.&nbsp; According to all parties involved, Bitcoin will not be allowed on the casino floors for the foreseeable future.&nbsp; A.G. Burnett, chairman of the Nevada Gaming Control Board, was very clear that state regulators are in no hurry to replace the current cash-only system.&nbsp; &ldquo;We would have to have an extremely high level of comfort with virtual currency of this kind in order for that to ever occur,&rdquo; Burnett told <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxze">Bloomberg Press</a>.</p>
<p>Even Stevens agrees that there needs to be more clarity from the <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzc">IRS</a>, the U.S. Treasury, and the Department of Justice before Bitcoin receives an extension, saying &ldquo;once we have more from our government, we might be able to implement bitcoin for casino gaming, but I think we&rsquo;re still a ways away from that.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Until then, consumers will have to be content with cashing in their Bitcoin on souvenirs, suites, and shrimp cocktails.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6qxza">Bitcoin Not A Gamble In Vegas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Coinpunk is Making an Unbannable iOS Wallet]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovyk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Apple has been slashing and dashing apps that serve as Bitcoin wallets or even connect to other 3rd party wallets. Here is a short list of the companies affected by Apple&rsquo;s ban. Bitcoin Express Bitpak Blockchain.info (Full version still available on Cydia for jailbroken iPhones) Coinbase Coinjar Gliph If you haven&rsquo;t seen Apple&rsquo;s take down message here is a taste of what Bitcoin iOS developers have seen: &ldquo;We found that your app contains content &ndash; or facilitates, enables, or encourages an activity &ndash; that is not legal in all the locations in which the app is available, which is not in compliance with the App Store Review Guidelines. Specifically, the facilitation of trading of virtual currency is not appropriate for [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovyk">Coinpunk is Making an Unbannable iOS Wallet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyk"><img width="950" height="350" src="http://cur.lv/6ovyl" alt="cover2"></a><p><span>Apple has been </span><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovym">slashing and dashing apps</a><span> that serve as Bitcoin wallets or even connect to other 3rd party wallets. Here is a short list of the companies affected by Apple&rsquo;s ban.</span></p>
<ul><li>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyn">Bitcoin Express</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyo">Bitpak</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain.info (Full version <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyp">still available on Cydia</a> for jailbroken iPhones)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyq">Coinbase</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyr">Coinjar</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovys">Gliph</a></p>
</li>
</ul><p dir="ltr">If you haven&rsquo;t seen Apple&rsquo;s take down message here is a taste of what Bitcoin iOS developers have seen:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;We found that your app contains content &ndash; or facilitates, enables, or encourages an activity &ndash; that is not legal in all the locations in which the app is available, which is not in compliance with the App Store Review Guidelines.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, the facilitation of trading of virtual currency is not appropriate for the App Store.</p>
<p dir="ltr">We encourage you to review your app concept and evaluate whether you can incorporate</p>
<p dir="ltr">different content and features that are in compliance with the Guidelines.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If you wish to appeal your review, you can submit a request to the App Review Board. The App Review Board was created for developers to appeal an app review they have concerns with. Please be as specific as possible when explaining why you believe your app is in compliance with the App Store Review Guidelines.&rdquo;</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">Coinpunk is raising funds to develop an unbannable iOS Bitcoin wallet that runs using HTML which can be loaded on the Safari app. Kyle Drake, the main developer behind Coinpunk, has started an Indiegogo campaign today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kyle plans on using the Indiegogo funds to pay for the effort involved in adding the following features:</p>
<p>- Standalone/browser store versions</p>
<p dir="ltr">- Integrated support for cold wallets</p>
<p dir="ltr">- More modular code that becomes a first-class Node.js citizen</p>
<p dir="ltr">- Altcoin support</p>
<p dir="ltr">- Fully open source</p>
<p dir="ltr">The donation tiers available start at $25 which will get you Coinpunk stickers and go all the way up to $10k, which gets you a trip to Portland, Bitcoin bar crawl, and other interesting perks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Indiegogo has yet to enable support for Bitcoins, but you can still toss Kyle BTCs using the address listed on the page and emailing your transaction id.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To get a sample of what the web wallet will look like, try his web wallet out (<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyt">wallet.coinpunk.com</a>).</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Apple may be preparing to release <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyu">its own payment system</a>, there&rsquo;s no reason to spoil the party for Bitcoin lovers who own iPhones. Go and check out <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyv">Kyle&rsquo;s campaign at Indiegogo</a>.</p>
<p><em>update:&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">If you scroll waaaay down to the bottom of the donation tiers you will see a Dogecoin tier for $20k. This isn&rsquo;t just for dogecoin, but funding to implement many other cryptocurrencies. Dogecoin and Litecoin are accepted for this donation level. As Kyle says in the description of this tier, &ldquo;Many currencies, such useful.&rdquo;</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovyw"><img alt="ra_suchfirst_dogecoin_meme_" src="http://cur.lv/6ovyw" width="559" height="295"></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">This is my first dogecoin meme so please be kind.</p>
<p dir="ltr">; )&nbsp;D5dnjBfuP8FsFAvYMW5hXyyvtpZrjidEub</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovyk">Coinpunk is Making an Unbannable iOS Wallet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ruben Alexander</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s YouTube Missionaries]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovz5]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries Thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries Beacons of light welcoming the huddled masses of tired and poor yearning for financial freedom. My road to discovering the new world of economic redemption started one evening last March. An article linked from BuzzFeed&rsquo;s website entitled &ldquo;Is it Time to Take Bitcoin Seriously?&ldquo; written by Alec Liu was revealed to me. As I investigated further I found my heart inexplicitly racing; some deep-rooted primitive part of my brain connected with this article. I had discovered an obvious truth that just clicked. Alec Liu, without knowing it, was the messenger that lit the spark that started my personal obsession to this revolutionary technology. Rarely can we predict the power of [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovz5">Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovz5"><img width="1024" height="686" src="http://cur.lv/6ovz6" alt="bitcoin missionaries"></a><p><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovz5" title="click to read"><img src="http://cur.lv/6ovz7" width="620" height="415" alt="Thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries"></a></p>
<p>Thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries</p>
<h1><strong>Thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries</strong></h1>
<h4><strong>Beacons of light welcoming the huddled masses of tired and poor yearning for financial freedom.</strong></h4>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovz6"><img alt="bitcoin missionaries" src="http://cur.lv/6ovz7" width="620" height="415"></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">My road to discovering the new world of economic redemption started one evening last March. An article linked from<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovz8"> BuzzFeed&rsquo;s website</a> entitled<a href="http://cur.lv/6ovz9"> &ldquo;Is it Time to Take Bitcoin Seriously?</a>&ldquo; written by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ovza">Alec Liu</a> was revealed to me. As I investigated further I found my heart inexplicitly racing; some deep-rooted primitive part of my brain connected with this article. I had discovered an obvious truth that just clicked. Alec Liu, without knowing it, was the messenger that lit the spark that started my personal obsession to this revolutionary technology. Rarely can we predict the power of our words and ideas. I doubt he could have predicted when he wrote that article for the on-line magazine Motherboard Vice who he might inspire or even that he had the power to do so. Could he have prophesied the course of life he would someday change?</p>
<p><span>My &ldquo;a-ha&rdquo; moment arrived. Yet I had to convince my skeptical side so I did what millions of others do when they want to know more about something &ndash; I consulted the &ldquo;experts&rdquo; on YouTube. &nbsp;There were quite a bit to choose from both pro and against the idea of digital currency. I reasoned out their best arguments as I&rsquo;m sure our readers have done. Slowly and diligently I found reasonable answers to each of their arguments against the technology. It mostly boiled down to &ldquo;it&rsquo;s never been done before&rdquo;. I&rsquo;ve yet to see any great new invention or technology built, designed or conceived by skeptics. Think about any of the great inventors in history and you won&rsquo;t find a skeptic among them. My expedition through the YouTube passageways was led in part by the &nbsp;following bitcoin technology &ldquo;missionaries&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>World Bitcoin Network&nbsp;</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Subscribers: &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;7,500 s</p>
<p dir="ltr">Channel views: 190,000</p>
<p><span>James D&rsquo;Angelo hosts this informative show which gives an especially persuasive &lsquo;Bitcoin 101&rdquo; teaching guide. In his own unique style using a digital chalkboard he illustrates visuals to help illustrate complex ideas. He comes across like the big brother or eager little league coach you never had. The channel&rsquo;s biggest video views dealt with the subject of why Bitcoin is not in a bubble. This video alone has received over 45,000 views. It should be 450,000 views. In</span><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovzb"> this link</a><span> he explains brilliantly why the growth in bitcoin price should actually be considered normal.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>Stefan Molyneux (Freedom Radio)</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Subscribers: &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;130,000</p>
<p dir="ltr">Channel Views: &nbsp;25 million</p>
<p><span>Stefan holds the distinction of having the most subscribers and most hits for his channel of the YouTube channels profiled here. He purposely takes on controversial topics which make for compelling viewing. Bitcoin is a common thread on his channels and he appears to me to be one of the earliest proponents to speak of the subject as of June 2011. He presents a reasonable and calm demeanor and has included guests both pro and con regarding Bitcoin. &nbsp;He&rsquo;s put together a couple of dedicated</span><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovzc"> videos</a><span> on the subject that make a great reference point for beginners.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>Let&rsquo;s talk Bitcoin!</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Subscribers: &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;3,200</p>
<p dir="ltr">Channel Views: &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;103,000</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;The show is in a podcast format and was originally hosted by Adam Levine, Andreas M. Antonopoulos and Stephanie Murphy. I discovered it last summer and found it reminded me of the NPR (National Public Radio) with its low key segments and slow jazz intros. It started out with the three main hosts mentioned above. Of the three, Andreas appears to me as the most passionate, energized, and engaging in my own opinion. Much of his forward thinking predictions and explanations brought clarity and focus to my understanding. He&rsquo;s now a sought after public speaker who does a fine job representing the bitcoin community ideals.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>The Bitcoin Channel</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Subscribers: &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;12,000</p>
<p dir="ltr">Views: &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;397,000</p>
<p><span>This channel has been around for a few years as well beginning in June 2011. &nbsp;The channel specializes charting the Bitcoin price with an effort to make short term predictions using formulas common to that specialty. The narrator&rsquo;s commentary is the interesting portion to me. If charting is your thing, you might find it interesting, but for me &ndash; I&rsquo;m more interested in the back story and theory added to give more meaning to price movements. One particularly interesting episode was from June 19, 2011 captured the &ldquo;flash crash&rdquo; of Bitcoin from $30 to almost zero in real-time as the Mt.Gox exchange was hacked. This event had a longer term effect of causing many people to lose faith in the currency and brought about many greatly exaggerated reports of bitcoin&rsquo;s death. &nbsp;It turned out to be an important moment of bitcoin history was captured while it was</span><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovzd"> happening.</a><span> It&rsquo;s important to see that at the time it was happening it was scary and confusing to those invested in the new technology. Put in perspective, it&rsquo;s fascinating.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">These channels of course are not alone on YouTube. In this short article it would be impossible to name them all. My journey led me to other helpful beacons of knowledge and discovery. I did, however, find myself returning to these sources repeatedly and eventually subscribed to their channels. To put things in perspective, others around the world are only now hearing about Bitcoin for the first time or only now reading or hearing something that spiked their interest. To much of the world, their first source of knowledge will be to turn to YouTube for influence. Their path will likely lead them to the many of the same places and to the same channels I found. We do well to recognize these efforts and thank them for introducing the newly curious population just now experiencing their &ldquo;a-ha&rdquo; moment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ovz5">Bitcoin&rsquo;s YouTube Missionaries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Mark Rees</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MMM #4 – Explosive Poetry]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow03]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Paul Boyer</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 16:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[TigerDirect accepts Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow13]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>TigerDirect.com has announced that it has chosen to accept Bitcoin payments. When I see this news, I immediately think of the miners that are supporting lower difficulty cryptocoins or Scrypt based coins. Now they will be able to upgrade their gear with Bitcoins.&nbsp;This is also great news for those who build their own computers or buy electronics on a regular basis. Here&rsquo;s a snippet of their press release. After several months of reviewing the options for processing Bitcoin, TigerDirect has chosen&nbsp;BitPay&nbsp;to provide its customers the most reliable means of transacting Bitcoin payments on their website.&nbsp;&nbsp; TigerDirect will not only accept the digital currency as payment, but will also sell the computer components used to mine the currency as well. &nbsp;We&rsquo;ve [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow13">TigerDirect accepts Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow13"><img width="950" height="350" src="http://cur.lv/6ow14" alt="bitcoin"></a><p><a href="http://cur.lv/6ovy5">TigerDirect.com</a> has announced that it has chosen to accept Bitcoin payments. When I see this news, I immediately think of the miners that are supporting lower difficulty cryptocoins or Scrypt based coins. Now they will be able to upgrade their gear with Bitcoins.&nbsp;This is also great news for those who build their own computers or buy electronics on a regular basis. Here&rsquo;s a snippet of their <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow15">press release</a>.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em>After several months of reviewing the options for processing Bitcoin, TigerDirect has chosen&nbsp;<a href="http://cur.lv/63iha" target="_blank">BitPay</a>&nbsp;to provide its customers the most reliable means of transacting Bitcoin payments on their website.&nbsp;&nbsp; </em></p>
<p><em>TigerDirect will not only accept the digital currency as payment, but will also sell the computer components used to mine the currency as well. &nbsp;We&rsquo;ve partnered with AMD to build the largest assortment of mining graphic cards from Sapphire, MSI, VisionTek, Diamond and XFX in the industry.</em></p>
<p><em> Customers will be able to utilize Bitcoin as payment on both the desktop and mobile websites.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>You really get a sense of enthusiasm when you visit TigerDirect.com and see their background displaying Bitcoins showering down from the sky. Clicking the &ldquo;learn more&rdquo; button takes you to an informative page about Bitcoin, the standard &ldquo;What is Bitcoin&rdquo; video, and in the url you see they&rsquo;ve labeled this campaign <em>Bitcoin Takeover</em>.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow16"><img alt="takeover" src="http://cur.lv/6ow17" width="620" height="17"></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>In any case, TigerDirect.com, welcome to the Bitcoin community.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow13">TigerDirect accepts Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ruben Alexander</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 12:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage - Software Freedom Day EU]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow1k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Software Freedom Day is a worldwide celebration and promotion of free software, open source software and related technologies]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Highlight of the Week: North American Bitcoin Conference!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow1u]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>On Friday through Sunday of this week, many Bitcoiners will gather in Miami, Florida for the North American Bitcoin Conference. Following the successful organization of the European Bitcoin Conference in Amsterdam this Fall, conference organizer, Moe Levin, concentrated his efforts on a winter international Bitcoin conference in the heart of Miami Beach, FL. With attendees and speakers from around the world, once again, the global message of Bitcoin is clearly demonstrated in this premier conference and setting. It is NOT too late to sign up. You can even purchase your conference pass with bitcoin here. On Friday evening, to kick off the conference, all attendees are welcome to a pre-conference reception at the iconic Clevelander Hotel to network and get [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow1u">Highlight of the Week: North American Bitcoin Conference!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow1u"><img width="978" height="552" src="http://cur.lv/6ow1v" alt="North American Bitcoin Conference"></a><p dir="ltr">On Friday through Sunday of this week, many Bitcoiners will gather in Miami, Florida for the North American Bitcoin Conference. Following the successful organization of the European Bitcoin Conference in Amsterdam this Fall, conference organizer, Moe Levin, concentrated his efforts on a winter international Bitcoin conference in the heart of Miami Beach, FL. With attendees and speakers from around the world, once again, the global message of Bitcoin is clearly demonstrated in this premier conference and setting. It is NOT too late to sign up. You can even purchase your conference pass with bitcoin<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow1w"> here.</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">On Friday evening, to kick off the conference, all attendees are welcome to a pre-conference reception at the iconic Clevelander Hotel to network and get ready for two. Additionally, the Clevelander Hotel recently signed up as a BitPay Merchant to accept payment in BitPay. From planes, to cars, to now hotels, one can travel fairly easily with Bitcoin. As the price of Bitcoin goes up more and more are looking to utilize this unique currency for daily expenses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Starting on Saturday, the conference will be broken into two tracks. On Saturday the conference will feature a free workshop for merchants to learn about accepting bitcoin. Leaders in the industry such as BitPay, New West Technologies and 3dcart will be demonstrating how one can easily incorporate bitcoin into their businesses. Alongside the Bitcoin merchant workshops, individuals can attend sessions featuring speakers including Ken Metral of Coingig, Chris Odom, Venture Capitalists, Jeffrey Tucker, Tony Gallippi, and a VC Panel and Startups Panel. The evening will conclude with another party at the Clevelander hosted by Triple Zero Media.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the highlights of Sunday&rsquo;s lineup include presentations from investors, a regulations panel, a Latin American panel and even a Mystery Speaker! The North American Bitcoin Conference will serve as the kickoff conference for 2014 and hopefully as a catalyst to further increase the size of the Bitcoin community in the US and abroad.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Remember, it is still not too late to sign up! Do not miss out and sign up <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow1w">here.</a> Also, feel free to stop by the Bitcoin Magazine table while you are at the conference.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow1u">Highlight of the Week: North American Bitcoin Conference!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Elizabeth Ploshay</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 03:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Junior Achievement of New York to Accept Bitcoin Donations]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow1x]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Just today, the Junior Achievement of New York began accepting donations in Bitcoin. Bitcoin is by far the most expedient way to accept donations and has proven to be a tool to empower individuals around the world. Junior Achievement of New York (JA New York) serves as a non-profit organization to empower students in grades K-12 by connecting students with volunteers. Volunteers then work with students in afterschool programs, workplace experiences, in the classroom and also help students develop academic, life and career plans. Jacqueline Dolly, Senior Director of Marketing and Communications of Junior Achievement New York stated, &ldquo;We are asking the Bitcoin community to support our fundraising efforts. We are the ONLY Junior Achievement affiliate in the country &ndash; [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow1x">Junior Achievement of New York to Accept Bitcoin Donations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow1x"><img width="850" height="315" src="http://cur.lv/6ow1y" alt="301812_172039246257568_955425759_n"></a><p dir="ltr">Just today, the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow1z">Junior Achievement of New York</a> began accepting donations in Bitcoin. Bitcoin is by far the most expedient way to accept donations and has proven to be a tool to empower individuals around the world. Junior Achievement of New York (JA New York) serves as a non-profit organization to empower students in grades K-12 by connecting students with volunteers. Volunteers then work with students in afterschool programs, workplace experiences, in the classroom and also help students develop academic, life and career plans.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Jacqueline Dolly, Senior Director of Marketing and Communications of Junior Achievement New York stated, &ldquo;We are asking the Bitcoin community to support our fundraising efforts. We are the ONLY Junior Achievement affiliate in the country &ndash; and perhaps the world &ndash; that has diversified its donor cultivation to include members of the new Bitcoin economy. As part of the world&rsquo;s largest and oldest economic K-12 education organization, we believe our success will have a huge ripple effect in the philanthropy community.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Junior Achievement of New York Issued the following release:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>NEWS RELEASE</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>For Immediate Release</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>January 22, 2014</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><strong>JUNIOR ACHIEVEMENT OF NEW YORK ACCEPTS BITCOIN DONATIONS</strong></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>[NEW YORK: NY] &ndash; Today, the NYC economic education charity, Junior Achievement of New York, announced it is now accepting Bitcoin donations. JA New York believes expanding its giving options to include Bitcoin acknowledges the changes and innovations shaping an emerging new economy. It also helps to keep Junior Achievement at the forefront of the shifting financial environment of the global economy.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Joseph Peri, president of Junior Achievement of New York said, &ldquo;By accepting Bitcoin, we are talking in the language of the 21st century global economy. We are also connecting the students we serve to professional role models and career opportunities in the digital economy. We welcome the Bitcoin community to invest in our mission to inspire and prepare young people to succeed in a global economy.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>As of today, JA New York&rsquo;s <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow20">website is ready to accept Bitcoin donations</a>. We will automatically convert any Bitcoin donations received into U.S. currency. JA New York joins a handful of NY-based charities, like the Foundation for Economic Education, that accept Bitcoin donations.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>On January 27, 7:00 PM-8:00 PM, JA New York will host a live Facebook Chat and Q&amp;A with Peter Vessenes, Chairman of the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow21">Bitcoin Foundation</a>. The live Bitcoin chat will focus on the emergence of digital currencies and their growing influence on the way we do business and live our lives in the 21st Century. To participate in Junior Achievement of New York&rsquo;s Bitcoin conversation, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow22">click here to RSVP.</a> (<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow22">http://cur.lv/6ow22</a>) and Like the JA New York community page (<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow23">http://cur.lv/6ow23</a>) #BitcoinConvo.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>###</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>About Junior Achievement of New York</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Junior Achievement of New York (JA New York) is the local affiliate of Junior Achievement USA&reg; (JA), the world&rsquo;s largest organization dedicated to giving young people the knowledge and skills they need to own their economic success, plan for their future, and make smart academic and economic choices. Our volunteer-delivered, K-12th grade programs foster college and career-readiness, entrepreneurship and financial literacy skills, and uses experiential learning to inspire students to dream big and reach their potential. With the help of more than 5,000 business and community volunteers, more than 67,000 NYC and Long Island students develop the skills they need to experience the realities and opportunities of work and entrepreneurship in the 21st-century global marketplace. Visit <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow24">www.jany.org</a> to share our story of impact and inspiration.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Jacqueline Dolly</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Senior Director, Marketing and Communications</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Junior Achievement of New York</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 205</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>New York, NY 10170</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Contact: 212-907-0046 I jdolly@jany.org I <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow24">www.jany.org</a></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Twitter:@JANewYork</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Facebook: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow25">http://cur.lv/6ow25</a></em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>Junior Achievement:Empowering young people to own their economic success</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow1x">Junior Achievement of New York to Accept Bitcoin Donations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Elizabeth Ploshay</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[HAK5 Episode Covers Bitmessage]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow27]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow28"> laxisusous </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow29">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow27">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 23:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How is RonPaulCoin different from Bitcoin/Litecoin?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow2x]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Is RonPaulCoin a clone of Bitcoin/Litecoin or are there differences beyond the specifications such as coin limit and difficulty algorithm?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Brock Hensley - FKA dirt</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 16:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin in Africa – On The Ground – Resources Program]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow31]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s not that Bitcoin has a bad image in Africa. It has no image at all. In that way it is a clean slate. The potential of Bitcoin in Africa is often cited. But the issues to overcome are real and routinely glossed over. The first step is clearly good PR. A solid image will form the groundwork. It&rsquo;s only by supporting local organisations and fostering good causes that Bitcoin will reach its full potential in Africa. There are no preconceptions about Bitcoin. When people see the technology making a positive change they will embrace it. ice3x.com is one of only two operational exchanges on the African continent. Intimately acquainted with the intricacies of doing business locally, we made a [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow31">Bitcoin in Africa &ndash; On The Ground &ndash; Resources Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow31"><img width="675" height="603" src="http://cur.lv/6ow32" alt="africa1"></a><p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s not that Bitcoin has a bad image in Africa. It has no image at all. In that way it is a clean slate.</p>
<p>The potential of Bitcoin in Africa is often cited. But the issues to overcome are real and routinely glossed over. The first step is clearly good PR. A solid image will form the groundwork.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s only by supporting local organisations and fostering good causes that Bitcoin will reach its full potential in Africa. There are no preconceptions about Bitcoin. When people see the technology making a positive change they will embrace it.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow33">ice3x.com</a> is one of only two operational exchanges on the African continent. Intimately acquainted with the intricacies of doing business locally, we made a choice to actively grow the community: the initiative &ldquo;Resources&rdquo; is operational.</p>
<p>African community organisations, doing good work but struggling to survive, come to us. They are vaguely familiar with Bitcoin. They are then introduced to the potential of the technology for their operations. They become intimate with Bitcoin and its promise.</p>
<p>ice3x.com is an exchange. Here it acts simply as a facilitator: a platform. It is the right approach &ndash; Corporate Philanthropy.</p>
<p>Organisations are given a wallet, zero fee account and a blogging voice to inform the world of their activities, collecting donations directly. They have complete control of their accounts and direct access to global funding, at no cost: a world of possibility presents itself. It is magic.</p>
<p>Mother of four and &ldquo;animal warrior&rdquo; Suzette Kotze is a local animal inspector and SPCA head. Aware of our exchange we received this email and we were moved:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Today I want to ask you on my knees, beg you actually&hellip;we are in urgent need of funds, otherwise we might close down, PLEASE !!!! What will happen to our animals if we are not here anymore&hellip;I am the only hope our animals have.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Kotze&rsquo;s SPCA is the first local community group to sign-up. There are five more in progress, to be verified.</p>
<p>In Kotze&rsquo;s small town there are at least twenty-one extreme animal abuse cases each month. The images received with her plea were truly horrific. We were compelled to act.</p>
<p>ice3x.com goes to great lengths to check the credibility of each applicant. Accountants are employed to conduct vigorous checks, which ensure the integrity of the program. Supporting not-for-profit documentation is a must.</p>
<p>Transparency is key. Total donations are reported regularly.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;ice3x.com is proud to support SPCA in this first program. This is a niche offering. But it represents a real opportunity to showcase the potential of Bitcoin to do good in Africa.</p>
<p>Suzette is new to Bitcoin. She is genuinely excited by the opportunity to take donations directly from all over the world at zero cost. By adapting her outlook to the digital age ice3x.com is helping her increase her reach.</p>
<p>These are the seeds in the fertile soil from which one thousand flowers will bloom.</p>
<p>The SPCA&rsquo;s blog spot is here: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow34">http://cur.lv/6ow34</a></p>
<p>Your support is most appreciated.</p>
<p><em>(Tristan Winters is an active member of the ice3x.com exchange team, proudly offering a quality exchange service in Africa and platform for corporate philanthropy).</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow31">Bitcoin in Africa &ndash; On The Ground &ndash; Resources Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Tristan Winters</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 14:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to run Bitmessage in Passive operating mode?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow35]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><ol><li><p>How to run Bitmessage in Passive operating mode?</p></li> <li><p>And how much is the possibility in real life/practically, that a Receiver's IP can be revealed to an attacker if passive operating mode is not used?</p></li> </ol><p>Read about Passive operating mode in 7th the paragraph: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow36">http://cur.lv/6ow36</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow37">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow35">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 12:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Taxation Vexation]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3a]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this week, Bitcoinx reviewed some of the decisions shaping Bitcoin regulation around the world.&nbsp; While there has been no movement regarding classification of the crypto-currency on the part of the IRS, their silence means more to Bitcoin users than just frustration. Though there are a growing number of businesses and high-profile websites accepting the [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3a">Bitcoin Taxation Vexation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this week, Bitcoinx reviewed some of the decisions shaping <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">Bitcoin regulation</a> around the world.&nbsp; While there has been no movement regarding classification of the crypto-currency on the part of the IRS, their silence means more to Bitcoin users than just frustration.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3c"><img alt="IRS needs clear tax rules on Bitcoiin" src="http://cur.lv/6ow3c" width="377" height="284"></a><p>IRS needs clear tax rules on Bitcoin. Image via Michael Carney/pondodaily</p></div>
<p>Though there are a growing number of <a href="http://cur.lv/68b4a">businesses</a> and high-profile websites accepting the virtual currency, the lack of direction on the part of the IRS may be affecting Bitcoin (and its users) on two fronts: investment and evasion.</p>
<p>Richard Asquith, Head of Tax for international expansion and investment firm, TMX Group, noted that if the <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">new rules</a> go through in the UK, the regulation could be highly beneficial for Bitcoin &ndash; in the UK.&nbsp; &ldquo;If the UK tax re-categorisation goes ahead, it will stabilize the domestic Bitcoin exchange market which had been threatening to move out,&rdquo; he said in an interview with <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3z">Forbes</a>. Asquith went on to add that &ldquo;it would also probably start attracting European and even global trade to migrate to the UK as it will be one of the first countries to have a well thought through tax regime.&rdquo;</p>
<p>While any stabilization in the market is likely to help Bitcoin in the long run, the absence of clear rules may be drawing potential investment away from the uncertainty in domestic markets.</p>
<p>The lack of clarity on the part of the government has others in the U.S. concerned with the issue of tax compliance.</p>
<p>In an annual <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3d">report</a> to Congress, National Taxpayer Advocate, Nina Olsen made it clear that &ldquo;It is the government&rsquo;s responsibility to inform the public about the rules they are required to follow.&rdquo;&nbsp; Olsen, who leads the independent Taxpayer Advocate Service office within the IRS, added that &ldquo;the lack of clear answers to basic questions such as when and how taxpayers should report gains and losses on digital currency transactions probably encourages tax avoidance.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Whether they ultimately decide to treat Bitcoin as a capital asset or a fiat currency for tax purposes, one thing is clear, the IRS needs to make a decision &ndash; and the sooner the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3a">Bitcoin Taxation Vexation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 10:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Heatmap 2014-01-21, Bitmessage user IP addresses]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3l]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3m"> dokumentamarble </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3n">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3l">[16 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E77 – The Adam Back Interview]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E77 &ndash; The Adam Back Interview Adam Back&nbsp;is a British Cryptographer and crypto-hacker. He&rsquo;s the inventor of Hashcash, the proof of work system used by Bitcoin and after we were initially introduced by a mutual acquaintance Charles Hoskinson, I met him [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 23:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[My Overstock.com First Day Buying Experience]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Overstock.com allows bitcoin purchases. It&rsquo;s music to my Barbecue. An AntiClimactic Ending to a New Beginning &ndash; And Why That&rsquo;s a Good Thing. I bought stuff from Overstock.com using bitcoin on the first and opening day of this new currency option. And boy, it felt good. I did something in celebration of the event that I don&rsquo;t normally do because it seems so geeky&hellip; I chose the option to share it with my personal friends on Facebook. Ok, I geeked out for a moment. What was my overall reaction? Well, it seemed so&hellip;.normal. I read the headlines all over financial news networks. I saw pieces of interviews with Overstock&rsquo;s CEO Patrick M. Byrne. When I went to their website I [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3p">My Overstock.com First Day Buying Experience</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3p"><img width="506" height="338" src="http://cur.lv/6ow3q" alt="Overstock.com First Purchase"></a><p><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3p" title="click to read"><img src="http://cur.lv/6ow3r" width="506" height="338" alt="Overstock.com allows bitcoin purchases. Music to my Barbecue"></a></p>
<p>Overstock.com allows bitcoin purchases. It&rsquo;s music to my Barbecue.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3r"><img alt="bbqsymphony" src="http://cur.lv/6ow3r" width="506" height="338"></a></p>
<p>An AntiClimactic Ending to a New Beginning &ndash; And Why That&rsquo;s a Good Thing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I bought stuff from Overstock.com using bitcoin on the first and opening day of this new currency option. And boy, it felt good. I did something in celebration of the event that I don&rsquo;t normally do because it seems so geeky&hellip; I chose the option to share it with my personal friends on Facebook. Ok, I geeked out for a moment. What was my overall reaction? Well, it seemed so&hellip;.normal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I read the headlines all over financial news networks. I saw pieces of interviews with Overstock&rsquo;s CEO Patrick M. Byrne. When I went to their website I expected a huge banner across the front page declaring something about the Big News! I expected on-screen balloons and digital confetti being blown across my monitor. Yet, I was met with patio furniture and bedding links for purchase; cue the crickets. It wasn&rsquo;t any different than the last time I had shopped at Overstock. I wanted to make a specific effort to shop at Overstock and buy something I truly needed. I wanted to do my part to &ldquo;thank&rdquo; the company for showing true initiative and the American Spirit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It didn&rsquo;t take long to think of something I needed. My wife bought me a smoker barbeque device for Christmas and I experienced my first effort being a &ldquo;Smoker&rdquo;. After reading up on it to make sure I was doing it right &ndash; I found an essential ingredient to the experience (other than the type of wood chips you &ldquo;cook&rdquo; into the food), was a meat thermometer. So last week I bought a version of the thermometer that was suggested in the on-line article&hellip; let&rsquo;s just say that the smoker, thermometer and I had a little &ldquo;misunderstanding&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I plunged the little digital unit into my intended dinner and wondered how the scientific geniuses at the thermometer company were able to make plastic electronics with a battery inside so heat resistant that it could withstand the heat of a barbeque smoker. Half way through my planned two hour smokefest, it was time to check the temperature of the meat. I learned an important cooking lesson and the limits of plastic technology. I pulled what was left of my digital thermometer out of my pork roast and watched it stretch like melted cheese. The wires came dangling out of the melted digital head and I knew at once I had overestimated the thermometer geniuses&rsquo; abilities. The apple-wood smoked roast was wonderful, but if you concentrated just right &ndash; you could detect the faint flavor of burnt plastic.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So this brings me to my Overstock experience. It was time for a new thermometer before I attempted a new siege inside the smoker the following weekend involving salmon. I searched &nbsp;the Overstock website and found immediately my new thermometer for my upcoming battle plan I like to call: &ldquo;heat meat and retreat&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">What struck me was that there was no mention of bitcoin anywhere. The prices were all in dollars which was a little bit of a letdown. Not only was there no greeting welcoming bitcoiners to the Overstock.com world of every-day shopping, but when I added an item to my digital shopping cart it simply plinked the dollar amount onto my tab just like it did a few weeks back on the site.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the checkout page I saw the section for &ldquo;billing information&rdquo; and thought triumphantly &ldquo;Ha! You won&rsquo;t need billing information &ndash; I&rsquo;m paying in digital cash today! There&rsquo;s no more need to give personal information.&rdquo; Then realized that&hellip;um&hellip; they were going to need to know what address to send it to. Okay, I can be happy I at least didn&rsquo;t have to share my banking information.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total price with shipping and discounts added in displayed were all priced in dollars, and the payment type defaulted to credit card. The page showed the obligatory boxes for credit card number and expiration date. PayPal was also listed as an option but for how much longer? Then&hellip; the button I was waiting to see&hellip;&rdquo;Bitcoin Accepted Here&rdquo;.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I smiled.</p>
<p dir="ltr">I clicked it for the selection type and then clicked the big green &ldquo;Submit Order Now&rdquo; button. I found another surprise. Based on my email address, which was a requirement on the billing screen, it must have looked up my account on Coinbase. I saw the big familiar looking &ldquo;Confirm Payment&rdquo; that I&rsquo;ve seen when sending money using the Coinbase website previously. The total was still listed boldly in US dollars. But underneath it &ndash; in a much smaller print&ndash; almost as an afterthought, was the amount of BTC for my purchase. It included a small QR code next to it. It was kind of&hellip;.anticlimactic.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once clicked, a new screen appeared announcing that it was awaiting receipt of the amount of BTC required and the wallet ID appeared that must have been created for the transaction. &nbsp;There was one hiccup that required me to open a separate tab to the Coinbase website where I needed to be logged in. For some reason the Overstock.com website didn&rsquo;t redirect me to the site in the same way Ebay sends you to PayPal if you&rsquo;ve selected that payment option. &nbsp;I&rsquo;m sure little glitches like that get worked out soon enough.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So that was it. Normal. You almost wouldn&rsquo;t realize you are dealing in bitcoin at all &ndash; and I think that is how it should be for widespread adoption. People are comfortable looking and pricing everything in dollars. If they keep their Coinbase account with money, the underlying units don&rsquo;t really matter as everything gets translated into dollars anyway. As Coinbase already has the money available from you to disburse the transaction- it goes quickly -no waiting for the blockchain. It felt&hellip;natural &ndash; and that&rsquo;s a good thing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Follow-up:</p>
<p dir="ltr">My new digital thermometer arrived a few days later and was exactly the item I ordered: one 8 second digital thermometer with a unusually stubby poker end. I grabbed some raw chicken and tried to insert the thermometer but found it just wouldn&rsquo;t go in very well. I looked closer at the box for some direction and was surprise to see the directions included a diagram of a person putting this thermometer into their ear. &nbsp;So, I got my second chance to buy something from Overstock with bitcoin much sooner than I had planned. This time my search term included the word &ldquo;Meat&rdquo;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3p">My Overstock.com First Day Buying Experience</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65yjx">Bitcoin Magazine</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Mark Rees</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 22:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage: A Peer to Peer Message Authentication and ...]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3s]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage: A Peer&#8208;to&#8208;Peer Message Authentication and Delivery System Jonathan Warren jonathan@bitmessage.org www.Bitmessage.org]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage Wiki]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage is a P2P communications protocol used to send encrypted messages to another person or to many subscribers. It is decentralized and trustless, meaning that ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Goes Up For Sale On eBay]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3w]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Just as Her Majesty&rsquo;s Revenue and Customs authorities in the UK are updating their policy on Bitcoin, eBay and PayPal are looking to re-evaluate their own approach to virtual currencies. Last week, PayPal President David Marcus tweeted &ldquo;To clarify: we have no policies against using PayPal to sell Bitcoin mining rigs. We don&rsquo;t support any [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3w">Bitcoin Goes Up For Sale On eBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3x"><img alt="eBay adds Virtual Currency category" src="http://cur.lv/6ow3x" width="496" height="310"></a><p>eBay to add Virtual Currency category in Classified Ads format. Photo: AP</p></div>
<p>Just as <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">Her Majesty&rsquo;s Revenue and Customs</a> authorities in the UK are updating their policy on Bitcoin, eBay and PayPal are looking to re-evaluate their own approach to virtual currencies.</p>
<p>Last week, PayPal President David Marcus <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3y">tweeted</a> &ldquo;To clarify: we have no policies against using PayPal to sell Bitcoin mining rigs. We don&rsquo;t support any currency txn whether fiat or BTC&hellip; for a host of regulatory issues. But we treat BTC and any FX txn the same way. We&rsquo;re believers in BTC though.</p>
<p>Days after Marcus&rsquo; comments hit Twitter feeds, eBay UK sent an <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow3z">email</a> to one of its merchants outlining a plan to update their policy on virtual currencies, including Bitcoin.&nbsp; While eBay UK insisted that virtual currencies &ldquo;cannot be listed in Auctions or Buy-It-Now formats,&rdquo; they also made it clear that &ldquo;eBay is opening a Virtual Currency category to allow the sale of virtual currency in Classified Ads format.&rdquo;&nbsp; The statement went on to &ldquo;request that you do not list these items until that date,&rdquo; warning that breaching the current policy could put users&rsquo; accounts statuses in jeopardy.&nbsp; The email further advised that in order &ldquo;to avoid any inconvenience in future, we&rsquo;d appreciate it if you go through our help pages or contact us before listing any such items.&rdquo;</p>
<p>eBay UK spokesman Steve Heywood further explained the policy updates, in an email to <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow40">CNET</a>, saying &ldquo;The updated policy clarifies that listings for Bitcoin and other similar virtual currencies must be listed in the Virtual Currency Category in the Classified Ad format. This applies to both the US (effective immediately) and the UK (effective 10 February).&rdquo;</p>
<p>Though Marcus is himself a supporter (and private owner) of bitcoins, and eBay has opened up more options for Bitcoin, PayPal is not yet ready to allow payment with the virtual currency.&nbsp; In an <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow41">interview</a> with Stephen Shankland, Marcus said they (PayPal) will consider it, &ldquo;[when] the regulatory framework is clearer, and the volatility comes down.&rdquo;</p>
<p>It is currently unclear whether eBay&rsquo;s new Bitcoin-friendly policy will be implemented in countries outside the US and the UK.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3w">Bitcoin Goes Up For Sale On eBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow4f]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage is a decentralized, encrypted, peer-to-peer, trustless communications protocol that can be used by one person to send encrypted messages to another person ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b0c Capital Asset or Currency?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow3b]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Now that we&rsquo;ve just about finished arguing whether Bitcoin is a legitimate payment form or not, we&rsquo;re faced with a whole new set of questions regarding the crypto-currency.&nbsp; One of the most prevalent, confusing, and contested topics is how Bitcoin can and will be taxed.&nbsp; In short, is Bitcoin a currency or a capital asset? [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">http://cur.lv/68b0c Capital Asset or Currency?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now that we&rsquo;ve just about finished arguing whether Bitcoin is a legitimate payment form or not, we&rsquo;re faced with a whole new set of questions regarding the crypto-currency.&nbsp; One of the most prevalent, confusing, and contested topics is how Bitcoin can and will be taxed.&nbsp; In short, is Bitcoin a currency or a capital asset?</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4k"><img alt="Bitcoin, currency or commodity?" src="http://cur.lv/6ow4k" width="407" height="311"></a><p>Will Bitcoin be taxed as a currency or a capital asset? Image: Shutterstock via venturebeat.com</p></div>
<p>While the Internal Revenue Service remains noticeably silent, other countries have been quicker to the mark, adding to the speculation and frustration of investors in the U.S.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s a rundown of what other countries are doing, and why the classification matters.</p>
<p>Last year, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4l">Germany</a> took a stand and ruled that bitcoins fall into the category of personal money, meaning that &ldquo;purchases are subject to sales tax&rdquo; and users will be required to pay capital gains.</p>
<p>Slovenia says Bitcoin is neither a monetary asset, nor a financial instrument, but that taxation will be reviewed on an individual basis (to determine whether income tax applies).</p>
<p>Singapore, where capital gains are not taxed, recognizes Bitcoin as a product, and will apply the goods and services tax.</p>
<p>In the past week, <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4m">Finland</a> decided that Bitcoin must be a commodity, after finding that it did not fit legal definitions of a currency or an electronic payment form.</p>
<p>Her Majesty&rsquo;s Revenue and Customs (HMRC), the tax authorities in the UK, are right now looking to <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3z">change</a> the classification of virtual currencies from a tradable voucher to a private currency.&nbsp; Though it is not yet official, handling Bitcoin as though it is private money means a value added tax would apply to commissions charged on exchanges, while still making it subject to capital gains taxes.</p>
<p>Though speculators seem to think that the IRS will eventually lean toward a capital gains classification, an income tax ruling could have bigger implications.</p>
<p>If treated under <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow4n">capital gains</a> rules, the same that are used against stocks or commodities, taxes up to 24% may apply, depending on the tax bracket.&nbsp; If the IRS decides that Bitcoin falls into the category of currency, gains would be taxed like income and the rate could go as high as 43.4%.&nbsp; The government&rsquo;s final decision could mean a difference of more than 20% for taxpayers.</p>
<p>In the absence of any clear direction, Bitcoin users in the U.S. are left without much more course of action than to just watch and wait.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6ow3b">http://cur.lv/68b0c Capital Asset or Currency?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 19:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage Free Download - Softpedia]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow4p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Softpedia guarantees that Bitmessage 0.4.0 Beta is 100% FREE, which means it does not contain any form of malware, including spyware, viruses, trojans and backdoors.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[XIB New Digital Currency Will Launch Today On The Ripple Network]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65ykf"> Aburgboy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2d">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2c">[6 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BitMessage: A Model For A New Web 2.0? – Bitcoin Magazine]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ovxj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[BitMessage: A Model For A New Web 2.0? Over the past twenty years, the democratization of cryptographic technology has brought us the potential for an unprecedented ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #20 from FellowTraveler/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #20 from FellowTraveler/master

Various Android fixes</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #20 from FellowTraveler/master

Various Android fixes</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 06:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[MIRI (formerly the Singularity Institute) seems to accept Ripple as a donation method now]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2r">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2q">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Edge Conf 2: Payments]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv2t]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2u">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv2t">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 04:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to attach a File with Bitmessage client?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv32]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I know there is a base64 encode and decode method, but I am not finding any downloadable software client to encode and decode a file. Can you name any file encoder and decoder software to download?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv34">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv32">[31 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 21:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What are difference between the protocols used by "Bitmessage" and "Retroshare"?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv35]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><ol><li><p>What are the basic differences between the protocols used by "Bitmessage" and "Retroshare"?</p></li> <li><p>Can Bitmessage offer the features as like RetroShare does?</p></li> </ol></div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv33"> BitCity </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv36">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv35">[9 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 20:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[I want to send UDS to my Bitstamp account via the Ripple network.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv38]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>How do I go about doing that? Is that even possible?</p> <p>Edit: I mean USD</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv39"> ramblington </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv38">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv38">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 16:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Another Android fix (for the PID file.)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3b]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Another Android fix (for the PID file.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Another Android fix (for the PID file.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 10:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fixed Android problems from OTPath and OTSettings.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed Android problems from OTPath and OTSettings.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed Android problems from OTPath and OTSettings.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 10:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Home folder (android), StringToULong, new Swig.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Home folder (android), StringToULong, new Swig.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Home folder (android), StringToULong, new Swig.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 06:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ripple trade book down?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3e]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Anyone else having problems seeing orders on the in-client orderbook? Can't see numbers for any pair, just shows N/A. Figured it might just be an update or something but it's been going on since last night..</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9w"> AlistorMcCoy </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3e">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3e">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 05:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[what is cloud mining ?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining bitcoin with cloud computing
2
2
Share on twitter Share on facebook Share on google Share on email More Sharing Services 1</p>
<p>I was investigating about this topic, and if it's profitable..</p>
<p>links about it:</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3i">http://cur.lv/6kv3i</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3j">http://cur.lv/6kv3j</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3k">http://cur.lv/6kv3k</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3l">http://cur.lv/6kv3l</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3m">http://cur.lv/6kv3m</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3n">http://cur.lv/6kv3n</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3o">http://cur.lv/6kv3o</a></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3p">http://cur.lv/6kv3p</a></p>
<p>The conclusion is that Bitcoin Mining on Cloud isn't profitable, but that for 1 or 2 years ago, but with the new level of worth.. still not profitable? If not, how much have to worth a bitcoin to be profitable this method?</p>
<p>Considering that a higher value implies greater difficulty</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Saqib Khan</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 20:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Miracle]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Until today Let's Talk Bitcoin! has played host to various forms of analysis, thought and proposal but all of it very much non-fiction.   <p>We're very pleased to present our very first piece of fiction, courtesy of Martin Hursk about a situation that would have been received as fantasy a year ago, but now is the reality for many Bitcoin early adopters.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Write for Let's Talk Bitcoin!</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 18:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Doge Markets - Such power! Wow. Including transitive ("ripple" type) transactions]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3r]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3s"> pigeons1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3t">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3r">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 18:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Why we should all be using the Dividend Rippler gateaway.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3u]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>This is in my opinion the best way to get alt coins into your ripple wallet without having to sign into another ripple gateaway. The detailed explanation on how to get it set up is <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3v">here.</a> Reasons to use it: you can get all those little bitcoin drips into your ripple wallet and then trade them for XRP, or just hold them there. If you want to build your wallet and have LTC, BTC, NMC or TRC, you can send them to your ripple wallet and trade some of those coins there for XRP. Finally, if you want to send alt coins from ripple to your alt coin wallet, Dividend Rippler gives you an easy way out without conversion. Win-win in my view.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3w"> kwelstr </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3u">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3u">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 18:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[The UK will not tax virtual currencies but will tax commission fees. Will this effect Ripples/XRP?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv3x]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3y"> Cybercommie </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3z">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv3x">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 16:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can I subscribe to MLs/chans through the B2M Gateway ?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv40]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv41"> ICanHearYouTick </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv42">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv40">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 16:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Do multi-signature transactions make a 'bitcoin kickstarter' possible? And what state are the bitcoins in, in the meantime?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This isn't a question about kickstarter really, just a way for me to phrase my question about the crypto in terms that I can understand.</p>

<p>My understanding, based on this article.. <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzg" rel="nofollow">Stop Saying Bitcoin Transactions Aren&rsquo;t Reversible</a> is that multi-signature transactions would make something like a bitcoin KickStarter particularly easy.</p>

<p>That is the kickstarter-like bitcoin service would act as a third party to many contracts transferring btc to the second party? </p>

<p>Maybe this has already been done? Hmm <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzh" rel="nofollow">@coinstarter</a>.. Yay! Great to see but doesn't really answer my question about how the crypto works. </p>

<p>To make things easier I'll call the people that pledge to the campaign the 'first parties' and the recipients of the funds the 'second party'. Could multi-party signatures to ensure the second party only receives btc after the projects are funded? and at the same time be sure that the third party (eg coinstarter) technically <em>can't</em> abscond with the funds.</p>

<p>Also - and this is my real question - in such a case what state are the bitcoins in prior to the project being funded. That is, are they marked in the blockchain and thus impossible for first parties to 'double spend' btc they have pledged to a campaign or are they actually not in escrow so if a first party spends them on something else in the meantime (after pledging, before the project is funded) the transaction just fails?</p>

<p>Thanks so much in advance, hope this question makes sense, crypto wise.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>utunga</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 12:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Ciao]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv43]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Buonmgiorno, come stai?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv44"> travisjox </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv45">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv43">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 08:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[eBay Files Patent Application for Programmable Money]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv46]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/5xyoq">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv46">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 02:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Run your own Ripple Client in two minutes]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow51]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9u"> miracle2k </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6ow52">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow51">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 00:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E76 – Politics and Charity]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv47]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E76 &ndash; Politics and Charity Connie Gallippi is founder and executive director of the BitGive (bitgivefoundation.org/) foundation and the sister of Tony Gallippi &ndash; Recently Stephanie caught up with Connie to talk about her origins, women in Bitcoin, the potential for [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 21:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there a site where you can buy Bitcoins using Amazon Giftcard?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv48]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>There are certain problems buying Bitcoins using credit cards because the operations are reversible.</p>
<p>Deliver giftcard is reversible or works like cash?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 18:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Pirate’s Bitcoin Booty To Go On Sale]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv49]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Nearly 30,000 bitcoins seized in October of last year have been signed off on a forfeiture order, federal prosecutors from the Manhattan U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s office announced on Thursday. Currently valued around $25 million, the bitcoins were seized from Ross Ulbricht, who allegedly founded and operated hidden website Silk Road under the pseudonym Dread Pirate Roberts. [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6kv49">Pirate&rsquo;s Bitcoin Booty To Go On Sale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4a"><img alt="$25 million worth of seized Bitcoin to be auctioned." src="http://cur.lv/6kv4a" width="498" height="248"></a><p>Millions worth of bit coins seized in connection with illegal activities have been cleared for federal auction. Image: Andy Field, Jay Hathaway via The Daily Dot</p></div>
<p>Nearly 30,000 bitcoins seized in October of last year have been signed off on a forfeiture order, federal prosecutors from the Manhattan U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s office announced on Thursday.</p>
<p>Currently valued around $25 million, the bitcoins were seized from Ross Ulbricht, who allegedly founded and operated hidden website Silk Road under the pseudonym Dread Pirate Roberts.</p>
<p>Described by <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4b">prosecutors</a> as the most &ldquo;sophisticated and extensive criminal marketplace on the Internet,&rdquo; Silk Road facilitated anonymous users in brokering illegal deals in computer hacking, forgeries, drug trafficking, and even murder-for-hire.</p>
<p>In addition to the 30,000 bitcoins included in the forfeiture order signed by U.S. District Judge J. Paul Oetken on Wednesday, the FBI are now in possession of another 144,336 bitcoins seized in connection with the Silk Road <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4c">case</a>.&nbsp; At today&rsquo;s exchange rates, the government is holding approximately $148 million total in their wallet from the bust, the largest such action involving the virtual currency to date.</p>
<p>Though the 30,000 seized in the initial action has been cleared for sale, the additional 144, 336 will remain in the government&rsquo;s wallet for the time being.</p>
<p>It is unclear how the FBI plans to offload the bitcoins, as there is currently no legally certified Bitcoin exchange in the United States. &nbsp;Manhattan U.S. Attorney Office <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4d">spokesperson</a>, Jim Margolin, said the bitcoins will go on auction soon, but did not give a specific date.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/6kv49">Pirate&rsquo;s Bitcoin Booty To Go On Sale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 17:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Online Games Where Gold Farming Is Legal]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4e]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Are there any games that are gold farming friendly? Gold farming is where you collect ingame currency and sell it for real money, or Bitcoins. It's a criminal offence to do this on games like Runescape and World of Warcraft due to the fact that they legally own everything. So I'm looking for games that permits you to do real world trading.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 14:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcloud: A Decentralized Cloud Based on Proof of Bandwidth]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4f]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yow"> galapag0 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4g">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4f">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 13:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Suggestions on Mining Rig Specs?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The reason I want to get in to Bitcoin Mining is so I can get some Office Space, Game Engine Licenses and Game Design Software / Tools so that I can get in to game design. Based on the current Bitcoin Market Value, which is $840.10 (Which for me is &pound;514.64): The amount which I think I'd need for everything is 350BTC, which is $294,035.00 (Which for me is &pound;180,113.20).</p>
<p>In a few months time, I will be designing and purchasing my own Custom-Built PC and I'm looking for suggestions of Machine Specs I should get which might help me get my Bitcoin Goal by the end of this year or the start of next. I want a computer that will be very powerful (meaning insane specs), as I'm willing to spend up to $8,000 on it, (Currently $13,059.20). Also, I'm also looking for suggestions of the best (based on your personal opinion) Bitcoin Miner and Mining Pool to use.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>CTCB</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 10:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[An anti ripple rap 'song']]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4l">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4k">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 20:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Open Source Finance (San Francisco, CA)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4m]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4n">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6kv4m">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 18:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Scaling Cryptocurrency With Ripple]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[The idea of Blockchains as the distributed record-keepers of cryptographic tokens is a paradigm-shifting one that we're still trying to understand the implications of.    John Light has in fact thought about some of those implications, and in this piece connects the dots between Cryptocurrency and Ripple for a valuable look at what might be a better way to scale.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>John Light</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 15:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is the title and who is the author of this tale of science fiction?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>A spaceship breaks down and the pilot decided to land on a planet. To not affect the inhabitants, look for the "ocean side" and lands in a small remote island.
Land on the beach. Tries unsuccessfully to repair the spaceship. After verifying that the atmosphere is breathable, walks along the beach. Find an attractive woman lying on the sand and... </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[¿Cuál es el título y el autor de este cuento de ciencia ficción?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4q]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Una nave espacial se aver&iacute;a y su piloto decide aterrizar en un planeta. Para no afectar a los habitantes busca el "lado oce&aacute;nico" y aterriza en una peque&ntilde;a isla alejada de todo.
Aterriza cerca de la playa. Intenta infructuosamente reparar la nave. Al verificar que la atm&oacute;sfera es respirable, sale a caminar por la playa. Encuentra una atractiva mujer acostada en la arena y....</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ripple Network mentioned on Blacklist - The Good Samaritan]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjr7]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjr8"> sexystick </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6fjr9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjr7">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Mad Money Machine #3]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjsz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Paul Boyer</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 01:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Trade Bitcoins Through Your Social Graph... With A Little Bit Of Help From Your BitFriends - Forbes]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjt0]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6fjt1">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjt0">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 01:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Considering the increase in bitcoin value, is it time to decrease the minimum bitcoin amount for withdrawal?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjth]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Are users finding it hard to reach the 0.01 bitcoin limit?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Sarah and Yair</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage - SlideShare]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow59]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage:An Analysis Vikram Reddy Pareddy CSc 8222 Department of Computer Science, Georgia State University]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[bitcoins question]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjue]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>How many karma points I need to buy bitcoins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>barzeta</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[/r/ActualMoney]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjuf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6fjug">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjuf">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 22:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E75 – Legitimacy and Permission]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjuh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E75 &ndash; Legitimacy and Permission Rob Banagale is the founder and CEO of Gliph, an application that lets you securely communicate and until recently send or receive Bitcoins as easily as a text message, no address required. Apple&rsquo;s App store had [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Let's Talk Bitcoin!</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 21:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Easiest Miner]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjui]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>What is the easiest miner to install and run on my PC?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sigmaasset</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 20:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fix to whirlpool for android version.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjuk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fix to whirlpool for android version.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fix to whirlpool for android version.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 08:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Mention of Ripple on NBC TV]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjul]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6fjum">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjul">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 07:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[FSK's Guide to Reality: The Tally Stick Monetary System]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjun]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6fjuo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjun">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 03:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Online bill payment via Bitcoin -- which means via the ripple-bitcoin bridges you can pay bills with via Ripple in Canada!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjup]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6fjuq">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6fjup">[7 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 22:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How I can split a reward for two or more answers?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjv3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In a question that I've done, I believe it is best to split the reward, but I think "Rugatu" does not have this option.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 14:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage E-Mail Gateway]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow5c]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Your bitmessage address is so long and looks like nosense, that some E-Mail filters sort it out as spam. If it is a mail for a bitmessage recipient ...]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fixed bug in opentxs showpayments]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg6z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed bug in opentxs showpayments

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fixed bug in opentxs showpayments

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 07:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[1000 mBTC Contest Winner Announced!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yl9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[After ten days of listening and voting, we have a winner!  Check inside for details, all shows will receive a 70 mBTC bonus and the Bitcoins &amp; Gravy Show was awarded the Editor's Choice 250 mBTC prize.  
Stay tuned for more details on the new LTB Network coming in late Q1 of 2014!]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Adam B. Levine</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 17:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Help, bitmessage keeps sending me the same messages over and over.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg99]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Not sure how else to desrcibe the behavior. This is an amazing little piece of technology, but I keep getting the same messages over and over. For example I've gotten some messages 4 times over the past day. And they keep rolling in.</p> <p>Did I set something up wrong? Wtf is going on.</p> <p>(Ubuntu 13.10, installed via git)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9a"> v1- </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9b">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg99">[19 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 09:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Regular Releases? Last version was October 10, 2013]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>The forum has spam and there is a lack of posts here about continuing releases. I saw a commit 13 days ago in github, but is there a place which lists the roadmap to future releases?</p> <p>Following up that question, are there other implementations with regular development progressing? </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9e"> kaega </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9f">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9d">[8 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 05:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[There should be a way to solve this problem with the ripple payment system.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9g]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yn0"> bob_newhart </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9h">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9g">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 04:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Independent Ripple Help]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9i]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yju"> themusicgod1 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9j">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9i">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What will be the future money?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9k]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I think Bitcoins will take over on paper money and also real Gold will also play an important role in future. For me keeping Gold and Bitcoin is wise for long run.</p>
<p>What ar your thoughts on this?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>kkbhanot</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 19:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Similarityies between Frank Sinatra's "Fly me to the moon" and Michael Bubl&eacute;'s "Feeling good"?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9m]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Similarityies between Frank Sinatra's "Fly me to the moon" and Michael Bubl&eacute;'s "Feeling good"? </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>MumsigaKex</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 13:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What route were taken by the Roman armies?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>For example, if the troops departed from a town near the current Ferrara (44&deg; 49' 0" N 11&deg; 37' 0" E) and wanted to get to a town near current Nancy (48&deg; 40' 0" N 6&deg; 10' 0" E):</p>
<p>What routes were taking? How long it took?</p>
<p>Were these routes passable all year round?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 02:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[¿Qué ruta seguían los ejércitos del Imperio Romano?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9p]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Por ejemplo si las tropas part&iacute;an de una localidad cercana a la actual Ferrara (44&deg;49&prime;0&Prime;N 11&deg;37&prime;0&Prime;E) y quer&iacute;an llegar a una localidad cercana a la actual Nancy (48&deg;40&prime;0&Prime;N 6&deg;10&prime;0&Prime;E):</p>
<p>&iquest;Qu&eacute; rutas tomaban? &iquest;Cu&aacute;nto tiempo tardaban? </p>
<p>&iquest;Estas rutas eran transitables todo el a&ntilde;o?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 02:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Show off your ComputingForGood contribution using this badge]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cg9s]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I thought this would be a fun one, so as an experiment I built a WCG giveaway badge that you can see here:</p> <p><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9t">http://cur.lv/6cg9t</a></p> <p>It will show the number of XRP you received in the last giveaway round. As soon as you receive your new XRPs, it will immediately update. As a bonus, if you have not received a payout in the last 24 hours, it will turn grey, so you'll be able to see how the payouts are coming along.</p> <p>What this does is look at all payments being made by rNKXT1p7jpt5WxSRSzmUV6ZB6kY7jdqHmx. Currently, there are about 6000 addresses in the database (the last 6000 payouts made). If your badge shows '0 XRP', that means you're not in the database yet; but once you do receive your next payment, it will reflect that.</p> <p>It's all free and anonymous, so enjoy!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9u"> miracle2k </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9s">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cg9s">[3 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 22:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[E74 – New Ideas in Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgao]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Subscribe to Let&rsquo;s Talk Bitcoin! for free to automatically download new episodes. Shownotes for E74 &ndash; New Ideas in Bitcoin My contribution to the Inside Bitcoins event on December 10th 2013 was a panel called New Ideas in Bitcoin. &nbsp;I invited the gentlemen who together are behind some of my favorite innovative projects. Alex Bourget [&hellip;]]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Let's Talk Bitcoin!</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 20:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage - Organic Design]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow5f]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[Bitmessage is a peer-to-peer communications protocol based on the Bitcoin crypto-currency used to send encrypted messages to another person or to many subscribers.]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[RTS Games?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgb6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I would like to know if you guys have played any awesome RTS games that you just can't get enough of!
I have played : </p>
<p>AOE ( all the parts )</p>
<p>Rise Of Nations</p>
<p>Command and Conquer games.</p>
<p>[All at good settings and I wanted to play age of empires online but I came to know of it late, that is , it is shutting down In July.)</p>
<p>So would you guys recommend any similar games like these for my specs&gt;</p>
<p>Intel G41 Chipset, 2GB ram, 2.7 (x 2)GHz Processors . ( I know they are not fit to play any great games but games similar to the ones I mentioned would be fantastic! :) </p>
<p>Thanks &amp; Best regards,</p>
<p>Jibit</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Jibit</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Does anybody know what BitMessageErl is?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgbg]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I noticed someone connect to my server with this user agent. Is someone writing a client in Erlang maybe? Cool.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yol"> bpeel </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cgbh">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgbg">[comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Dynamic difficult of PoW]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgbl]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Since the PoW is needed to avoid DoS attacks, clients could accept messages without/with-low difficult if there is a "normal" rate of messages and require an "high" but feasable difficult when the rate of messages become not manageable</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yoa"> Inaltoasinistra </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/6cgbm">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/6cgbl">[10 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BOUNTY for translating the Bitmarket source from C# to C++ !! Tell me your price !]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68az2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>You should know, that BitMarket is a C# application and serves as proof of concept.</p> <p>I really hope, that somebody will take the effort and translates it to a more universal language like C++ </p> <p>What is your price tag ?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/68az3"> lordoftheflies1337 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/68az4">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/68az2">[7 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 01:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[News on Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgc8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I would like to be up to date so please answer here, with brief a description and link, to get rewarded <strong>100&micro;BTC</strong> for every news article (many in one answer please), thanks.</p>
<p>Btw, only articles that get published starting from today and preferably written in English or google-translated.</p>
<p>Include the date under every article's link.</p>
<p>Please avoid posting news from<br></p>
<p>thebitcoinnews.co.uk<br>
bitcoinviews.com<br>
futuresflash.com<br>
virtualmining.com<br>
freedomnewsroom.com<br>
xrptalk.org<br>
watchinga.com</p>
<p>as you will not get any reward in exchange, thank you</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>cscoxx</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 20:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin in the Real World]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b4a]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Even as Bitcoin is facing regulation challenges overseas, online retailers and service providers both here and abroad have continued to initiate Bitcoin payment options in order to make their businesses more inclusive and their transactions more immediate. Street vendors in London, bars in Berlin, flower shops in Santa Monica, real estate brokers in New York, [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4a">Bitcoin in the Real World</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even as Bitcoin is facing <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymu">regulation</a> challenges overseas, online retailers and service providers both here and abroad have continued to initiate Bitcoin payment options in order to make their businesses more inclusive and their transactions more immediate.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/68b4b"><img alt="More retailers accepting Bitcoin." src="http://cur.lv/68b4c" width="224" height="300"></a><p>An increasing number of retailers worldwide are now accepting Bitcoin. Image &amp; sign: Cryptocables</p></div>
<p>Street vendors in London, bars in Berlin, flower shops in Santa Monica, real estate brokers in New York, and even a university in Cypress join a growing list of businesses that are being drawn to the absence of transaction fees and the ability to process payments in under a minute by eschewing traditional money transfer providers and using Bitcoin instead.</p>
<p>Others, like internet gaming giant Zynga, <a href="http://cur.lv/68b4d">online megastore</a> Overstock.com, and popular blog hosting site WordPress, see value in the inherent universality of the virtual currency.&nbsp; (Bitcoin is neither created nor regulated by any central government and, as such, is not subject to an individual country&rsquo;s economic scales or inflation.)&nbsp; Andy Skelton, spokesperson for WordPress, issued a statement in November saying that the company recognizes the <a href="http://cur.lv/68b4e">restrictions</a> some people face due to the socio-politics of their geography.&nbsp; &ldquo;We don&rsquo;t think an individual blogger from Haiti, Ethiopia, or Kenya should have diminished access to the blogosphere because of payment issues they can&rsquo;t control,&rdquo; Skelton said on the website. &ldquo;Our goal is to enable people, not block them.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Far from being just an ideology or exercise in economics, Bitcoin is quickly proving to be a useful and legitimate tender for real-world goods and services.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4a">Bitcoin in the Real World</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 18:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Creative ways to earn Bitcoins]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgca]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Is there a webpage where you can offer your creativity, ingenuity, analytical or artistic gift to help solving problems for companies who are willing to pay in bitcoins? Is there a connection between industry or large companies asking for advices, problem solutions, and creative people who want to earn bitcoins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Ecostroj</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 14:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is the title of this movie?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgcb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Possibly 80's, from USA. A group of coworkers arrive by plane to a tropical island to receive a leadership course. Immediately upon arrival asked to sign a life insurance policy to start the course. A person refuses to sign, instructors indicate that if one person does not sign, then the course will not be performed. Nobody reads the insurance and all signed. The chief instructor informs them that what they just signed is a complete surrender of all their human rights and thereafter can do whatever they want with them. Nightmare Begins (psychological and physical torture) and the attempt to be rid of it.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 13:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Cuál es el título de esta película?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6cgcc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Posiblemente de los 80, estadounidense. Un grupo de compa&ntilde;eros de trabajo llegan en avi&oacute;n a una isla tropical a recibir un curso de liderazgo. Inmediatamente al llegar les piden que firmen un seguro de vida para iniciar el curso. Una persona se niega a firmar, los instructores indican que si una sola persona no firma, entonces el curso no se va a realizar, nadie lee el seguro y todos firman. La jefa de los instructores les informa que lo que acaban de firmar es una cesi&oacute;n completa de todos sus derechos y de ah&iacute; en adelante pueden hacer lo que quieran con ellos. Se inicia la pesadilla y el intento de librarse de ella. </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Multifolio</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 03:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitcoin from Wall Street to Washington]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68b4d]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Though Bitcoin has had no shortage of speculation (both positive and negative) in 2013, the sheer volume of press it has received speaks to the resilience of the virtual currency.&nbsp; With the start of the new year, now seems the perfect time to see where the highly debated tender has been &ndash; and where it&rsquo;s [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4d">Bitcoin from Wall Street to Washington</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://cur.lv/68baa"><img alt="Washington and Wall Street embrace Bitcoin" src="http://cur.lv/68bab" width="405" height="229"></a><p>Washington joins Wall Street in embracing Bitcoin. Image via Troy Kuhn.</p></div>
<p>Though Bitcoin has had no shortage of speculation (both positive and negative) in 2013, the sheer volume of press it has received speaks to the resilience of the virtual currency.&nbsp; With the start of the new year, now seems the perfect time to see where the highly debated tender has been &ndash; and where it&rsquo;s headed&mdash;amongst some of the nation&rsquo;s money makers and policy makers.</p>
<p>It may be no coincidence that the upturn in attention accompanies an increasing number of Wall Street firms not only interested in, but also investing in Bitcoin.&nbsp; Merrill Lynch released a report last month, prompting lead report strategist David Woo to share <a href="http://cur.lv/68bac">his view</a> that Bitcoin is a &ldquo;serious competitor&rdquo; in monetary transactions and &ldquo;as a medium of exchange, Bitcoin has clear potential for growth.&rdquo;&nbsp; The legitimacy of the currency was solidified further last week when a San Francisco based hedge fund posted a job opening for a Junior Bitcoin Execution Trader.&nbsp; At the same time, a number of other investment firms have admitted to creating Bitcoin departments within their companies.</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/65ynq">Wall Streeters</a> may have taken notice of the virtual currency&rsquo;s prospects some time ago, but new players are joining the game consistently, bringing different industries and bigger names to the table.&nbsp; In a December 2013 statement, Overstock.com CEO Patrick Byrne announced that the website will begin accepting payment in Bitcoin later this year, making it possible to use bitcoins to purchase, well, almost anything&mdash;and potentially setting precedent for other major retailers, who have been observing from the sidelines, thus far.&nbsp; Byrne made it clear that his was a business as well as a <a href="http://cur.lv/68bad">philosophical</a> decision, telling CNN&rsquo;s Ben Rooney that he believes &ldquo;the monetary base should not be something that a government can create with a stroke of a pen.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Byrne isn&rsquo;t the only one with a Libertarian love for the cyber currency.&nbsp; Even more recently, Congressman Steve Stockman has announced that he will accept Bitcoin donations to help fund his campaign for U.S. Senate.&nbsp; In an online video, Stockman stated that his <a href="http://cur.lv/68bae">support</a> for the deregulated monetary form stems from the desire for the &ldquo;freedom to choose what you do with your money, and freedom to keep your money without people influencing it,&rdquo; the Dallas Morning News reported.&nbsp; As the Federal Election Commission has yet to decide how to classify the donation, it is unclear at this time how the Bitcoin can be spent in terms of campaign financing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/68b4d">Bitcoin from Wall Street to Washington</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Suggestion: "Conversations" in the client.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ygs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Please let me know if this is something that is already being implemented, as I am new to Bitmessage...</p> <p>I would love to see a feature where I can "make a conversation" that the client would keep track of. I imagine it would work something like this:</p> <p>1) Go to "conversations" tab 2) Choose a recipient address from my address book 3) Choose a sending address from my identity list 4) Click "Start" (or something)</p> <p>Then the client would do the heavy lifting from there...</p> <p>5) The client would take any sent mail that matched the proper sender and receiver, and add it to the conversation. 6) The client would take any received mail that matched the proper sender and receiver, and add that to the conversation. 7) The messages are compiled in chronological order.</p> <p>The user interface could be similar to an instant messaging chat, where you just push "reply" after typing what you want to say.</p> <p>That is what I would love to see for Bitmessage.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65ygt"> AviatorBJP </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65ygu">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65ygs">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 05:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is bitcoin deflationary and inflationary at the same time?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzi]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Hello I was wondering as bitcoin is in public and media represented as deflationary currency if it really is so.</p>

<p>Deflation is on <a href="http://cur.lv/68b9k" rel="nofollow">wikipedia</a>:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>In economics, deflation is a decrease in the general price level of goods and services ...
  <strong>This allows one to buy more goods with the same amount of money over
  time.</strong></p>
</blockquote>

<p>Inflation on <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzj" rel="nofollow">wikipedia</a>:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Economists generally believe that high rates of inflation and hyperinflation are caused by &gt;an <strong>excessive growth of the money supply</strong>.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>At the moment there really is an excessive growth of bitcoin supply with every block reward gained until c. 2140 when all bitcoins are expected to be mined. So there will be only transaction fee as block rewards, which will be the end of growth of money supply. </p>

<p>So can we consider bitcoin as either inflationary and deflationary currency until 2140 because there are still new bitcoins generated until c. 2140 ?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Marek</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 16:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can I still get paid for monetizing my videos on YouTube even though I'm not connected to AdSense?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yjc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I've recently began to monetize my videos, but I noticed that my channel has to be connected to a AdSense account. Now, I was wondering; if I monetized my video before I create an AdSense account and people clicked the ads, would I get paid for those previous clicks after I've linked an AdSense account?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 13:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Using BTC addresses as BM chan names]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yjh]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Bitmessage noob here. I'm not sure whether this is commonly done already. Is there any problem with creating a chan using a BTC address as the chan name? This would give an anonymous customer a way of contacting you to discuss a potential or past transaction, which could be finalized when the customer sends btc to the chan name.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yji"> pa2013 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yjj">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yjh">[4 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BitMarket - A decentralized, confiscation proof, open market system]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yjq]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yjr"> AyrA_ch </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yjs">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yjq">[37 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 22:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #13 from randy-waterhouse/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4y]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #13 from randy-waterhouse/master

Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #13 from randy-waterhouse/master

Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>randy-waterhouse</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 02:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv4z]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Update debian/rules with new config build defaults.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author></author>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 02:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #15 from da2ce7/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv50]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #15 from da2ce7/master

Windows: update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #15 from da2ce7/master

Windows: update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[update 3rd-party project files]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv51]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>update 3rd-party project files</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 14:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Running a dedicated node.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ylb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>I have a spare VPS lying around and I was wondering if I could run Bitmessage as a dedicated service without the GUI, just command line, doing nothing but helping process messages.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65ylc"> darknyan </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yld">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65ylb">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 11:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Introducing Twister: a fully decentralized P2P microblogging platform leveraging both the Bitcoin and BitTorrent protocols.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ylx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yly"> c0ldfusi0nz </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65ylz">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65ylx">[10 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 23:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[India Uncertain About Bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ymp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>A number of Bitcoin exchanges in India, including the country&rsquo;s largest trading platform, BuySellBitco, have suspended operations this week. The halt comes in response to a statement issued by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) on Christmas Eve, warning consumers about the potential dangers associated with decentralized digital currencies.&nbsp; Ajit Prasad, the RBI&rsquo;s Assistant General [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymp">India Uncertain About Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A number of Bitcoin exchanges in India, including the country&rsquo;s largest trading platform, BuySellBitco, have suspended operations this week.</p>
<p>The halt comes in response to a <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymr">statement</a> issued by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) on Christmas Eve, warning consumers about the potential dangers associated with decentralized digital currencies.&nbsp; Ajit Prasad, the RBI&rsquo;s Assistant General Manager, cautioned &ldquo;the users, holders and traders of Virtual currencies (VCs), including Bitcoins, about the potential financial, operational, legal, customer protection and security related risks that they are exposing themselves to.&rdquo;</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/65yms"><img alt="Bitcoing Trading Suspended in India" src="http://cur.lv/65ymt" width="300" height="164"></a><p>India&rsquo;s largets Bitcoin exchanges temporarily suspend operations. &nbsp;Image: Eric Blattberg</p></div>
<p>The Reserve Bank of India&rsquo;s subsequent announcement that they are &ldquo;examining the issues associated with the usage, holding and trading of VCs under the extant legal and regulatory framework of the country,&rdquo; has left virtual currency traders fearing a government crack-down on &ldquo;unintentional breaches&rdquo; of anti-money laundering and financial terrorism laws.</p>
<p>Unlike the recent actions we&rsquo;ve seen in <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymu">China</a>, policy makers in India have stopped short of issuing any bans or directly prohibiting trading in bitcoins.</p>
<p>Still, the country&rsquo;s top exchanges have not taken the warning lightly.&nbsp; Reuters <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymv">reports</a> that INRBTC, another large trading platform in India, had no choice but to &ldquo;suspended its services indefinitely&rdquo; amidst concerns that both they and their customers are &ldquo;exposed [to] both legal and financial risks.&rdquo;</p>
<p>While India&rsquo;s growing interest in Bitcoin may have been temporarily stunted in the wake of the announcements, the price of the currency hasn&rsquo;t been so reactionary, trading at $795 at the time of publication.&nbsp; <a href="http://cur.lv/65ymw">BuySellBitco.in</a> made it clear in a notice on their homepage that the precautionary suspension of operations is &ldquo;being done to protect the interest of our customers and in no way is a reflection of Bitcoin&rsquo;s true potential or price.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymp">India Uncertain About Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 21:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #9 from mahyar/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv53]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #9 from mahyar/master

homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #9 from mahyar/master

homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #12 from FellowTraveler/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv54]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #12 from FellowTraveler/master

FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #12 from FellowTraveler/master

FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 02:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How does your account get credited when you send bitcoins(ex. Coinbase)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This question might have already been answered. If so, can someone send me the link to it.</p>

<p>Let's say I create a blockchain wallet. It gives me a bitcoin address to deposit coins. Once I send bitcoins to the address that is given how does the system know what account is associated with that bitcoin address.</p>

<p>I wanted to develop a site where you can deposit bitcoins into your account and I want to know how that is done. </p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user11419</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 01:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Litecoin and Dogecoin Blockchain size]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzl]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I am new to mining cryptocurrencies. I am planning to set up a wallet for both Litecoin and Dogecoin. I am just curious on asking what are the current total blockchain sizes of both coins? This is to prepare me to download them ahead of time.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>SageTheGreat</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 07:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!!]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yn8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!!
(So far tested on Mac only.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>FINALLY fixed the password-thread-timeout-crash!!
(So far tested on Mac only.)

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 01:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Small fix for chai5.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ynf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Small fix for chai5.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Small fix for chai5.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #11 from FellowTraveler/master]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv55]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #11 from FellowTraveler/master

Fixing crash bug in password threads.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #11 from FellowTraveler/master

Fixing crash bug in password threads.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 00:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fixing crash bug in password threads.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ynk]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Fixing crash bug in password threads.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Fixing crash bug in password threads.

Signed-off-by: FellowTraveler <f3llowtraveler></f3llowtraveler></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>FellowTraveler</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Any free sandbox survival games?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6fjvr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost like Minecraft, just with no price tag.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 07:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[China Deals Bitcoin Another Blow]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ymu]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of Bitcoin is still recovering this week after BTC China, the country&rsquo;s largest Bitcoin exchange, stopped accepting deposits in Chinese yuan. The drop in the currency piggybacked on the downward trend seen after the People&rsquo;s Bank of China issued a partial ban on the virtual currency on December 5, prohibiting financial institutions from [&hellip;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymu">China Deals Bitcoin Another Blow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Bitcoin is still recovering this week after BTC China, the country&rsquo;s largest Bitcoin exchange, stopped accepting deposits in Chinese yuan.</p>
<div><a href="http://cur.lv/65yno"><img alt="China's Bitcoin ban hits hard." src="http://cur.lv/65ynp" width="300" height="224"></a><p>China&rsquo;s Bitcoin ban hits hard.<br>Image: Flickr, zcopley</p></div>
<p>The drop in the currency piggybacked on the downward trend seen after the People&rsquo;s Bank of China issued a <a href="http://cur.lv/65ynq">partial ban</a> on the virtual currency on December 5, prohibiting financial institutions from dealing in bitcoins.</p>
<p>Though Bobby Lee, BTC China&rsquo;s co-founder, has made it clear that the decision to suspend deposits in yuan was forced when the People&rsquo;s Bank of China asked Chinese payment processors to cease trading with Bitcoin exchanges by the start of the new year, he does not see this as the end.</p>
<p>BTC China posted a statement that the yuan deposit feature had been temporarily stopped, but other transactions would continue uneffected.</p>
<p>The full text reads (<a href="http://cur.lv/65ynr">translated</a>):</p>
<p><i>Dear BTC China users: due to reasons we all understand, Bitcoin China (BTC China) had to temporarily stop the yuan deposit feature while bitcoin deposits, and bitcoins withdrawals to cash and RMB are still available on our home page. We will provide other ways to recharge as soon as possible. This is an inconvenience to you and we express deep regret at BTC China. 2013. 12. 18</i></p>
<p>As Danny Bradburry of <a href="http://cur.lv/65yns">CoinDesk</a> reports, BTC China is expecting to reinstate deposits in RMB in the future.&nbsp; Lee said he is &ldquo;working with another third party payment company to try and reinstate RMB pricing,&rdquo; and is hoping to make an announcement soon.</p>
<p>With this month&rsquo;s restrictions on financial institutions and the current ban on deposits in yuan, the People&rsquo;s Bank of China has made it increasingly difficult, if not virtually impossible, for individuals in the country to buy new bitcoins, putting a damper on Chinese enthusiasm for the currency.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymu">China Deals Bitcoin Another Blow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cur.lv/65ymq">Bitcoinx</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Bitgirl</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 19:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Rugatu video]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ynt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>We would like to create a video introduction for Rugatu so that new users understand how it works from the first moment. We liked <a href="http://cur.lv/65ynu">this video</a> as an example of what we want to achieve, so if you're good with this kind of cgi and editing please take a shot at our video.</p>
<p>Anything else you want to know, please ask.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>cscoxx</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 11:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[parsing bitcoin input and output addresses from scripts]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>can someone walk me through the process of combining script inputs and outputs to reveal the base58 encoded input and output addresses. take for example, <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzn" rel="nofollow">block 728</a>. this has two raw script inputs:</p>

<pre><code>493046022100e26d9ff76a07d68369e5782be3f8532d25ecc8add58ee256da6c550b52e8006b022100b4431f5a9a4dcb51cbdcaae935218c0ae4cfc8aa903fe4e5bac4c208290b7d5d01

and

493046022100a2ab7cdc5b67aca032899ea1b262f6e8181060f5a34ee667a82dac9c7b7db4c3022100911bc945c4b435df8227466433e56899fbb65833e4853683ecaa12ee840d16bf01
</code></pre>

<p>the first byte of each (49 hex = 73 dec) is the instruction to push 73 bytes onto the stack. <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzo" rel="nofollow">according to the wiki</a> each of these input scripts consists of a signature and a public key.</p>

<p>the raw output script is</p>

<pre><code>76a91412ab8dc588ca9d5787dde7eb29569da63c3a238c88ac
</code></pre>

<p>which translates to the instructions</p>

<pre><code>OP_DUP OP_HASH160 OP_PUSHDATA0(20 bytes) 12ab8dc588ca9d5787dde7eb29569da63c3a238c OP_EQUALVERIFY OP_CHECKSIG
</code></pre>

<p><strong>so given this information, how can i extract input addresses (as shown in blockexplorer.com)? is this even possible?</strong></p>

<pre><code>1Miuw7ifaTYY5qrzKYFcTDiojSFxRfAqwP and 18KrJNtPVu6LWRNPQReqF29iFm7vDhirMk
</code></pre>

<p>and output address</p>

<pre><code>12higDjoCCNXSA95xZMWUdPvXNmkAduhWv
</code></pre>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>mulllhausen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 03:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.  Verified to work from build -&gt; running on OSX 10.9]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv57]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.  Verified to work from build -&gt; running on OSX 10.9</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>homebrew scripts for open-transactions and its chaiscript dependency.  Verified to work from build -&gt; running on OSX 10.9</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>mahyar</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 22:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #7 from da2ce7/zlib_windows]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv58]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #7 from da2ce7/zlib_windows

Merged.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #7 from da2ce7/zlib_windows

Merged.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 13:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[fix basic linker error on windows]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv59]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>fix basic linker error on windows</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>fix basic linker error on windows</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[include zlib for windows]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6kv5a]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>include zlib for windows</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>include zlib for windows</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>da2ce7</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Are there alternatives to POW to prevent spam?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yo9]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>POW has a huge problem: or it's so difficul to solve that a phone can't send messages or it's so easy that a guy with some video-card can flood the net.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yoa"> Inaltoasinistra </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yob">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yo9">[28 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 19:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage crashing on OSX all the time. Could it be the same problem bitcoinQT and litecoinQT had on OS X? They both put a bounty out and someone found a fix.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yog]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>My bitmessage client on os x keeps hanging. spinning beach ball of death. I was wandering if its the same problem that was fixed here. <a href="http://cur.lv/65yoh">http://cur.lv/65yoh</a></p> <p>It just has the same symptoms. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yih"> anarcoin </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yoi">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yog">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[BitMessage mentioned in The New Yorker]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yok]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yol"> bpeel </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yom">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yok">[1 comment]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 15:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fund the official Bitmessage client using Bitcoin with Tip4Commit]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yov]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yow"> galapag0 </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yox">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yov">[2 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 19:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Bitmessage and I2P]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yp6]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>Is it possible to run PyBitmessage in <a href="http://cur.lv/65yp7">I2P</a> network?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yp8"> eskouga </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/65yp9">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/65yp6">[5 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 21:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Device not found. NO GPU output 3 Computers same issue?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have 3 computers that I want to use for mining when idle. 2 of them are windows 7 one of the is windows 8 all three are x64 base. two of them have 7700hd ATI cards and the third has a 7870HD XFX. All three are having same issue. No output. No GPU found on the devices. All three computes have same look on the screen no devices found. I have used catalyst drivers from V12.8-V13.11 and same with the SDKs I have used different versions of CGminer (V2.11.4 just crashes on startup). I would like to blow out the CPU's as well but that's another issue all together. My command lines along with my startup screens are below.</p>

<p>Please include your bitcoin/litecoin address with reply. </p>

<p>Thank you for your time!</p>

<pre><code>        cgminer -o ltc.give-me-coins.com:3333
</code></pre>

<p>CGMiner </p>

<h2> cgminer version 3.8.5 - Started: [2013-12-14 16:02:44]</h2>

<p>(5s):0.000 (avg):0.000h/s | A:0  R:0  HW:0  WU:0.0/m
 ST: 2  SS: 0  NB: 1  LW: 2  GF: 0  RF: 0
 Connected to ltc.give-me-coins.com diff 16 with stratum as user </p>

<h2> Block: cd82d7df...  Diff:2.93K  Started: [16:02:44]  Best share: 0</h2>

<h2> [P]ool management [S]ettings [D]isplay options [Q]uit</h2>

<p>[2013-12-14 16:02:38] Started cgminer 3.8.5
 [2013-12-14 16:02:40] No devices detected!</p>

<pre><code>        bfgminer.exe -o ltc.give-me-coins.com:3333
</code></pre>

<p>BFG miner</p>

<p>bfgminer version 3.8.1 - Started: [2013-12-14 16:01:01] - [  0 days 00:01:08]
[M]anage devices [P]ool management [S]ettings [D]isplay options  [H]elp [Q]uit
Connected to ltc.give-me-coins.com diff 16 with stratum as user 
Block: ...9616fd46 #479102  Diff:2.93k (20.95Gh/s)  Started: [16:01:01]
ST:2  F:0  NB:1  AS:0  BW:[631/ 20 B/s]  E:0.00  I: 0.00 BTC/hr  BS:0</p>

<h2>0            |   0.0/  0.0/  0.0 h/s | A:0 R:0+0(none) HW:0/none</h2>

<hr><p>[2013-12-14 16:01:00] Waiting for devices; press 'M+' to add, or 'Q' to quit
[2013-12-14 16:01:00] Probing for an alive pool
[2013-12-14 16:01:01] Pool 0 <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzq" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/6qxzr</a> alive</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>JoeyUser</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 05:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Why doesn't BTC depreciate in value as its supply increases?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The popular intuition is that that greater supply = less demand. I've looked around and haven't found a counter-argument. Why is the BTC gaining value as its quantity increases?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Leftover Salad</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 05:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Closed wallet on MultiBit, found it in AppData, but when I click &quot;open&quot; nothing happens]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have clicked on "close wallet" by mistake, and thought it was lost, and then found it in <code>C:user&lt;my name&gt;AppDataRoaming</code>... but, when I click to open the wallet nothing happens.</p>

<p>I have saved my private keys to a USB stick, and my public address is written down (this wallet is in <a href="http://cur.lv/6qxzu" rel="nofollow">MultiBit</a>). I have Windows 8.</p>

<p>Is it possible to recover my wallet?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Elle</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How does an online wallet relate to a local one?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qxzv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm pretty new to bitcoin so there are some questions that popped up during my "research" concerning the management of my wallet(s) and transactions in general.</p>

<p>To initially acquire some bitcoin I bought some small amount on localbitcoins.com.  The way I understand it localbitcoins.com created a wallet for me which keeps a record of all the transactions (key pairs) I was involved ergo the amount of bitcoins currently assigned to me. Since an online wallet will never be as secure as one created with a local client and because I wanna get a better understanding of how btc works I also installed MultiBit on my local machine.</p>

<p>Now here are my questions:</p>

<ol><li><p>Is my assumption right that I now own two fully valid wallets (although the local one is probably inexistent to the btc-ecosystem since it doesn't show up in any transaction) ?</p></li>
<li><p>Can these two wallets somehow be interlinked so when I buy more bitcoins the increase of my online wallet would be forwarded to my local one? Or can they even be merged so they are always in sync?
If not, do I have to transfer all the bitcoin from localbitcoin.com to my local wallet "manually" by issuing new transactions? If I would for example also buy from MtGox, do I have to create a wallet there as well an then transfer the btc from this wallet to my local one?
Or more generally, how do I get transactions done on different exchanges into one single wallet? </p></li>
<li><p>Is there a way to buy bitcoin (Euro for Bitcoin) with my local bitcoin client? Can I for example use the funds deposited on MtGox to make a transaction directly to my local wallet (i.e. with an adress created by MultiBit)?</p></li>
<li><p>Do online wallets provide something like an export to a wallet file which I could then import into MultiBit?</p></li>
</ol><p>Thanks very much in advance!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Flavio</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 23:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[/r/Bitcoin FAQ - Newcomers please read]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/68bfo]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div><p>This posts explains some dos and don'ts about what to post on <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokc">/r/Bitcoin</a> .</p> <p>First lets start with...</p> <hr><p><strong>Messaging mods</strong></p> <p>Modmail is for:</p> <ul><li>Problems with the subreddit (some sidebar links are broken for example)</li> <li>Problems with submissions (spam filter sometimes catches too much, we sort things a few times a day. If you have an <strong>urgent</strong> submission, contact us)</li> <li>Requests that need mod support - if you need us to verify your identity for say, AMA, or that you represent an organization, contact us and we'll do our best to help you</li> </ul><p>Modmail is <strong>not</strong> for:</p> <ul><li>Asking general questions</li> <li>Reporting obvious spam submissions (that's what the <strong>Report</strong> button is for)</li> <li>Advertisements on the subreddit (it is handled <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfp">through Reddit</a>, not us)</li> <li>Help with shadowbans (again, that's Reddit, not us. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfq">Contact them</a>)</li> </ul><p><strong>Frequent requests:</strong></p> <ul><li>"Can I get a flair?" - No, at the moment we are <strong>not</strong> giving anyone flair on the subreddit</li> <li>"Can you add my subreddit to the sidebar?" - If you are a local Bitcoin subreddit, we can add you to the wiki. If you are not a Bitcoin-related subreddit, 99% chance the answer is no. If you are a Bitcoin-related subreddit, we only add subreddits that are established - if you have less than a few hundred subscribers and less than a post a day, the answer is most likely no. Beyond that, we can talk.</li> <li>"Can you link to my website from the sidebar?" - No</li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Submissions</strong></p> <p><strong>Please don't post:</strong></p> <ul><li>Ask to be stickied - it's like asking for upvotes. People don't like it when you ask for upvotes.</li> <li>General questions about how Bitcoin works - go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfr">/r/BitcoinBeginners</a> or search in <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfs">http://cur.lv/68bfs</a> .</li> <li>General newcomer questions, like "which client should I use?", "how do I buy Bitcoin?" - again, <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfr">/r/BitcoinBeginners</a></li> <li>Questions about mining - go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bft">/r/bitcoinmining</a></li> <li>"Is it profitable to mine?" - punch your numbers into <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfu">a calculator</a> or go to <a href="http://cur.lv/68bft">/r/bitcoinmining</a></li> <li>"Should I buy Bitcoin?" / "Is it still worth investing in Bitcoin?" - You shouldn't take financial advice from the Internet, you need to figure this out for yourself</li> <li>"What about altcoin X?" / "Should I buy altcoin X?" / "You should buy altcoin X!" - This is a very big topic in itself. Short answer is no under most circumstances. For a longer explanation, please read <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfv">my blog entry</a> and the accompanying <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfw">reddit submission</a> for discussion on the topic.</li> <li>Asking for money - unless you are a reputable charity, your post will be treated like spam</li> <li>Complaints about not buying Bitcoins when they were $X/BTC - nobody cares</li> <li>Referral links - your post will be treated like spam</li> <li>"BUYBUYBUY"/"SELLSELLSELL" - you will be treated like a troll</li> <li>Submissions or posts with curse words directed at someone - don't insult other people. Your posts will be treated like spam otherwise. Occasional expressions like "holy shit this is awesome!" are tolerated in moderation.</li> <li>"Can I buy less than 1 bitcoin?" - The answer is "yes, you can purchase as little as 0.00000001 BTC at a time, you don't have to buy a whole coin, similarly how you can buy a gram of gold, you don't need to buy a whole gold bar"</li> <li>"What happens after all 21M BTC are mined?" - Either Bitcoin will be long gone before then (if the system doesn't catch on), or <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfx">miners will be earning their money from transaction fees instead</a>.</li> <li>"What happens to lost coins?" - Lost coins remain lost, unless someone finds a private key for them. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfy">This is <strong>ONLY</strong> viable if quantum computers become strong enough</a>. Otherwise, <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfz">the numbers used by Bitcoin are too big to be brute forced - heat death of the universe will occur before a colission is found.</a>. <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg0">As for re-mining old bitcoins, there are many reasons to not return lost coins back to circulation.</a></li> </ul><p><strong>Take heed when posting:</strong></p> <ul><li>Memes - memes are allowed, but some people may not like you for posting them. Be sure to use <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg1">/r/Bitcoinmemes</a> as well</li> <li>Information about all-time-highs, price spikes, crashes and so forth - 90% of the time, someone has already posted about it. Check <a href="http://cur.lv/68bg2">/r/bitcoin/new</a> first before posting.</li> <li>Questions about help with a particular website or business - <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokc">/r/Bitcoin</a> is not tech support for any business, you're better off contacting the support of the business in question through their forums or ticket system</li> </ul><p><strong>What to do if you see...</strong></p> <ul><li>Spam - click "report" underneath the submission, vote accordingly. Don't message mods unless the spam is subtle or needs context</li> <li>Repost - vote accordingly, click "report"</li> <li>A post from the "don't" list above - direct the posted to a proper subreddit if applicable (for questions and newbie posts), vote and report accordingly otherwise</li> <li>A post that is allowed on this subreddit but you don't like it being here - vote accordingly, don't report it. If it is allowed, the mods will not remove the post. Your votes shape what submissions get the most exposure - upvote the posts you want to see more of, downvote the ones you want to see less of.</li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Some good guides you should look into:</strong></p> <ul><li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg3">Will I earn money by mining?</a></li> <li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg4">Basic Bitcoin security guide</a></li> <li><a href="http://cur.lv/68bg5">The straightforward Bitcoin safety and security guide</a></li> </ul><hr><p><strong>Please do</strong></p> <ul><li>Read the sidebar for community rules - following them will make everyone's day better.</li> <li>Be sceptical of any news without credible sources - a lot of bad people are trying to play on your emotions by fabricating fake stories. Be sceptical of any story without a credible citation, especially when it is related to economic or legal side of things.</li> </ul><hr><p>Thank you for your attention. Post responsibly, vote on all submissions, live and let live, have fun.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> submitted by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokl"> ThePiachu </a> <br><a href="http://cur.lv/68bfo">[link]</a> <a href="http://cur.lv/68bfo">[189 comments]</a>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 04:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yokm]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yqt"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>November 02, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokp" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yqt"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qxzw(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxzx">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3180 from pstratem/processgetdata]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yra]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3180 from pstratem/processgetdata

Reduce latency in network processing</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3180 from pstratem/processgetdata

Reduce latency in network processing</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 05:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[process received messages one at a time without sleeping between messages]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrb]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>process received messages one at a time without sleeping between messages</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>process received messages one at a time without sleeping between messages</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>pstratem</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 04:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3154 from gavinandresen/mempool_refactor]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrc]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3154 from gavinandresen/mempool_refactor

Mempool refactor</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3154 from gavinandresen/mempool_refactor

Mempool refactor</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 04:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Refactor: CTxMempool class to its own txmempool.{cpp,h}]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrd]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Refactor: CTxMempool class to its own txmempool.{cpp,h}</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Refactor: CTxMempool class to its own txmempool.{cpp,h}</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 01:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3193 from joshtriplett/patch-1]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yre]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3193 from joshtriplett/patch-1

.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3193 from joshtriplett/patch-1

.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 02:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrf]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories

Unless a .gitignore pattern is anchored, it'll match in any directory, not juts at the top level.  Simplify .gitignore accordingly.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>.gitignore: Simplify references to the same file in different directories

Unless a .gitignore pattern is anchored, it'll match in any directory, not juts at the top level.  Simplify .gitignore accordingly.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>joshtriplett</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3087]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3087

caca6aa Make some globals in main non-public. (Pieter Wuille)
85eb2ce Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database. (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3087

caca6aa Make some globals in main non-public. (Pieter Wuille)
85eb2ce Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database. (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 14:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yokw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>26 lines (14 sloc)</span><span>1.232 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>Join our Bitmessage chan! First, download the client from bitmessage.org. Then, go to file --&gt; Join/Create chan --&gt; Join Chan and enter the following details (use the full name of the chan including the "created by" part)</p>
<p><strong>Name of chan:</strong> Bitcoin Crowdfunding incubator (Created by BM-2cVPTkVZo2mDoJyXmaGkujtJNovVhu6W1H)<br><strong>Chan address:</strong> BM-2cVVS3U9zdfDyQRxP8wsLUG3epavsqsDja<br></p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoky" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://cur.lv/5yoky"></a><br><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokz" rel="nofollow"><br>Image created by </a><a href="http://cur.lv/5yol0" rel="nofollow">Jack Z</a></p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qxzy(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qxzz">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is Ad5.eu a scam/legit site?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow5o]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Researched answers please. I would also appreciate it if you've used the service before. Ad5.eu is a URL shortener site, but pays, like Adf.ly and CoinURL. The rates are really high, and I'm wondering if it's a scam or not. Please give researched answers, or even better, your experience with this service.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 11:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yol4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>November 01, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yol6" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy00(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy01">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yola]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>15 lines (12 sloc)</span><span>0.604 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>You can <em>visit any project in the browser</em> by surfing to entrances.github.com/[ProjectName].html</p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy02(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy03">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3128]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrr]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3128

0056095 Show short scriptPubKeys correctly (Peter Todd)
22de68d Relay OP_RETURN TxOut as standard transaction type (Peter Todd)

Signed-off-by: Gavin Andresen <gavinandresen></gavinandresen></pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3128

0056095 Show short scriptPubKeys correctly (Peter Todd)
22de68d Relay OP_RETURN TxOut as standard transaction type (Peter Todd)

Signed-off-by: Gavin Andresen <gavinandresen></gavinandresen></pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 02:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3114]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrs]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3114

a616206 Give peer time-adjustment data an own lock (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3114

a616206 Give peer time-adjustment data an own lock (Pieter Wuille)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Make some globals in main non-public.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yru]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Make some globals in main non-public.

This means they are declared static, and their extern definition in
main.h is removed. Also moved CBlockIndexWorkComparator to the .cpp
file.</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Make some globals in main non-public.

This means they are declared static, and their extern definition in
main.h is removed. Also moved CBlockIndexWorkComparator to the .cpp
file.</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 23:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database.]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database.

As block index entries have a flag for marking invalid blocks, the
'best invalid work' information can be derived from there. In addition,
remove the global from main.h</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Do not use the redundant BestInvalidWork record in the block database.

As block index entries have a flag for marking invalid blocks, the
'best invalid work' information can be derived from there. In addition,
remove the global from main.h</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>sipa</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 23:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3159]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrv]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3159

9eb4ab6 transactionview: make exportClicked() use message() (Philip Kaufmann)
868d3ee transactionview: add message() signal (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3159

9eb4ab6 transactionview: make exportClicked() use message() (Philip Kaufmann)
868d3ee transactionview: add message() signal (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 16:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3189]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrw]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3189

71ba467 [Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message() (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3189

71ba467 [Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message() (Philip Kaufmann)</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 07:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3067 from Diapolo/debug-switch]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrx]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3067 from Diapolo/debug-switch

re-work -debug switch handling</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3067 from Diapolo/debug-switch

re-work -debug switch handling</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 22:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What do I do with all my old block erupters?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qy04]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I'm making like nothing off these guys and am looking to use them for something else.  I guess these ASICs are designed for SHA-256 hash function based cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>Try to mine Terracoin?</p>

<p>cryptocurrency list:
<a href="http://cur.lv/65yhh" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/65yhh</a></p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>tarabyte</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[[Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message()]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yry]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>[Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message()

- add new processSendCoinsReturn() function, which parses the
  status of WalletModel::SendCoinsReturn and generates a pair consisting
  of a message and message flags
- result is we only need one emit message() call
- this change ensures that the GUI is shown for warnings/errors in
  sendcoinsdialog, because of message() taking care of that for modal
  messages
- changes 2 warning message into error messages and removed "Error:"
  in front of the actual error message string</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>[Qt] sendcoinsdialog: convert QMessageBox usage to message()

- add new processSendCoinsReturn() function, which parses the
  status of WalletModel::SendCoinsReturn and generates a pair consisting
  of a message and message flags
- result is we only need one emit message() call
- this change ensures that the GUI is shown for warnings/errors in
  sendcoinsdialog, because of message() taking care of that for modal
  messages
- changes 2 warning message into error messages and removed "Error:"
  in front of the actual error message string</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[transactionview: make exportClicked() use message()]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yrz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: make exportClicked() use message()

- use message() for displaying success or failure of export
- rework the strings to be more detailed / informative
- additional small cleanups</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: make exportClicked() use message()

- use message() for displaying success or failure of export
- rework the strings to be more detailed / informative
- additional small cleanups</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[transactionview: add message() signal]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys0]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: add message() signal

- allow to use message() in transactionview by connecting to the
  message() signal in WalletView</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>transactionview: add message() signal

- allow to use message() in transactionview by connecting to the
  message() signal in WalletView</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3160 from Diapolo/walletview]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys1]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3160 from Diapolo/walletview

[Qt] walletview: make backupWallet() use GUIUtil::getSaveFileName()</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3160 from Diapolo/walletview

[Qt] walletview: make backupWallet() use GUIUtil::getSaveFileName()</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>laanwj</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[re-work -debug switch handling]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>re-work -debug switch handling

- re-work -debug help message text
- make -debug log every debugging information again (even all categories)
- remove unneeded fDebug checks in front of LogPrint()/qDebug(), as that
  check is done in LogPrintf() when category is != NULL (true for all
  LogPrint() calls
- remove fDebug ONLY in code which is NOT performance-critical
- harmonize addrman category name
- deprecate -debugnet usage, should be used via -debug=net and remove the
  corresponding global</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>re-work -debug switch handling

- re-work -debug help message text
- make -debug log every debugging information again (even all categories)
- remove unneeded fDebug checks in front of LogPrint()/qDebug(), as that
  check is done in LogPrintf() when category is != NULL (true for all
  LogPrint() calls
- remove fDebug ONLY in code which is NOT performance-critical
- harmonize addrman category name
- deprecate -debugnet usage, should be used via -debug=net and remove the
  corresponding global</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Diapolo</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Merge pull request #3176 from Diapolo/key]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ys3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3176 from Diapolo/key

fix wrong memcmp() usage in CKey::operator==</pre>]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[<pre>Merge pull request #3176 from Diapolo/key

fix wrong memcmp() usage in CKey::operator==</pre>]]></content:encoded>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>gavinandresen</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 08:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yole]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>October 28, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolf" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65yrm"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy05(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy06">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[18 lines (13 sloc)]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolj]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div><div>
<span>18 lines (13 sloc)</span><span>0.598 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>These are our crowdfunding entries:</p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolk" rel="nofollow">http://cur.lv/5yolk</a><br></p></article></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy07(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy08">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy09(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy0a">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolt]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div><div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysa"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>October 19, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yolv" rel="nofollow">.</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysa"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy0b(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy0c">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Fetching contributors…]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yolz]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
    Fetching contributors&hellip;

    <div>
<p><img src="http://cur.lv/5yokx"></p>
<p>Cannot retrieve contributors at this time</p>
</div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>14 lines (11 sloc)</span><span>0.509 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p>You can visit any project in the browser by surfing to entrances.github.com/[ProjectName].html</p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy0d(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy0e">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 05:24:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[What does the US government do with seized coins?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6ow63]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>It was reported today that the US government shut down the web site Silk Road, where people bought and sold things (allegedly including illegal drugs) using Bitcoins.  The operator was arrested, and BTC 26000 was seized.  (Source: <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow64">New York Times</a>).</p>

<p>A few months ago, it was also <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow65">reported </a> that the US Drug Enforcement Agency seized BTC 11.02 from a person suspected of buying or selling illegal drugs.</p>

<p>Is anything known about what the US government (or any other government) does with seized coins?</p>

<p>Some possibilities:</p>

<ul><li><p>Sell them on an exchange for USD, and turn the proceeds over to the Treasury</p></li>
<li><p>Sell them at public auction, as is commonly done with other seized property</p></li>
<li><p>Use them in future sting operations</p></li>
<li><p>Do not return them to circulation, but hold them indefinitely</p></li>
<li><p>Destroy them by transferring them to <a href="http://cur.lv/6ow66">an address with no private key</a></p></li>
</ul>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Nate Eldredge</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 20:55:53 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Entrances]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/5yom3]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div><div><div>
<div>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysj"><span><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a></span><time>September 24, 2013</time><div><a href="http://cur.lv/5yom5" rel="nofollow">Update README.md</a></div>
<div><p><a href="http://cur.lv/5yokq" rel="nofollow"><strong>1</strong> contributor</a></p></div>
<div>
<h2>Users who have contributed to this file</h2>
<ul><li>
<img src="http://cur.lv/65ysj"><a href="http://cur.lv/5yoko" rel="nofollow">Entrances</a>
</li></ul></div>
</div>
<div><div>
<div><div>
<span>14 lines (10 sloc)</span><span>0.408 kb</span>
</div></div>
<div><article><p></p>
<p></p>
<p></p>
<p>Hey! Welcome to the Web Developer's group!</p>
<p>We build stuff together. Have a look at the projects at entrances.github.com</p>
<p>If you want to discuss contracts, payments or other sensitive information, send a Bitmessage to <strong>BM-2D7XVMiTuyLtSGF6t4NERnUDrfbZvTdtG4</strong></p>
<p></p></article></div>
</div></div>
</div></div></div></div></div></div>
        <br>
        This post has been generated by <a href="http://cur.lv/5yokr">Page2RSS</a>
        <img width="1" height="1" src="http://cur.lv/6qy0f(feed)%7Cutmcsr%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FEntrances%2Fentrances.github.com%2Fblob%2Fmaster%2FREADME.md%7Cutmcmd%3Drss%3B%2B"><img src="http://cur.lv/6qy0g">]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is there a way to accept bitcoin payments and verify the identity of the people who paid without asking for any other information?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qy0h]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I have a website and I am considering supporting bitcoins, but I would like to do this without asking the users to log in nor give me their email or details before buying.</p>

<p>Is there a way to accept bitcoin payments and verify the identity of the people who paid without asking for any other information?</p>

<p>I would like the buyers to claim their product after they pay, using the transaction id, the confirmation number, the address... or something like this, so I do not have to ask for any other information before they buy, but I can be sure that I deliver the product to the right person.</p>

<p>That is, you can pay directly using my btc address (that will be different for each transaction) and you do not have to enter anything else. 
After the transaction is confirmed, you can come back to the website and you can claim the product entering a "code". (Only then you'll be asked for the email or more details).</p>

<p>Can I use the pair of transaction addresses as this code? Is this secret or other people will be able to claim they paid?</p>

<p>Thank you very much!!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>aninom</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 17:06:21 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is it safe to connect multiple alternative crypto currency clients to the same TOR socks port?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qy0i]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Or should I create multiple TOR socks ports and use one for each client?</p>

<p>I plan on running bitcoind, namecoind, litecoind, etc... all on the same ubuntu machine running under different users but all going though the same TOR connection.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user3145</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 23:14:43 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How did you find out about Bitcoins?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yso]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>I found out about bitcoins from an article on Mashable a few days ago, I've spend my days since then researching all about them and now hoping to get 1 shiney BTC. </p>
<p>How'd you find out about bitcoins?</p>
<p>Edit: by the way I'd love to offer a reward but I literally have no coins, my computer isnt powerful enough to mine and I havent earnt enough to transfer to my wallet yet :(</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>kerodean</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 17:28:01 +0100</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Something to laugh at?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65ysp]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Sudden boredom has led to me posting this. Got any video, image or text that seems to make people laugh? Why don't you post it here to prevent boredom of me and others! (May tip very funny stuff)</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scythe</author>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 09:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How do I export my private keys from my Bitcoin-Qt client?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/6qy0j]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Trying to use this posted method:</p>

<p>To export a private key from your Satoshi bitcoin-qt client:</p>

<pre><code>launch your bitcoin client as usual and wait for it to load the blockchain and start up
click on 'help' in the menu bar (top right)
click on 'debug window'
select the 'console' tab
type: walletpassphrase "your walletpassphrase here" 600
type: dumpprivkey [your public key here]
this will return the private key, you can copy it now; ensure you clear your clipboard/history afterwards
type: walletlock
</code></pre>

<p>I do not understand what "your walletpassphrase here" means.  I do not have a wallet pass phrase to the best of my knowledge.</p>

<p>Also, I am a bit of an amateur at this and I still don't understand the "your public key here"..... is that the address that corresponds to your wallet?</p>

<p>Trying to export the private key to another wallet because the bitcoin wallet has taken 2 days to synch and is still not done.</p>

<p>Any help would be very appreciated.</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>user2865</author>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[Can you find some "bugs"?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yt2]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by <a href="http://cur.lv/65yt3">this thread</a> on bitcointalk.org we decided to offer bounties for finding software bugs and vulnerabilities on Rugatu, so here is your chance to earn bitcoins while doing some ethical hacking.</p>
<p>Here is a small list so you can make an idea of what to expect, although every contribution will be rewarded.</p>
<ul><li>0.001 BTC Embarrassing language mistakes and typos<br></li>
<li>0.0025 BTC Unknown unexpected behavior (e.g. endless loops, links to 404 pages, UI issues ...)<br></li>
<li>0.005 BTC Harmless XSS problems<br></li>
<li>0.010 BTC CSRF and XSS problems</li>
<li>0.05 BTC Critical CSRF and XSS problems (e.g. possibility of session stealing)</li>
<li>0.1 BTC Manipulating parts of the DB</li>
<li>0.25 BTC RFI/LFI bugs</li>
<li>0.5 BTC Full access to the Database</li>
<li>1 BTC Full root access to the server</li>
<li>2 BTC Stealing coins from the hot wallet.</li>
</ul><p>Rules:</p>
<ul><li>No (D)DoS</li>
<li>Security related bugs have to be reported privately - report at rugatu dot com</li>
<li>Once a bug is abused you won't get a reward anymore</li>
<li>UI issues have to apply for at least 2% of the users (IE 6 problems are ignored)</li>
</ul><p>Have fun.</p>
<p>11.18.2013 Rewards updated</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>paraipan</author>
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 02:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[First bitcoin]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yt4]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a pic my my FIRST bitcoin :) thinking about hanging it on my wall.</p>
<p><img alt="alt text" src="http://cur.lv/65yt5"></p>
<p>anyone else have pics of their very first bitcoins?</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Scott</author>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title><![CDATA[How do you like Rugatu on facebook?]]></title>
<link><![CDATA[http://cur.lv/65yt8]]></link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Our facebook page isn't too fancy but it definitely needs some love, so for every "like" you give we tip you here on Rugatu, only make sure you answer to this question. </p>
<p><a href="http://cur.lv/65yt9">Rugatu Q&amp;A Community on Facebook</a></p>
<p>Please tell us your suggestions on how to make it better too. Thanks and good luck!</p>]]></description>
<enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
<author>Rugatu</author>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 16:20:35 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>